How about earning money as a pro baseball player?
If you use magic to pitch at like 1,000 km/h,
you could get a huge contract!
You'd make a killing!
When I was in high school,
I hated the guys on the baseball team.
They acted like they owned the classroom.
Then—
But, I knew that they practiced hard,
sweating under the brutal sun.
I wouldn't want to trample on their efforts
by cheating with magic.
Uncle.
For about six years,
from elementary school through high school,
I dedicated my life to Alien Soldier.
I know how they must've felt, as I sweated like they did.
No, you don't. Apologize to all baseball players right now.
He seriously believes what he's saying.
Uncle from Another World
Uncle from Another World
Uncle from Another World
gets
to
decide
The
way I
should
and
shouldn't
live?
[UNCLE]
[UNCLE] Th
[UNCLE] That
[UNCLE] That's c
[UNCLE] That's comp
[UNCLE] That's complet
[UNCLE] That's completely
[UNCLE] That's completely fi
[UNCLE] That's completely fine.
GET HOME
GET HOME
Sold cheaper than a scouring pad
June, 2018
Compared to other sports, don't you think
that baseball terminology sounds kinda dangerous?
Like dead balls and stolen bases?
And sacrifice flies and twin killing?
Exactly.
That reminds me, I almost got assassinated once.
Huh?
That's a heck of a topic change!
Icuras Elran.
In this incident, I was totally exhausted
after exploring a dungeon.
Hold on, this person...
They were there when you broke the Luvaldram barrier.
They were also there when you were drunk with Elf.
True, they were!
Were they just waiting for the right moment?
Seriously?
Found you.
Mabel.
What's wrong?
You! Because you slew the Blaze Dragon
without sealing it with the God-Freezing Sword!
You released me from my meaningless duty
to hand the sword down to an heir!
Hooray!
Great! Good for you! I'm glad that my hard work paid off!
Yes! Yes!
He's not picking up on the sarcasm at all!
Mabel's life's going down the drain because of Uncle!
Why?
Why didn't you draw your blade?
I'm constantly attacked by people with intent to kill,
as if I'm living inside a Psikyo shoot 'em up game.
So I can tell that you have no murderous intent at all.
Actually, your complexion's looking a bit off.
Are you eating well?
I know... that you... saved the village.
So that's the time Mabel tried to kill me,
but I ended up taking her to an inn.
You dragged her!
Where am I?
An inn.
Here.
So? What happened?
I thought you were going home to be a hermit.
When I returned, my house
was being cut down for firewood.
The mayor said I needed to work
and earn my own way through life.
Mabel
Manu
If I didn't agree to that, they'd breed me like a pet.
This world is super messed up.
The villagers must have had
a hell of a grudge against the Ice Clan!
So, which one did you choose?
I froze the villagers' legs with the God-Freezing Sword,
dripped cold water on their necks, and ran away.
All the villagers?
All 108.
Damn, how tenacious are you?!
Now I can't go back!
Does the idea of working really bother you that much?
Well...
Surrounded by beautiful flowers in a flower shop,
tasting delicious samples at a bakery,
or cuddling fluffy stuffed animals in a toy store...
I don't have the willpower to endure such harsh labor.
Which part of those jobs was harsh?
Her standards are ridiculous!
I understand.
Working your life away on the daily grind in an office...
Going drinking with coworkers after work...
I wouldn't be able to handle that.
What? Uncle has strong views on typical white-collar jobs?
Working in Japan was so easy 18 years ago!
※Life was rough back then too
But I'm supporting myself as an adventurer now.
It's the best job to let me search
for a way back to my world.
You're amazing.
I wish I could have something like that.
What? Amazing?
Well, in my world, I did beat Alien Soldier
on super hard in under 30 minutes.
Huh? Is that good?
Yeah, and I'm using those skills I learned
from video games to become a better adventurer!
Your world?
Mabel, you were a guardian all your life.
Can't you make a living using the God-Freezing Sword?
That freezing magic you used earlier
was pretty impressive.
I-I, the guardian, should use the God-Freezing Sword?
But, my clan kept it for four hundred years—
It's like I told you before.
No matter what anyone says, this is your life, Mabel.
You choose what you want to do.
The power to do that is what strength is.
You remember it.
For now, maybe I should find a way
to break the ice seal completely.
I went to Mount Marchid to pick powa-powa blossoms,
but nothing happened.
Really?
The ice seal is linked to my heart.
If I become an adventurer
and work on fixing my gloomy personality,
then maybe that'll help.
Gloomy?
I think being an introvert is perfectly fine!
I-It's not fine.
The villagers said they
get depressed just being around me.
My eyes are always puffy too.
I disagree!
It's fun talking with you,
and your eyes are gorgeous
like Hether's from Dynamite Headdy!
No, wait, you're making me blush!
Oh, that's right. That thing on your left hand.
What?
It'll support you for the rest of your life.
It's my way of accepting responsibility,
as the one who took away your duty.
Please accept it.
F-For the rest of my life?
What's this geezer doing?!
That's twice now.
I put it on you while you were sleeping.
Um... I... but...
I'm sorry.
I respect you, but I don't think of you in that way.
I can't accept this.
It's melting, it's melting!
Her icy heart was thawed in an instant!
Come on, it's okay!
N-No, it's n-not good. Wh-Why?
I-I rejected him, r-right? I-I did.
Huh? I-I said no, r-right?
I found it while exploring today.
Maybe this was meant to be.
This is a cosmite ring,
said to be one of only seven in existence.
It's my token of apology.
B-But it's so valuable!
Well, it's getting late now.
Stay here for tonight.
It's a small bed, so there's not much room.
Elf is staying here too, so maybe you can stay in her room.
E-Excuse me.
What?
Do you have any money I can borrow for the bathhouse?
I haven't bathed in a while.
Do you think you smell?
You smell a little earthy, but it's not a bad smell.
D-Don't smell me!
Well, if you sell the ring, you can easily afford the fee.
Huh?
Sell the ring?
Yeah.
As I said, sell the ring and never worry
about money for the rest of your life.
Hey, orc face!
It's too late for this!
Have you awakened to some sort of orc instinct?
Th-Then, I'll stay with you until you feel bett—
He turned me down, and yet...
Hey, you! Lend me a hand! She's out of control!
So that's how it is.
Huh? Wai—Stop!
My defense is weak because I spent my spirits
in the dungeon earlier today!
And that's how I was nearly assassinated,
but got sealed in ice overnight instead.
Isn't that horrible?
Yeah.
Yes.
You were horrible.
Still, you're amazing!
You said you beat Alien Soldier in 30 minutes?
To be precise, it was 29 minutes and 29 seconds!
It was so intense.
Really?
The key is to not use
the more player-friendly Homing Force,
but to rush through the early stages
with Ranger Force instead.
Wow, someone beat it in 12 minutes in this video!
How dare you, internet?
It's not the internet's fault, Uncle.
Speaking of the internet,
what are these North American versions
of games I keep seeing online?
Oh, that's the region code.
The same game can be in different languages
depending on the sales region.
My English isn't the strongest,
but I kind of understand what's said
at the beginning of Altered Beast.
Like, "Go, Hero, defeat the evil!" or something like that.
Wait, let me use a translation app.
Rise from your grave.
Grave?!
The main character was dead?!
You didn't understand the story at all.
Why's that?
Perhaps my blood from another world.
Wait, they're still talking.
I think that he might be the same
as the ancestors of the Ice Clan—
someone transported here from Japanbahamal in Irellars.
Wait, she just said...
Granbahamal Raybelio
Mi Ld Shyiene Zad
All creation, summon an ice storm
I am not an orc
Hey, she just said "Japanbahamal."
What?
How do they know about Japan?
Let's take a look.
What a disaster that he put the ring on you
while you were sleeping.
Marriage while sleeping, let alone
a forced marriage by an orc while sleeping,
is a lifelong trauma.
No one would marry you after you married a filthy orc.
But don't let it bring you down.
A-Actually, you don't seem to mind.
Why's that?
Perhaps my blood from another world.
I think that he might be the same
as the ancestors of the Ice Clan—
someone transported here from Japanbahamal in Irellars.
Now I see.
I had no idea they were talking
about this while I was frozen.
They're talking about Japan, right?
Raybelio Yuul Elran.
The founder of the Ice Clan
was a knight from Japanbahamal who lived 400 years ago.
He lost his life in a great battle in Japanbahamal,
and was bestowed a new life and body in Granbahamal.
Then, he received a message from God.
"Transported one."
"I shall grant you one power
to aid your survival in this harsh world."
The knight responded with his wish.
"Give me a sword that can slay you."
A divine bonus!
A parallel world reincarnation classic!
The knight's reply was so cool!
What happened next?!
God responded,
"You wish to have the power to slay God."
"Ha ha ha, how interesting." Howev—
Anyway, does that ugly orc face really look human to you?
"Ha ha ha, how interesting."
Because you share blood?
"...interesting."
Is that why?
"...intere—"
You can't be serious.
I-It's just getting interesting.
C-Could you be a little more patient?
I read all this in a book in my village.
Shoo, shoo.
The knight acquired the God-Freezing Sword
and studied at the shrine of knowledge,
broke the seal of the sword
by falling in love with a shrine maiden,
and slew the Blaze Dragon.
The sword's been passed down your clan for generations.
She spoiled it just when it was getting interesting!
B-Back to my point, how do you see orc face?
T-Telling this story is the only thing I'm good at.
I practiced so hard.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry! Don't cry.
Th-There, there.
I didn't get anything.
Huh?
What?
I didn't get anything cool like the God-Freezing Sword!
You must have received
your magic power as your divine bonus.
I didn't get any bonus!
I didn't even talk with God!
Then, let's look at the moment
you were transported 18 years ago!
That's it!
18 years ago?
Can you even go back that far?
It was a long time ago, so it may take a while to search.
Well...
Mob lynches, execution, execution...
He's mumbling some disturbing things!
He was constantly hunted
because they thought he was an orc variant.
Seriously?
Found it!
You shitty orc! Are you trying to eat my cow?
No, Uncle, this isn't the right one!
Then how about this one?
Cleanse this evil orc that dares defy our dogma!
That's the time you made the magical pot!
So, this one?
Nope!
This one?
No!
This?
Why the heck were you hunted so much?!
I'm a real heavy sleeper.
If I'm attacked while I'm asleep, I sleep right through it.
It's amazing you managed to survive this long.
Oh, is this it?
What's going on?
It's similar to the holy magic resurrection spell.
I first witnessed this spell much later on.
What's it doing in such an old memory?
Isn't that you when you were 17,
right when you arrived there?
Of course.
This was how my body was formed in Granbahamal.
So did God create your body?
It seems like it.
This is where I was first mistaken
for an orc variant and beaten up.
I didn't know their language,
but I offered them my money.
They mistook the cash for spell cards
and beat me even more.
It was January 2000.
I was off to buy new video games with my holiday money.
I was super happy but got in an accident
on the way, and the rest is history.
I wonder what game I was going to buy.
That's some dark stuff.
W-Wait. I hear something.
Huh? Is this God's voice?
Wait, let me turn up the volume.
Wǒ shì yì shìjiè zhī shén.
Nǐ shì zhuǎnyí zhī rén.
Zài zhège yánkù de shìjiè lǐ
wǒ huì cìyǔ nǐ yìzhǒng shēngcún de lìliàng.
I don't understand this!
Did God mix up the region code or something?
What could God be mumbling
while I was getting clobbered senseless?
Uncle, I'll translate it! Please rewind 30 seconds!
Okay.
Qīn'ài de gùkè péngyǒu. Nǐmen hǎo.
Greetings, dear
customers and friends.
We sincerely welcome
you to Granbahamal.
Zhōngxīn huānyíng nín guānglín Granbahamal.
A store announcement?
This is totally prerecorded.
They're saying, "I shall grant you
one power," just like Mabel said.
Wǒ shì yì shìjiè zhī shén.
Nǐ shì zhuǎnyí zhī rén.
I see.
Zài zhège yánkù de shìjiè lǐ...
What I desired at that moment became my ability.
So your powers must have awakened then!
This is when you gained unrivaled magic power!
Your wish must've been something like
"I want the power to kill these shitheads"!
Or "Make them miserable
and make them regret ever being born," right?
T-Takafumi, did something happen to you
while you were in high school?
※His family fell apart
No, if I recall correctly, what I was thinking was...
If only...
If only I could speak their language,
we could understand each other!
Yeah, that was it.
Shēnqǐng tōngguò.
Wǒ shíxiànle nǐ de yuànwàng.
Uh...
Dēngshàng Doldo de shāndǐng.
"Approved. Your wish has been granted."
Nǐ jiù kěyǐ zài zhīshì de shèngdì
huòdé zuìdī xiàndù de zhīshì.
"Climb to the top of Mount Dold to begin
your acquisition of knowledge," it says.
So, then, Uncle's magic power was...
translation?
That's so lame.
Suddenly I understood their language,
so I guess that was my bonus.
Could you have just learned the language
at Mount Dold instead?
I am not...
I am not an orc!
Oh, I see.
This is how you managed to work it all out!
Well, this is quite expected of Uncle, in a way.
No.
I was sold to a freak show
as a rare orc who knew the human language.
I was worth three copper.
And then—
Wait, Uncle!
I need some coffee.
Me too!
Oh, good idea!
Let's have a break!
God seemed to have lost their passion for their job.
The people of the other world were as shitty as always.
The horrible story seemed to have no end,
so we decided to have a coffee break.
This is good.
Good beans.
What a profoundly deep flavor.
Your shadow inevitably lengthens
As I wave you goodbye
Why do you never notice?
I've been looking at you for so long
These emotions I can't express
Are searching for a place to go
A brush of orange in the sky
Gently rises above
A melody rings
As I wish upon a tiny, tiny star
Someday it will shine bright
In that sky that's far away
I wish I could make it clear, I wish you could understand
My love for you is infinite
It twinkles like a star
Shining only for you