Why aren't you...
wearing anything... down below?
I'm not sure how to answer that...
Duty?
Uh... Francesca, was it?
Yes. Please call me Cesca.
For now, could you go put something on?
It's, um, hard for me to look at you.
But I'm wearing panties.
More than that!
Calm down, calm down.
It's a swimsuit. It's a swimsuit...
They're panties!
They're absolutely panties!
You glanced at them, didn't you?
Sorry!
Well, if you insist, then I'll put something on.
Why weren't you wearing it from the start?!
You won't do anything?
I won't. I won't, so hurry up and put it on.
I wouldn't mind you touching a little bit.
Just hurry up and put it on!
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 11
Panties, and an Aerial Garden
Uh, there's a lot I'd like to ask... Do you mind?
No, go ahead.
First of all, where on earth are we?
The Garden of Babylon, floating in the sky.
An aerial garden?
Please follow me.
I see.
So what's the purpose of this facility?
It's a garden the professor built as a hobby.
The professor?
Professor Regina Babylon.
Our creator.
Creator?
Master, this person isn't human.
I can't sense the flow of life within her.
I was built by the professor
to serve as this garden's control terminal.
That was 5,092 years ago.
Five—
Then you're a machine, Cesca?
Not all of me is mechanical.
I have some biological parts
that were created with magic, as well,
so "an amalgam of machine and magical life form"
would be a proper description.
Wow. You look just like a normal girl.
I cannot produce children, but I am capable of intercourse.
I didn't ask about that!
Whoa! Don't lift your skirt!
It's still in mint condition.
I didn't ask about that!
If you have need, please ask at any time.
I don't really understand her.
Neither do I.
Still, over 5,000 years...
This goes for you, too,
but after all that time, hasn't this aerial
garden ever deteriorated or malfunctioned?
All parts of it have been reinforced with magic.
I remain on standby, except in emergencies,
so maintenance of this garden has been left on auto.
Huh? Then what about now?
One could say this is an emergency.
We finally have a guest.
Speaking of which, what is your name?
Oh, it's Touya. Mochizuki Touya.
Touya. I have recognized you as suitably compatible.
As of this moment, Unit #23, code name "Francesca,"
will be transferred to your command.
Please take good care of her for many years.
Compatible?
Only someone possessing all affinities,
like the professor, could have activated that magic circle.
So there was someone who possessed
all affinities over 5,000 years ago?
The professor decided to pass us on to someone compatible
and capable of passing through that magic circle.
That was over 5,070 years ago.
So someone compatible
is someone who possesses all affinities?
No, it's not.
Huh?
I recognized you as compatible because you told me
to cover myself when you saw me in my panties.
That's why?! What does
that make me compatible with? I don't get it!
It's important.
If you had given in to your lust and assaulted me,
I would've thrown you down to the surface.
Furthermore, if you had done nothing
and let me remain in my panties,
I would've deemed you incompatible and
politely asked you to return to the surface.
Seriously?
Your reason for exposing your panties was that deep?
To determine whether someone had the kindness
and consideration to be put in charge of us,
the professor decided on this method.
I mean, I get it, but still...
That professor's crazy.
I don't deny that.
You don't?
The professor said she would leave
the final decision in our hands.
If I'm to have someone as my master,
I believe a closet pervert who steals glances,
controls himself, and feigns disinterest,
would be safer than someone who's a bit too kind
and familiar with women, and acts like a feminist.
What do you mean, "closet pervert?" That's rude!
And "safer" somehow irritates me, too!
With that, I am now your possession.
Please treat me well from now on, Master.
Why do I have a feeling I just got
caught up in something really messy?
Okay, everyone, say it with me:
Pan-ties... zero... huh?
Oh, a crab!
I'll catch it!
Are you all right?
Sorry.
It's cold.
So that's where it went!
Why would it crawl in there?
That's not normal, is it?
My chest was packed full of sand this afternoon, too.
I found shrimp and small fish in mine, too.
I guess you need to squeeze them
closer together to get rid of any gaps.
What are they talking about?
Things we'll never have to worry about.
I don't understand this at all.
Charlotte, didn't you say you had work
that needed to be finished?
Oh, you're right!
Sorry, I'll be leaving early!
Good grief.
It's been a while since he dove into the sea.
Do you think Touya's okay?
Seeing as he hasn't come up,
I imagine things are going well.
Um, what's in these ruins?
Who knows? Maybe there's nothing.
Was your information on it that vague?
I'm surprised you brought us out here on that.
Well, it sounds interesting, doesn't it?
Sorry for the wait!
Now, let's go.
There!
What is this place?
Are we in the sky?
You've found another incredible place.
What a lovely garden.
Wow.
These look like ruins of the ancient Partheno civilization.
Ancient Partheno civilization?
It was an advanced civilization that created many spells,
and many magical devices, or artifacts, that use those spells.
This garden is one such artifact.
By the way, who is that there?
Your new woman?
Hey, what led you to that?!
Touya.
That's not it!
Your desperation makes you suspicious.
I told you, she's not.
She's Francesca.
She's in charge of this garden.
So she owns this garden?
No, ownership of this Garden of Babylon
has already been transferred to my master, Touya.
What do you mean by "master?"
I mean "beloved husband."
Don't lie.
You mean "proprietor" or "boss."
Proprietor?
What do you mean, Touya?
Huh? Why am I being accused here?
I showed Master Touya my panties
and offered him my body and soul.
Therefore, he is my master.
Hey! You're not giving enough of an explanation!
Panties? What were you two doing before we got here?
Nothing! I did nothing!
You're mistaken!
Touya.
Y-Yes?
On your knees.
Yes!
You looked at ours before, and now you're doing it again?
Do you love panties that much?
No, I saw them by accident that time.
So today you looked at them by choice?
No, no, there was no choice. I couldn't prevent it.
What is it?
Seeing us in swimsuits on the beach wasn't enough for you?
You looked at ours quite a bit, didn't you?
Well, that was, um...
I pushed myself to get a matching bikini
with my sister. Was that not enough?
Are swimsuits and panties not the same?
I see.
Uh...
Given the way this is going,
perhaps I should show you my panties, too?
Sorry. Just be quiet for a moment.
Touya, I'm talking to you right now.
R-Right!
You look like you don't even understand why she's so mad.
Huh?
Oh, just let him off the hook.
If you want to accuse him further,
you'll need to make it clear where you stand with him, too.
At the very least, you'll need to be on equal footing
with that princess there.
Yes.
You all, as well.
W-We don't really...
Y-Yeah.
Everyone, let's leave this to Touya and Leen
while we take a walk through the garden for a bit.
A walk?
Shouldn't we have stayed to hear the story with them?
Don't worry. Just leave that to Leen.
That actually worries me more.
Indeed. Master Touya is too good-natured.
Touya's always nice to everyone, after all.
Well, everyone, shall we chat for a bit?
You all remember what I proposed
on the day we moved into the mansion, right?
I'll get right to the point.
You all love Touya, don't you?
I-I don't exactly love him!
Y-You know, Touya's unreliable and soft-hearted, right?
W-Well, he is kind, and I do think that's
a good thing, but... Wait, no!
But you're always happily gazing
at the clothes he bought you, aren't you?
And Linze, you followed him around
the other day, didn't you?
Th-That was, um... I was just wondering
where he was going.
I thought he might be going to some naughty shops, so I...
You too, Yae.
I-I've done nothing.
Is that so?
When you're injured,
you always have Touya heal you, don't you?
Even though Linze can use healing magic, too.
W-Well, that's...
None of this displeases me.
In fact, I'm delighted by it.
It means Touya has three friends who support and trust him with all their hearts.
You're a weird one, then.
Shouldn't that bother you?
Should it?
I can say with certainty
that Touya will accomplish
something great in the near future.
I think it's unnatural for me to monopolize him.
There are plenty of things I can't support him in alone.
I don't want to tie him down
for such a trifling reason as wanting him to myself.
So, would you all like to become Touya's brides?
Huh?
Y-You can't just ask us
that out of the blue and expect us to...
Uh, um...
Well then, let's shelve this discussion
until your feelings have settled.
Uh, um, well...
I haven't forgotten it, but...
How about it?
Have your feelings settled on the matter?
You've all been more conscious of Touya
since that day, haven't you?
Linze.
Y-Yes!
Your heart is always racing
when you're with Touya, isn't it?
Yes.
Your eyes are always following him too, Elze.
That... may be true... but....
And Yae, you're always nervous around him, aren't you?
H-How did you know?!
Touya's the only one who hasn't noticed.
I would like to support Touya along with all of you.
So I'll make my proposal once more.
Why don't we all become Touya's brides?
B-By "bride," you mean m-marriage, right?
I'm happy. I'm happy, but...
You look great, Linze.
Honestly, it's still too sudden
for me to decide to be his bride.
My heart isn't ready...
I mean, wh-what should I even do?
Oh, gosh!
That would mean me becoming Master Touya's w-w-wife...
and Master Touya my husband. My husband!
You look beautiful.
It looks like you still need a bit more time.
I love you, darling!
So, did you find what you were hoping to obtain, Leen?
Well, I was hoping I might find
a few ancient spells, but this is even better.
Yeah, it is.
A garden that's withstood 5,000 years,
with flowers that have never wilted.
It's an array of ancient magic.
The woman who built this,
Regina Babylon, must have been a genius.
Though she was also a pervert
who made her creation expose her panties...
Cesca, is there anything here, aside from this garden?
No, nothing.
Unlike the others, this is just a lovely garden.
There is no treasure, and nothing I would call a weapon.
Well, this garden is a treasure in itself, really.
I'm grateful that you like it.
I hope you will accept me,
and this Garden of Babylon, as my dowry to you.
I don't need a dowry from you.
Hey, Cesca.
You said that "unlike the others,"
this was just a garden, right?
Yes.
In addition to this location,
there are several areas drifting in the sky,
controlled and managed by my sisters.
Altogether, they complete Babylon.
What?!
In other words, your creator, Professor Regina Babylon,
made the floating island over 5,000 years ago,
and it has now split into pieces
that are drifting above the world below?
That is correct.
This is on such a huge scale that I can't make sense of it.
If things like that were floating in the sky,
it would cause a commotion.
Elze, Linze, Yae, what's wrong?
You're all red.
W-We're fine.
It's nothing.
You're imagining it.
Really?
Babylon is protected by magic barriers
that prevent recognition from outside.
It's nearly impossible to perceive it from the surface.
Just how many of these floating islands are there?
In addition to my garden, there's also the library,
the laboratory, the storage facility,
the tower, the castle walls, the workshop,
the alchemy ward, and the granary.
There were nine originally,
but I don't know how many remain at present.
I'm drawn to this library you speak of, personally.
It sounds like it must be packed
with the ancient civilization's wisdom.
It's the library of the professor who made this.
It might be a mountainous collection of porn.
Collection of porn?
Don't worry about it!
You don't need to know those words! Okay?
A-All right.
Can you make contact with the other floating islands?
My connection with the other sisters
has been severed, so I can't contact them.
So there's no way to find the other facilities
at the moment, then.
Could we find them with Touya's smartphone?
Oh, we could try that.
Nice idea, Linze.
Oh, uh... y-yes.
Search: Babylon.
Guess it won't work...
Has no one else ever found these islands,
in all this time they've been drifting in the sky?
There was contact twice.
Once 3,208 years ago, and again 985 years ago.
The first was at the library, the second at the granary.
So in the end, the only way to find the other Babylons
is to search for each of their teleportation circles.
By the way, do you know
where the other teleportation circles are?
I do not.
Wh-Why did they scatter like this in the first place?
Who knows? The professor never told us.
Maybe it was just to aggravate people.
N-No way.
Elze, your face is red. Are you sure you don't have a cold?
I-It's nothing.
Okay, then.
So, what do we do with her now?
What do we do?
What do you want to do, Cesca?
I would like to stay with you, Master.
From morning to night. Even into the bath and bed.
Into the bath and bed?!
No, I told you, she's just saying that.
Maybe the right answer is to just walk away
and pretend this never happened.
Actually, isn't it a problem if you leave this place?
Won't there be trouble if you're absent
when something happens?
I'll know right away if anything happens.
Plus, I have the power to teleport here.
Management can be left on auto, so that's not a problem.
Oh, really?
Guess I'll have to accept this, then.
For that reason, I would like you
to complete your registration with the garden, Master.
Registration? What do I need to do?
Pardon me for a moment.
Registration complete.
I've recorded your genetic information.
Ownership of the garden
is now transferred to Mochizuki Touya.
Hey! What are you doing?!
How could you suddenly k-k-kiss him?!
I haven't even done that yet!
This is the most effective
means of taking a genetic sample.
I cannot produce children, but I imagine
the other method would still cause various problems.
Ch-Children?!
Oh, boy.
Touya.
Yes!
I love you, Touya.
Huh?
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.