Starting today, I'll be in your service here,
so please take care of me.
Sorry, Laim.
Please take care of Francesca.
Right...
I prepared my clothes myself.
My will to work is second to none.
However, I will be taking my breaks.
I see.
W-Well, it's already late, so let's all get some rest.
Cute, cute.
Cute, cute?
Cute, cute!
Cute, cute, right? Is this how you do it?
I love you, Touya.
Touya, it's Yumina.
May I come in?
C-Come in.
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 12
Decisions, and With My Smartphone
U-Um...
Touya.
Yes?!
I'm angry, you know.
I haven't received a kiss from you yet,
and now those other two have stolen one before me.
That's why?
Obviously!
So... you're not upset over Linze's confession?
It's plain as day that Linze loves you, Touya!
Sorry, it wasn't plain to me.
I won't complain even if you take ten or twenty wives.
I'd consider it proof of your masculinity.
However! How-e-ver!
You've been too careless, letting others kiss you
when you haven't even kissed your actual wife yet!
You're too unguarded!
You need to improve your defenses!
Thoroughly!
W-Wait, but...
No excuses!
Right.
If you'll hug and kiss me, I'll forgive you.
Whoa... That's raising
the difficulty level way too high, Yumina!
So I'm the first one you've kissed yourself, aren't I?
Huh? Oh...
Yeah, I guess you are.
What do you think about Linze?
Me? I think she's cute.
Honestly, I was happy when she confessed.
But I haven't made up my mind yet about you,
so adding Linze to that...
Do you like or dislike her?
Of course I like her. I cherish her.
You heard him, Linze.
Huh?
Huh?! How?!
What's going on?!
I asked Leen to cast the invisibility spell on her.
When did you come in here?
Oh... When Yumina came in!
It's your fault, Touya.
You shut yourself up in your room
without giving her an answer.
Well...
Linze was crying the whole time, thinking you hated her.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry, too.
I'm sorry for not considering your feelings.
N-No, um, like I said earlier,
it's not as if I hate you.
I think you're cute.
I think I like you, too.
Touya...
Now that you've both confirmed your feelings
for each other, how about it?
Would you take Linze as your wife, too?
Huh?!
It's common for kings, nobles,
and great merchants to have two or three wives.
You don't have a problem with it, right, Linze?
I would like to be Touya's wife, as well.
Th-This is so sudden...
Can I?
All right. If both of you are okay with that.
Thank you.
Now Linze is a fiancée like me.
Yeah. Well, it's already late,
so both of you should get back to your rooms.
Then give me a goodnight kiss.
Huh?
M-Me, too.
I-Is on the forehead okay?
I'll settle for that.
Well, goodnight.
Goodnight.
Yeah, goodnight.
What am I supposed to do now?
I need to talk to you for a moment.
Sure?
Rumble...
But the door... Never mind. Forget about it.
Yae? What are you doing here?
I was waiting for you, Master Touya.
I heard you'll be taking Linze as your wife?
Th-That's how things turned out.
How do you feel about Linze?
Do you really love her?
I don't know if I'd go as far as "love" yet,
but it's true that I cherish her.
And she accepted that?
Yeah.
That girl's always been timid,
but then she's bold when it counts.
The complete opposite of me.
I'm somewhat the same, too.
Without some kind of trigger, I can't make up my mind.
Um...
Touya, I want you to fight us now.
Huh?
If you win, we won't say anything else.
But if we win, you'll listen to one request from us.
I've removed the edge from this sword,
but it can still break bones, so be careful.
Huh? Be careful? But...
Touya, make sure to remove your edge with Modeling, too.
Also, no using offensive magic.
In exchange, I won't use Boost, either.
Wait, before that... Why do I have to fight you two?
Well, the two of us need something tangible like this.
You'll regret it for life if you don't take us seriously.
What on earth is going on?
What'll it be, Touya?
Modeling.
Rubber bullets are fine, right?
Yes.
You're prepared, then?
Yeah.
Blade Mode!
Too easy!
Gun Mode!
Reload.
I win.
You won't shoot?
If you'll admit defeat, I'd rather end it here.
You're too soft.
Can you protect Linze and the others like that?
That's who I am. What can I say?
True.
That's why Yae and I fell in love with you, too.
Huh?
Wha...
Back then?
P-Put us in the same position as Yumina and Linze!
Huh?
What we're saying is, um, w-we also...
You should be the one to say this, Mistress Elze!
No, I...
A-Anyway, first of all...
I-I love you too, Touya!
Same here, as well.
The same position as Yumina and Linze?
You mean...
We also, um,
want to be your wives, Master Touya... please.
No, do it!
You lost to us, after all!
You did this just to tell me that?
I figured it wouldn't work if we didn't do this.
Yumina?!
Wait, did you advise them to do this?
Yes.
I proposed long ago that we should
all become your wives, Touya.
W-Wow, she's scary.
S-So what about you?
Huh?
I-I said, "What do you think about us?"
O-Of course I like you both.
But...
I'm sorry, but could you all give me a bit more time?
I want to sort out my thoughts on all this.
That makes sense.
We have forced all this upon you rather suddenly.
Thanks.
So this is where you were.
Cesca...
I have a general grasp of the situation.
What is there that you need to debate?
I don't know if I can make everyone happy.
Maybe they'll all end up feeling dissatisfied.
Are you talking about S&M play?
What led you to that?!
I'm just questioning
whether I can fulfill my duties as a husband.
Oh, speaking of duties,
there's something I forgot to tell you yesterday.
Something you forgot to tell me?
There's a message for you, Master.
From who?
Professor Regina Babylon.
The professor?
The professor who built this place?
Huh? What?
What are you doing?
I don't know.
The professor said my new master would
understand once I handed this over.
What?
This person is...
Yes. That's Professor Regina Babylon.
Hey, hey. I'm Regina Babylon.
Nice to meet you, Mochizuki Touya.
How do you know my name? And...
I know.
That's a good question to ask.
It's only natural you'd want to know about things.
Well, let's answer your question, then.
Take a good, long look.
This is my favorite pair.
Like I care!
I'm joking, I'm joking.
Just a bit of fun.
Don't let it get to you.
Jeez! I've got bigger issues than that right now!
What's this?
Staring at my aroma pipe?
Perhaps this color is reminding you of my panties
and making you lust—
Hey, wait, wait.
I'll answer your question, so just let it slide.
Next panty joke you tell, I'm pulling the cord for real.
Now, you want to know how I know about you?
That's because I have a tool
that lets me see into the future.
The future?
I can't choose which era, though.
But thanks to that, I can hold
this mock conversation with you.
All of your reactions and words reach me.
I've been watching the adventures of you
and your friends out of curiosity.
So you've seen everything?
There was a time I couldn't see, though.
The future was unstable.
Unstable?
Yeah, the Fraze's sudden,
indeed very sudden appearance was the cause.
The Fraze?
I couldn't predict their appearance.
I did everything I could,
but in the end, the Partheno civilization collapsed.
Then the flow of time from your era
to the future was altered by the Fraze's appearance?
Yes.
At this rate, the world will be destroyed,
so I can't see the future.
That's what I thought, anyway.
It wasn't destroyed?
One day, the Fraze just disappeared from this world.
I don't know why.
And thanks to that, you can see the future again.
I'm glad I haven't lost my entertainment.
Your current situation
with your ladies is especially fun to watch.
Please stop peeping on us.
What's the harm?
I'm entrusting you with my Babylon in exchange.
Consider it my thanks, and use it as you will.
Huh? You can't just...
Then may I ask one more question?
You just said you're enjoying
watching my current situation,
but are you enjoying it knowing
what will come to us in the future?
You want to know what's going to happen with those four?
It wouldn't be any fun if I told you.
That's more important than any ruins.
Besides, you're not the type to agonize
over the future, are you?
So that ends our discussion.
By the way, once this message finishes,
Francesca will become completely nude.
I'm joking. See you later.
Shall I strip?
You don't have to strip!
That's more than I can handle.
You seem to be having a lot of fun lately, Lady Sushie.
Oh, it's you.
That's because Touya visited!
You should let me know if you're planning to visit.
Is that so?
It's been a while, God.
Things are exciting and thrilling when he's around!
I can't believe I actually made it here.
I want to play around and poke at Touya now!
There's plenty of magic power here, after all.
Want to poke him, too? Poke, poke!
So what do you need?
I get it.
So in the end, I can't really make a decision,
and I'm wondering if this is really right.
I see no reason to give it that much thought.
I think you should just genuinely enjoy it.
Someone else told me the same thing,
but I still keep mulling it over.
In that case, you should ask an expert.
Huh?
Hey, it's me, it's me.
Yeah, sorry, but could you stop by for a bit?
Okay, I'll be waiting.
Sorry for keeping you!
That was awfully fast.
I can hear my heart pounding... ready to burst...
Uh, and this is?
The God of Love.
Perfect for you to get advice from, right?
Nice to you meet you.
I've been curious about you for a while,
so I've looked in on occasion.
I've had a lot of people watching me...
So, you're really a god of love, then?
I am. But I don't manipulate people's feelings.
I just help liven the mood or provide clichés.
Clichés?
That's right.
Like, when people say, "I'll marry her once this
battle's over," I make them unable to get married.
That's your fault?!
So what's the matter?
Oh, well...
That's quite the interesting situation.
But I don't understand the problem.
If you all love each other, what's the issue?
But four at once?
Abandon what you knew as common sense in your old world.
If you love all four and want to
make them happy, then that's true love.
But I don't know if I'll be able to
make all four of them happy.
It's important to cherish your partners,
but you can't lie to yourself, either.
You mean it's okay to be selfish?
Of course. It wouldn't be love if only one side were happy.
Do you have your answer?
I don't know.
But I think I can see it.
That's good to hear.
I'm glad my cliché hasn't gone to waste, either.
What do you mean?
A while back, I set up the "happened to catch them changing in the bath and got surprised" scene.
Be grateful.
Th-That was your doing?!
I'm anxious, light-headed.
Hold on a moment, I'm warming—
Kohaku.
What's the matter?
Sorry, could you call the four of them here?
Uh, first of all, I won't be marrying.
What?!
Hey, what do you mean?!
Touya?!
H-Have we done something wrong?
You said you'd make me your wife.
H-Hold on!
I'm talking about right now.
I'm not getting married for now.
For now?
Then you mean you will eventually marry us?
Of course. So long as none of you are against it,
I'll wed all four of you.
I promise to keep that promise.
But I won't do it right now.
I don't think it's right to just go along
with things and marry everyone.
What do you mean?
I'm not mature enough to bear responsibility
for another's life yet, and I have no plan for the future.
So I'd like you to wait a bit longer.
That's quite selfish of you.
Of course, if you lose interest in me during that time,
you're welcome to cast me aside.
You're saying that knowing we can't, aren't you?
I see why they say whoever falls in love first loses.
Even if my sister casts you aside, I'll keep waiting for you.
Hey, I never said I was going to cast him aside!
I'm all right with that, as well.
Now that we've all confirmed our feelings,
all that's left is to let them grow.
Thanks.
So now that we're all Touya's fiancées,
why don't we have our husband kiss us each in turn?
Huh?!
I-I-Isn't it a bit too soon for that?
L-Like, even if we're engaged,
we should have modest relations.
But he kissed me yesterday.
H-He kissed me, too.
O-On the forehead, though.
Well, um...
Th-Then you need to d-do it with us, too!
I-I'd like you to.
A-All right.
This is just too embarrassing!
Touya?
Again, Big Sis?
I wanted him to kiss me, too!
I never get tired of watching him.
According to the professor, he'll end up with nine wives.
My, that many?
Wait, why are you enjoying this, too?
Huh?
Please, Master Leen! Let me in on the fun, too!
Leen, could it be you're one of them, as well?
Who knows? Perhaps.
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.
I see.
Sounds like a decision you'd make.
I need to hone myself as a man from here on out.
Well, you're kind, caring, and a little easily persuaded.
Young man, you can't use that currency here.
Huh? But this is all I have!
Is there someone in trouble?
Sorry, God. I'm heading out for a bit.
Excuse me. I'll pay for that.
Thank you.
Thanks! You saved me!
Well, we all ought to help each other when in need.
That's an interestingly shaped coin.
Is it?
The device in your pocket looks more interesting.
Huh?
I'm Mochizuki Touya. And you are?
Ende. Nice to meet you, Touya.