I'm very sorry about this, but you're dead.
God
I made a bit of a blunder and dropped some lightning on the world below.
I'm truly sorry about that.
I didn't think there'd be anyone where it fell.
I see.
Uh, M-Mochizuki?
Touya. Mochizuki Touya.
Yes, yes. Mochizuki Touya.
Still, you're quite calm about this.
I thought you might panic a little
when you heard you were dead.
Maybe because it doesn't feel real to me yet?
It feels like this is all a dream.
Plus, there's no use complaining about what's already done.
You're very prudent about this.
I certainly never thought I'd die at 15, though.
So, what's going to happen to me now?
You'll be resurrected at once.
Really?
Just, well...
We can't bring you back to life in the world you came from.
Those are the rules.
So I'd like to bring you back in a different world.
Hmm...
All right, then.
Huh? You're sure?
I understand your situation,
and I'm grateful for being able to live again at all.
My granddad always told me to be
a person who can forgive others' mistakes.
You're a good young man.
Oh, right. Anything you'd like me to do to make up for it?
Anything?
Yes, please tell me what you'd like.
What I'd like, huh?
Well...
Could you make it so I'm able to use this in the other world?
That?
Oh, I suppose you couldn't, could you?
I doubt I could charge it there.
No, no. That'll be fine.
You'll be able to charge the battery with magic.
Magic? There's a power like that in the other world?
Of course. It's a magical world.
You'll quickly be able to use magic yourself, as well.
Still, are you sure that's all you want?
Yes, thank you.
By the way, about the smartphone...
If I'm able to use it, would calling my original world be...
Ah, sorry, but you won't be able to interact directly.
Watching or reading things
from it won't be a problem, though.
Also, I'll make it so you can call me, too.
Understood.
Let's go with that, then.
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 1
Awakening, and Another World
So this is another world?
I guess I'll run into someone if I follow this road.
Incoming Call
God
End
Answer
Incoming Call
God
End
Answer
Hello?
Oh, I got through. I got through.
Looks like you've arrived safely.
Yes, somehow.
I forgot to mention something about your smartphone.
I altered the map and navigation to match
the world you're in now, so try using it.
Really?
That's a big help.
I was just wondering what direction to head in.
If you check the map as you make your way,
you should reach a city without issue.
Well, do your best down there.
He's registered as "God..."
Call Ended
God
West...
But I don't have any food or water.
Even if I reach a town...
It's not like I can use money from my world.
You there!
Wh-What is it?
Oh, we can understand each other.
Wh-Where did you obtain these unusual clothes?!
Would you please sell them to me?!
I'll pay plenty for them!
Huh?
Come on, climb down.
Let's get your clothes here.
Oh, yes.
I can't read the writing...
Welcome back, Owner.
Hey, someone find some clothes that fit him!
That man owns this store?
Y-You!
Wha... Huh?
C-Could you sell me those clothes, too?!
Is this highway robbery?
If you find any new clothes, please bring them to me!
Sure.
By the way, is there an inn
or something similar in this town?
I want to secure a place to sleep
before the sun went down today.
Ah, if you're looking for an inn, just head down
to the main street, turn right and follow it straight.
There's a sign for "The Silver Moon." You can't miss it.
Thank you very much.
The Silver Moon Inn?
So that sign read, "Fashion King Zanac," huh?
That's not what you promised!
You were supposed to pay one gold coin in return!
Look, see this scratch right here?
That's why you get a silver coin.
Here.
Only one coin?!
A small scratch like that doesn't mean it's damaged!
Big Sis...
Forget it. I don't need your money.
Just give that antler back.
Hey, that's not going to happen.
This is ours now.
Sorry to interrupt, but do you have a moment?
Who are you?!
What do you want?
Oh, sorry, my business is with those ladies.
Huh? Us?
Would you sell that antler to me for one gold coin?
Sold!
Then...
Wha...
What the hell did you do?!
That was mine already.
Bastard!
I'll go ahead an give all your basic abilities
and so forth a boost.
Now you shouldn't die unless something crazy happens.
Incredible.
It's like everything is in slow motion.
Here's your gold coin.
Are you sure?
It's a big help to us, but...
I'm definitely the one who shattered it.
I don't mind, so take it.
I broke it to catch them off guard,
but if I had known they'd be that easy to beat, I wouldn't have had to.
Well, in that case...
Thank you for saving us.
I'm Elze Silhoueska, and this
is my younger twin sister, Linze Silhoueska.
Thank you very much.
I'm Mochizuki Touya.
Mochizuki? That's a rare name.
Oh, my name's Touya. Mochizuki is my family name.
Oh, your family and given name are backwards.
Are you from Eashen?
Eashen? Uh, well...
Why did you come to this town?
Uh, for starters, I'm looking for the Silver Moon Inn.
Then I was going to think about it from there.
The Silver Moon?
That's the inn we're staying at.
Huh?
Here it is.
For now, I'd like to stay for a month.
Sure thing.
Finished checking in?
Yeah. Sorry to keep you waiting.
My, you three knew each other?
He helped us out just a moment ago.
What? You've found a man already?
Th-That's not it!
So that's why we were out in town delivering
the Crystal Deer Antler to those men who requested it earlier.
But that went terribly.
I was against it and said we shouldn't.
But Sis, you never listen to me.
I guess we should only accept requests
from proper places like the guild.
Should we take this opportunity to register?
I think that's best.
Safety first.
Let's head out tomorrow.
Guild?
Is that something like a temp agency?
Um, if you wouldn't mind, could I come with you?
I was thinking I should look for work, too.
Of course you can. Let's go together.
We'll show you the way as thanks for saving us, right?
Yes.
That's a big help.
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
That band's breaking up?
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
Budokan Live is a success!
Click to View Photo
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
When they came back on stage after the call
for an encore, their eyes were filled with tears.
The vocalist, Shinobu, announced their
indefinite hiatus...
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
They brought joy to
their fans, playing their
greatest hit at their
Budokan concert.
So many things happened in just one day.
I can't read it at all.
I'll need to do something about my literacy first.
Hey, how's this one, Linze?
The reward's pretty good,
so it makes a good starter, right?
Yeah, it's not bad.
Any good ones on your side?
Huh?
Actually... I can't tell what's written here at all.
Huh? You mean you can't read?
Uh, it's a mission to defeat beast monsters
in the forest to the east.
Five One-Horned Wolves...
The reward's 18 copper coins.
If you'd like, we could form a party.
You seem strong, so it'd be nice to have you.
Please!
Okay.
Then let's go apply at the counter.
Oh.
What's the matter?
I don't have any weapons.
Huh?
Thanks again!
All right, now we're all set.
Yes.
As usual, you'll be our rear guard,
Linze, and I'll be our vanguard.
Touya, you'll be in the vanguard with me, right?
Oh, sure.
That's an Eashen sword, isn't it?
Yeah.
Don't lose that or your Guild Card.
Getting one reissued is a real pain.
Got it.
Come forth, Fire!
Hail of Red Stones: Ignis Fire!
Incredible! Was that magic?
Touya, not bad.
The job was only to defeat five,
but we managed to take down one extra.
Yes, I can confirm we've received
five One-Horned Wolf horns.
Oh? What about that horn?
I thought I'd save it as a memento of our first mission.
I see.
Well, please present your Guild Cards.
Now then, here's your reward, 18 copper coins.
That completes your mission.
Thanks for your work.
I'm glad we partnered up with you.
We would've had a harder time if it was just us.
I think we might make a good party.
There aren't that many men who can keep up
with my sister so easily, you know?
No, I was actually pretty nervous.
I never realized they were such ferocious beasts.
So, um...
I have a favor to ask you two.
Favor?
Yeah.
I'd like you to teach me how to read and write.
Not being able to read is rather inconvenient.
Especially when you can't read what your mission's about.
If that's the case, then you should have Linze teach you.
She's smart, so she's good at teaching others.
Th-That's not... true...
But if you don't mind me, then...
Thanks. It's a big help.
A-Also, while I'm at it, I guess...
Could you teach me magic, too?
I want to try using it myself.
Huh?
You want us to teach you magic?
Do you have any aptitudes?
Aptitudes?
Magic is strongly influenced
by the aptitudes you're born with.
Those without any aptitudes can never use magic,
no matter how hard they try.
Aptitudes, huh?
I don't really get it, but I think I'll be all right.
A certain individual gave me his seal of approval
and said I'd be able to use magic soon.
Who was that?
Uh, someone very important.
Is there any way to figure out what my aptitudes are?
These are spell stones.
They amplify, store, and release magical energy.
If you use these...
Maybe Water would be easiest to understand.
Come forth, Water.
Oh!
This is active magic.
This spell stone responded
to my magical energy and created water.
By the way...
Come forth, Water.
If you don't have an aptitude for Water,
it turns out like this.
This means I can't use Water magic.
So you can't use it, even though you're twins?
I'm not proud of it, so don't be so direct about it.
Although Elze can't use Water magic,
she can use Fortification magic.
By the same token, I can't use that one.
I'd need an aptitude for Fortification.
Everyone possesses magical energies,
but without an aptitude, you can't use any spells.
Then if I try that myself,
we'll know if I have an aptitude or not?
Yes.
Hold the spell stone in your hand, focus your mind,
and chant, "Come forth, Water."
Come forth, Water.
Are there other spell stones, too?
Th-There are, but...
Let's go somewhere else first.
Come forth, Fire.
Come forth, Earth.
Come forth, Wind.
Come forth, Light.
Come forth, Dark.
Huh? What's the matter?
Who on earth are you?
This is the first time I've seen
anyone capable of using six Elements.
I can use three myself,
but that's still rare.
Yet you can use six...
That's incredible.
Huh?
What's that spell stone?
That's a spell stone for Null magic.
Null magic is special in that it doesn't have any set chants.
Huh? Then how do you use it?
Well, for example, there's my sister's Fortification,
which activates just by chanting "Boost."
There's also "Power Rise," which increases strength.
A rare one would be "Gate,"
which allows you to travel long distances.
Wow, magic that lets you travel
long distances sounds really convenient.
Boost is more helpful.
All the men who underestimated me
because I'm a woman have paid for it, thanks to that.
Fortification magic, huh?
No wonder you're so strong.
Yeah.
But how can you tell what kind of
Null magic you'll be able to use?
At some point, you just know the name of the spell somehow.
Yes, that's right.
Null magic is also called personal magic,
and it's rare for two people to be able to use the same spell.
Then I won't know right away
if I have an aptitude for Null magic?
No, you'll know if you pick up the spell stone
and try using some Null magic.
Even if the spell doesn't activate, the spell stone should
show some kind of change, like glowing or shuddering a bit.
You were interested in the Gate spell.
Why not try casting it?
Sure, I'll try it.
Gate.
No way.
It worked?
It did.
This is...
The eastern forest we were just in.
The Gate spell allows the caster
to travel to places they've been before.
You must have thought of this place
when you used the spell.
Still, I can't believe you can use all Elements.
There's something strange about you.
I've never heard of anyone being able to use all Elements.
You're incredible, Touya.
Hmm, but this is probably thanks to God, right?
I feel like I'm being praised for cheating.
Hey, sorry to interrupt your fun, but do you have a moment?
Micah? What is it?
This here is Aer.
She works at Café Parent, but...
Actually, I'm trying to think of
something new to add to our menu.
Since you're travelers,
we thought you might have some ideas.
Food? Hmm, what would be good?
Nothing's coming to mind.
How about you, Touya?
Maybe some native Eashen dishes?
If you know anything good, please tell me.
By the way, what kind of food are you hoping for?
Something light to eat, I suppose?
Like a dessert.
It would be even better if it's popular with women.
Something women would enjoy?
All I can think of are crêpes or ice, though.
Ice? Frozen water?
No, not that. I meant ice cream.
Ice cream?
Do they not know about ice cream?
Um, what's that?
Oh, a useful magic item, I suppose.
I'm the only one who can use it, though.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't pry about it too much.
Um, could you get a sheet of paper
and write down what I'm about to read?
Sure.
Sweets, sweets!
Three eggs.
200 milliliters of heavy cream.
About 60-80 grams of sugar.
Looks like ingredient names are the same.
Oh, right. Linze, can you use Ice magic?
Yes, I can.
It's Water magic, after all!
Great!
What now? This sounds fun!
It's delicious!
What is this?! It's cold and delicious!
So good!
I've never had anything like this before.
I think this'll be popular with women.
What do you think about adding it to your menu?
Thank you very much!
We'll be using this ice cream!
I'll try making it one more time!
I should learn it, too.
Seriously, what are you?
Not to mention that strange device!
I'm really curious, too.
It's a secret.
But thanks to it, I managed to repay you two.
Repay us?
For teaching me magic.
Or something like that.
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.