The four of them alone defeated a dragon,
and now they're casting healing magic on every resident...
I'm shocked beyond surprise.
On top of that, they're donating all
the dragon's usable parts,
which could go for over 10 gold apiece,
to the village's recovery.
They're very benevolent. I bow my head to them.
Just who are these people?
Who knows? I certainly don't.
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 7
Nation of Beastmen, and an Observer
I'm the village elder, Solum.
For defeating the dragon that attacked our village,
and making such a generous contribution
to the village's restoration,
we are extremely grateful.
No, it was only the right thing to do.
What's this?
One of the fangs harvested from that dragon.
Please, take it for yourself.
Huh? But...
I hear you damaged your weapon.
You could use this fang as material to create
a new weapon, or sell it to buy a brand new one.
In that case, I'll gratefully accept.
It's surprisingly light.
Also, I'd like to return this.
Huh?
It was stuck in the dragon's eye.
I believe it belongs to you?
This was that...
Kohaku, was anyone there that night, aside from us?
Yes.
I believe I sensed someone within the grove of trees.
Likely two.
I thought they were villagers at the time.
So this is the Royal Capital of Mismede, Berge.
Your Royal Highness, I, Olga Strand,
have returned from the Kingdom of Belfast.
Yes, good work.
Garen and knights of Belfast, I am pleased
that you protected Olga and delivered her safely.
Yes, sir!
You are the envoys sent by the King of Belfast, yes?
I hear you defeated a dragon
that attacked Eld Village on your travels.
Is this true?
Yes, that is correct.
These four dispatched the black dragon
that attacked the village.
And you?
My apologies for the delay.
I am the daughter of Tristwyn Urnes Belfast,
King of Belfast Kingdom,
Yumina Urnea Belfast.
Heavens! What brings the princess of Belfast to my kingdom?
An alliance with Mismede is that important to us.
Here is a letter penned by my father.
Please read it for yourself.
I see.
I'll think on the matter
and give a response in the near future.
Until then, please enjoy yourselves in my palace.
A brave warrior who defeated a dragon, eh?
It's been ages since my blood roiled so.
How about it, young Touya?
Care to spar with me?
Huh?
I've never seen arms like that.
Mister Touya,
when His Majesty, King of Beastmen,
sees someone strong, he cannot resist facing them.
Frankly, we're troubled by it, too.
Okay...
Go ahead and give him a good thrashing!
Give him all you've got!
No, no, no, no! He's your king, guys!
The match will continue until one is put
in a position to receive a fatal wound,
or your opponent admits defeat.
Use of magic is allowed.
However, use of offensive magic
that directly targets your opponent is prohibited.
Are both opponents ready?
Don't hold back!
Think of this as a real battle,
and use all means available to you to try and defeat me!
Sure...
Now, begin!
Slip!
There, that's the match.
H-H-Hold on!
What was that?!
One of my Null Magic spells, Slip.
He said it was all right to use anything
but offensive magic.
No, no, no!
That doesn't even allow a match to happen!
One more time! Without that spell this time!
That spell's off limits!
Got it.
Begin!
King Jamukha has the advantage in hand-to-hand.
But with magic allowed...
Obstructing Dust Storm: Blind Sand!
Too slow!
Multiple!
So that spell was a bluff.
Yes.
Well done, Master Touya.
Boost!
Accel!
Oh? You managed to dodge that?
Well done, Touya.
So fast!
What was that?
Null Magic?
Was that a Null Magic spell?
Yes. It's my Null Magic, Accel.
What kind of spell is it?
Oh, it's a spell to increase one's agility.
It guzzles my mana, though,
so I can't keep it active constantly.
I see.
That's a nice spell you have there.
Right?
You have my gratitude, because I'm going to use it!
Accel!
Did you just...
It's surprisingly hard to control, isn't it?
But I won't miss next time.
Accel!
What on earth is going on?
I can't see them.
You're not too bad!
But I have more strength!
That's true.
So I'll challenge you with speed.
Accel, Boost!
Accel!
Checkmate.
I don't understand the meaning of that word,
but it seems I've lost.
Winner: Mister Mochizuki Touya!
To think he'd cast Null Magic spells on top of each other.
I can't believe you can use Accel, too!
Looks like I got a bit full of myself.
I'll have to take a lesson from this.
I guess...
This, and this...
Mister Touya, you look good in that outfit.
Thanks.
By the way, um, do you know where Mistress Olga is?
I haven't seen her...
This is looking good.
Mister Touya, that looks good on you.
I wouldn't be surprised
if people thought you a Mismede noble.
You think so?
You do look good, Touya. It's lovely.
Yeah. I'd say it's perfect.
It brings out a different charm in you.
You look sharp in it, Master Touya.
You all look good, too.
Oh, mind if I take a picture?
What was that?
Sorry, this is one my Null Magic spells, too.
It allows me to record an image of a scene and save it.
Oh! A spell that can paint a picture in an instant?
Can you take it out, too?
I can, so long as I have paper
or something to transfer it to.
Drawing.
This is amazing!
Touya, could you paint me, as well?
Sure.
Cute, cute, cute, buff.
Whew, I'm beat.
Huh?
Me?
What's this?
You've brought a strange guest with you, Paula.
So, who might you be?
Oh, I'm Touya.
Mochizuki Touya.
Touya's my given name.
I see. The rumored dragon slayer, then?
Dragon slayer?
Well, it's true...
And you?
My, forgive me.
I'm Leen, an elder of the fairy folk.
This little one is Paula.
Despite my appearance, I'm far older than you are.
Older? By how much?
How much would it be?
I'm certain I'm past 600, at least...
600?!
It's a hassle to think about, so let's say I'm 612.
B-By the way, this Paula...
Is she a summoned beast?
She isn't. She's a bona fide teddy bear.
She's moving because my Null Magic, Program, is in effect.
Program?
The Null Magic "Program" allows you to input some commands into an inanimate object, and make it operate.
Program: start.
Condition: someone sits down.
Activation Sequence: move.
Program: end.
I forgot to set a distance.
Well, you can use the spell as such to apply commands.
So if you programmed Paula
with a command to fly, could she fly?
It's not powerful enough to allow that much freedom.
Program can only implement simple motions.
But if you wanted to move a model bird's wings
to make it fly, you could.
Let me try it out a bit.
Huh?
Program: start.
Condition: someone sits down.
Activation Sequence: move backward two meters.
Program: end.
What did you just do?
What? Use Program?
Your talent for magic is splendid.
What elements, other than Null Magic, can you use?
I can use all the elements.
I'm not even surprised anymore.
I've decided.
You will be my apprentice.
Huh?
I'm joking.
Forcing those who aren't interested isn't my style.
But if you change your mind...
Sorry!
Time to run!
I won't let you go.
Master, you seem exhausted.
So much has happened today.
Oh, right!
If I use that Program spell...
Oh, are you heading out?
You two, as well?
We just finished breakfast, so we
were thinking of taking a stroll in the garden together.
I'm glad you're getting along.
Where are Elze and Yae?
At the arena, undergoing joint training
with Mismede's soldiers.
Oh, I see.
By the way, what are you up to?
Just shopping for a few things.
My shopping...
Isn't this great?
Come forth, Water!
Feel My Blade, Both Cold and Clear: Aqua Cutter!
Is that good enough?
Yeah, thanks.
What are you making?
I figured I'd create a new weapon.
A new weapon?
Modeling.
Yeah, looking good.
Next come the bullets.
Modeling.
Enchant: Aports.
Program: start.
Condition: user speaks "Reload."
Activation Sequence:
expel empty cartridges at high speed,
use Aports to draw bullets
from within a one-meter radius,
and place them in the empty cylinder.
Program: end.
I missed?
Oh, there's no rifling.
Modeling.
Reload.
Is it complete?
Yeah, I suppose.
This is called a gun.
It's a weapon with a long-range attack.
Touya, would it possible to get one for myself, too?
I'd like one, too.
Huh?
Then, for now,
pick a design you like from here.
Program: start.
Condition: user speaks "Blade Mode" or "Gun Mode."
Activation Sequence:
use Modeling to transform the edge from a dagger
to a longsword, or a longsword to a dagger, at high speed.
Program: end.
Blade Mode!
Gun Mode!
Incredible!
It can be a gun or a sword!
After the fight with the King of Beastmen, I was thinking
of ways to handle situations where I can't use magic.
So what name will you give this weapon?
Well...
I think I'll go with Brunhild.
That took longer than I thought.
I'm a bit hungry.
Shall we go grab a bite to eat?
We should. I'd love to eat
the traditional food of this nation.
I believe they're famous for a dish called "currae."
I think you can eat it at that restaurant.
Sounds good.
Master, someone's watching us.
Okay, let's go say hello. Can you tell where they are?
If you look to your right,
they're on top of the highest building.
You two on go on ahead. I'll join you soon.
Huh?
Where are you going?
Just some quick business.
Kohaku, protect both of them.
Take care.
Accel!
Hey.
Uh, can you understand me?
Who are you two?
Accel, Boost!
Relax. Those are rubber bullets, so you're not hurt.
So, who are you two?
Why were you observing us?
I'll search you to make sure you're not hiding any weapons.
Huh? This sensation...
Lapis?
We're with Espion.
We're spies working directly
for His Majesty, the King of Belfast.
For the king?
Yes.
Right now, we've been ordered
to safeguard the Royal Princess.
So you've been protecting Yumina from the shadows, then?
Exactly.
Oh, then is this knife...
That's Cecile's.
She's a master of throwing knives.
I'm not that good.
Wait, you've been with us this whole time? Since Belfast?
That's our mission.
So my butler Laim is in on this, too?
He is.
So? Where do we go from here?
We'll continue protecting Lady Yumina
from the shadows, as we have,
so please keep our identities secret from the princess.
So it would be bad if she found out?
Yes.
If she found out, she'd get really mad at the king.
It would be a serious national affair!
That bad?
Sorry for the wait.
We ordered the pork cutlet currae for you, Touya.
This is...
Apparently the sauce poured over the food is called currae.
This is totally curry.
What an incredible taste.
I think my tongue's on fire.
What's the matter?
No, it's nothing.
It's spicy!
Gate.
Welcome to Mismede, King Belfast.
I'm grateful for the invitation, King Mismede.
That boy you brought...
Mochizuki Touya, was it?
My apprentice, Charlotte, is in Belfast, too...
I should pay a visit soon.
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.