After dying due to God's mistake,
I started living a new life in another world,
a world of fantasy where magic and magical beasts exist.
But everything's all right.
Because I have the abilities God gave me,
and this smartphone.
Let's find an inn in this city tonight.
Yeah, we have a long way to go before the royal capital.
Were you two really okay with the request
to deliver a letter to the royal capital?
Wouldn't the listing beside it
to defeat the megaslime be better?
No!
Why not?
I hate squishy and springy creatures like slimes!
It's an inherent dislike!
Besides, those things melt your clothes and stuff.
Absolutely no way!
That's kind of a shame, maybe...
Let's grab a meal before going to the inn.
I hope there's a place like the Silver Moon...
In that case, wouldn't it be easier to use Gate to return to the Silver Moon, and start from here again tomorrow?
No way!
Huh?!
It's better to stay in unfamiliar places and visit
unfamiliar stores when you're in an unfamiliar town.
You just don't get it.
Hey, hold it, you!
What's going on?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 2
First Journey, and Samurai
That girl's wearing an odd outfit.
She's a samurai.
Samurai?
Lady, I hear you took real good care of my buddies.
Oh, you are with the men I turned in to the guards, yes?
The fault for that lies with you.
It is what you get for running amok.
Shut up!
Get her!
I've never seen techniques like that.
That's...
Jiu-jitsu?
Hunger causes my strength to wane...
She just suddenly stopped moving!
Look out! Behind you!
Come forth, Sand!
Obstructing Dust Storm: Blind Sand!
My eyes!
Now!
Touya!
Ah, jeez...
You just had to stick your nose into trouble!
It's the guards!
Touya, let's get out of here.
All right.
You hurry, too.
I think we've run far enough now.
I am grateful for your assistance.
I am called Kokonoe Yae.
Oh, Yae is my given name. Kokonoe is my family name.
Are you from Eashen, then?
Indeed.
I come from Oedo in Eashen.
Oedo...
So even that part's similar.
I'm Mochizuki Touya.
Touya's my given name. Mochizuki's my family name.
Oh! Master Touya, are you from Eashen, as well?
Oh, no. I'm from a different country that's very similar.
Huh?
Oh, right. They think I'm from Eashen.
More importantly, you looked a bit unsteady back there.
Well, embarrassing though it is,
I lost my travel funds on the way here, so...
I shall gladly partake!
Wow, so you're traveling to improve your martial arts, Yae?
Indeed.
My family has produced generations of warriors.
I chose to travel in order to hone my skills.
I see.
Someday, I shall become a swordsman on par
with my father and older brother!
What an incredible appetite.
So, Yae, what are you doing after this?
For now,
I'm planning to head
to the royal capital to test my strength.
What a coincidence. We're heading
to the royal capital for work, as well.
Hey, would you like to come with us?
Do you truly...
mean that?
After you've shown me such hospitality...
Since it's come to this, please allow me
t' serve 'ou t' the besht o' m' abilithees.
You don't mind, right, Touya?
Huh? Oh, no. I don't...
It's settled, then.
Nice, indeed.
Will our food expenses be all right?
So you can handle horses too, Yae?
I have trained in the equestrian arts, yes.
That means the three of us can trade off.
Frankly, it was a bit hard with just me and Linze.
I-I'm ashamed.
Heavens, no.
Touya, you're a talented mage, aren't you?
He can use my own Boost, not just Elemental magic.
Apparently Touya can activate most Null Magic
as long as he knows the spell name
and details about its effects.
Good grief... When he's that all-powerful,
it's more exasperating than surprising.
But there are many different types of Null Magic, right?
Yes.
It's mostly personal magic,
so it's said there are as many types as there are users.
So there's a preposterous number of them, huh?
But unlike Elemental magic,
only certain individuals can use them,
so few know exactly what kinds of Null Magic exist.
The magic tomes circulating now
are all just hobbyists' collections.
Well, there aren't many who'd go out of their way
to study magic they can't use themselves.
A spell that curls hair into rolls.
Whoa, my hair's gone wild!
A spell to make dogs very friendly.
Stop it, that tickles!
Oh, a good omen!
A spell to make tea stems stand upright.
Yeah, despite how many there are, most are useless.
Well, you never know when they'll be useful,
so what's wrong with learning every one you can?
I know God boosted my memory,
but memorizing all the ones in here is gonna be hard.
A spell to draw distant
objects into your hand?
That could be useful.
Why don't you try using it?
Aports.
Huh?
Nothing's happening.
What did you try drawing toward you?
I figured Yae would be surprised
if she suddenly lost her katana.
Maybe a katana was too heavy for it to work?
I see. It does say it works on small objects.
This time I'll picture it clearly....
Aports!
What, what? Touya, what did you take?
This.
The ribbon tying Yae's hair.
It worked, then.
Depending on how it's used,
that could be convenient or terrifying.
Terrifying?
Because you'd lose objects without realizing it.
You could pickpocket all you want with that spell, right?
I see. It is scary when you think of it that way.
I guess it could steal money,
gems, and things of that nature.
Don't go doing it, okay?
Please don't do it.
I won't do something like that.
But...
I wonder if you could use this
to draw things like underwear to you.
I'm just joking.
Um...
My hair is blowing about in the wind.
A spell to reduce friction for a short period of time,
Slip...
Null Magic is full of spells
that are hard to figure out what to use them for, huh?
Hmm? This is...
Long Sense.
What does that spell do?
It expands your senses. It allows you to see
and hear things at a distance, apparently.
Don't go use it for peeping, okay?
I won't!
Can it pick up smells, too?
This smell is... iron?
No, it's blood!
Up ahead!
Come forth, Fire!
Whirling Spiral: Fire Storm!
Ow...
Friction, begone! Slip!
I guess Null Magic just depends on how you use it.
You have my gratitude.
I'm glad you're safe.
There's still more?!
Oh, beautiful swordsmanship.
Linze!
There's no end to them!
How many of them are there?!
Come forth, Dark!
I seek a scalebound warrior: Lizardman!
That's...
Summoning magic! That man is summoning the Lizardmen!
Got it! Slip!
That is far enough.
You all saved us back there.
No. More importantly, is anyone hurt?
Seven guards were done in.
Damn it! If only we'd noticed a little sooner!
Someone! Is anyone there?!
Leim...
Leim is...
Someone help Leim!
His chest...
There's an arrow in his chest!
Linze! Healing magic!
The arrow's lodged in his body.
Even if I used healing magic on him in this state,
the foreign object would remain in his body.
Leim!
My lady...
Leim! Leim!
It's time to bid farewell.
The time I spent with you was...
Leim!
Leim, don't try to talk! Leim!
Linze, you can heal him if we pull the arrow out, right?
Huh? Yes, but...
Leim...
All right!
Aports!
Huh? You drew the arrow from his body?
Come forth, Light!
Soothing Comfort: Cure Heal!
The pain is fading?
Leim!
Leim! Leim!
Incredible, Touya.
I'm grateful, Touya or whatever!
You have saved Leim's— no, all of our lives!
My apologies for the delayed introductions.
I'm Leim, a butler in service to Duke Ortlinde.
And this young lady is the Duke's daughter,
Sushie Urnea Ortlinde.
I'm Sushie Urnea Ortlinde!
Pleasure to meet you.
Yes...
Huh? What's wrong?
What's wrong?
How can you be so calm?!
She's related to the Duke! The Duke!
The Duke?
Duke is the highest rank a noble can have.
The rank is only given to members of the royal family.
The royal family? Huh?
Indeed.
My father, Duke Alfred Urnes Ortlinde,
is the younger brother of His Royal Highness!
So you're the King's niece?
Should I address you as Lady Sushie?
"Sue" will suffice.
We're not in a formal setting here,
so no need for formalities!
As I just said, we all owe you our lives.
But what's royalty doing out here?
I was returning to the royal capital
after visiting my grandmother.
And then you were attacked?
By ordinary bandits? Probably not, I suppose...
From what I heard, they were just hired hit men.
They didn't even know the name of whoever hired them.
I see. How unfortunate.
Spill everything!
There's nothing else to say!
So you wanted... what?
We can't protect the young lady on our own right now.
So, seeing your skill, I'd like to ask for your help.
Would you guard us on our journey?
Once we arrive at the royal capital,
we'll pay you a proper reward.
Guard you, huh?
Why not?
We're heading to the royal capital anyway.
I don't mind, either.
I entrust the decision to you, Master Touya.
All right.
Let's stick together until the royal capital, then.
Thank you for helping us!
That's the royal capital?
The capital of the Kingdom of Belfast, Alephis.
It's built on the bank of Lake Palette, formed by waterfalls flowing down,
earning it the nickname "The City of Lakes."
Sue!
Father!
Oh, Sue!
I'm glad you're safe!
When I heard the news, I thought I was going to die!
So you're the adventurers who saved my daughter?
You have my thanks.
Please, raise your head.
We only did what anyone naturally would have.
You show humility, too.
Allow me to introduce myself properly.
I am Alfred Urnes Ortlinde.
So you came to the royal capital
on a mission to deliver a letter?
Yes.
If you all hadn't accepted that mission,
my Sue may have been kidnapped, or even killed.
I'll have to thank whoever made the request.
Do you have any idea who the attackers were?
There are many who would see me
as a hindrance, given my position.
Perhaps someone thought they could
kidnap my daughter to threaten me.
Father.
Sorry for the wait.
Did you get to speak with Ellen?
Yes. I didn't want to worry her,
so I didn't tell her about the attack.
Um, who's Ellen?
Oh, my wife.
Sorry you can't see her,
even though you saved my daughter.
My wife is blind.
Is she... ill?
Yes, it was about five years ago.
She managed to survive, but she lost her vision.
Did you try magic healing?
Of course.
But it didn't help.
Even though it restored some of the damage to her body,
it had no effect on the aftereffects of her illness.
If my grandfather were still alive...
My wife's father, Sue's grandfather, wielded special magic.
He was able to remove afflictions from the body.
The purpose of Sue's latest journey was to try
and unravel his magic,
in hopes that, perhaps, she could learn it.
If only we could find someone capable
of using Grandfather's magic...
Sue, Null Magic is personal magic.
There won't be anyone who
can use the same spell.
But we can try searching for someone
with a spell that has similar effects.
Recovery.
How do you feel?
I can see...
I can see!
Darling! Sushie!
Ellen!
Mother!
I knew you'd be able to do it!
You can use any Null Magic, after all!
I'm truly impressed!
Your drive to aid others without fear of failure...
is something I respect from the bottom of my heart, Master Touya.
Thanks.
To save not only my daughter, but my wife, as well...
I wish to give you all proper thanks.
Bring it to me.
First, take this.
My gratitude for saving my daughter
and protecting her on her travels.
I want you to have it.
Ow. What's this?
There are 40 platinum coins inside.
What are platinum coins?
The denomination above gold coins.
Each one's worth ten gold.
Meaning 40 platinum is...
1,000 Yen
Coppergu
10 Copper
1,000 Yen
10,000 Yen
Coppergu
Silver
1,000 Yen
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
Silver
10 Copper
10,000 Yen
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Silver
Gold
10,000 Yen
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Gold
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Gold
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Gold
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Gold
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Gold
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Gold
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Gold
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Gold
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Gold
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
Gold
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
10 Gold
Gold
Platinum
10 Silver
100,000 Yen
10 Gold
1,000,000 Yen
Gold
Platinum
100,000 Yen
10 Gold
1,000,000 Yen
Platinum
10 Gold
1,000,000 Yen
Platinum
10 Gold
1,000,000 Yen
Platinum
10 Gold
1,000,000 Yen
Platinum
10 Gold
1,000,000 Yen
Platinum
10 Gold
1,000,000 Yen
Platinum
10 Gold
1,000,000 Yen
Platinum
10 Gold
1,000,000 Yen
Platinum
One! Ten! Hundred! Thousand! Ten thousand!
Hundred thousand! Million! Ten million!
40 million yen?!
This is way too much for us to accept!
If you plan to continue as adventurers, you'll surely have need of that coin.
Just think of it as capital.
Okay...
These are my family's medals.
With these, you can pass right through the checkpoints,
and make use of facilities available only to nobility.
It's proof that you have our duchy's
support should anything happen.
Come see us again sometime!
You'd better, okay?!
We've delivered the letter,
so now our mission's complete.
That sure was an eventful journey.
Yeah.
We're heading back to Reflet Village now.
What about you, Yae?
I have made up my mind!
Master Touya, I offer myself up to you.
Huh?!
N-No, I did not mean it in that manner!
Huh? Then what did you mean?
Though our journey together was short,
I have seen the manner of person you are.
You possess great power, yet never act arrogant,
and constantly choose to help others.
Your attitude is impressive.
So for the sake of my training,
I wish to remain at your side, Master Touya.
Huh?
What do you think?
Why not?
You can come with us!
Then you can join the guild,
and we can accept missions together!
Yeah, let's do that!
I would be honored.
It would be a shame to part here now that
we're all getting along so well.
Once again, it's a pleasure to have you, Yae.
Thank you, as well!
It's nice being able to bring smiles to others with my power.
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.