Hey, while we're here in the royal capital,
why don't we shop a bit before we return?
That's a good idea!
Yes.
Hey, I didn't see anyone like that in Reflet.
What's their race called?
The demi-humans?
There are several varieties: elves, dwarves,
different beastmen, different fairies.
Demi-humans, huh?
That's another world for you.
Hey, hey.
What's going on with that girl?
Um, is something the matter?
Wh-Why do you ask?!
Uh... Well, you seemed like something
was troubling you, so...
A-Actually, I got separated from my companion.
We had agreed on a place to meet up, but I don't know where I am now...
I'll guide you.
Huh?
Big Sis!
Arma!
I was worried about you!
I'm sorry.
I'm 17!
Oh, please...
Thank you for taking care of my little sister.
Not at all. I'm glad we ran into her.
Farewell.
Bye-bye!
Now, let's go shopping!
It'll probably be difficult going everywhere as a group,
so why don't we meet up at the inn two hours from now?
Sure.
No problems here.
Yes.
Master Touya's late...
Maybe he got lost?
I doubt that.
Oh, there he is!
You're late!
Sorry!
Did I come back late?
Sorry.
Press home to open
I'm 25 minutes late, huh?
You can tell the time with that thing, too?
Yeah. It's sort of like my own Null Magic.
More importantly, what's with that coat, Touya?
Huh?
Oh, this?
It's a coat that increases your magic resistance
to affinities you possess.
On the other hand, it doubles the damage you take
from affinities you don't.
It sounds like a coat made especially for you.
It looks good on you!
W-Well, shall we head home to Reflet?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 3
Shogi Board, and Underground Ruins
Shogi again?
Yeah.
You've played it several days in a row now.
I've got nothing to do in the shop with all the rain.
If you're going to use your brain,
I wish you'd use it to help the shop.
Modeling...
It allows you to reshape minerals and wooden objects, huh?
All right!
Modeling!
The test's a success.
What the heck is this?!
What about you, Barral? Is your shop all right?
I've left my wife in charge, so it's fine.
More importantly, think we could
have another shogi set, Touya?
Huh?
Could you please?
I don't really mind, but...
Thanks!
Check!
You stubborn bastard!
Jeez, both of you!
Sorry, just this one game.
Good grief.
H-Hey, Micah, where's everyone else?
I think Linze's in her room,
but Elze and Yae stepped out
to buy Café Parent's new dessert.
I hear you came up with it for her?
I did, but... they went in this rain?
We're back!
I'm soaked!
I have returned!
Welcome back. Manage to get it?
Pulled it off.
It helped that fewer people were out because of the rain.
It was delicious!
You ate it there, too?
Here, this one's for you, Micah.
Thanks.
One's for Linze, and another one's for us,
so could you deliver the last one to the Duke?
Me?
It's only common sense to share
with people who've helped you.
Then shouldn't you come with me, too?
Heavens, no.
Good! This is so good!
Mind your manners, Sue.
But this truly is good!
So good!
This... "roll cake," you called it?
I envy the people of Reflet
who get to eat this whenever they please.
If I could use Gate like you, I'd go buy some every day.
If you like, I can give your mansion's chefs the recipe
and directions to make it.
Mother!
We'll be able to eat it every day!
Oh, Sue.
Limit yourself to every other day.
I think every other day might still be too much...
So Mister Touya, you call this shogi?
Yes.
It's a two-player game
where you try to capture the enemy king first.
Would you like to try it?
Absolutely!
I want to play, too!
Well, be patient. I'm up first.
I see...
So if you capture your enemy's pieces,
you can reform your army.
Yes, that's the aspect
that adds depth to the game of shogi.
Father! When will you let me play?!
Watch out! You'll mess up the board!
In a little while.
You should go play outside in the meantime.
It's raining outside!
Touya!
Do something about this!
Hey, that tickles, Sue!
I want to play, too! Me, too!
D-Duke, isn't it about time you let Sue—
Duke!
Stop!
This is fun.
I'd love to play this with my brother, too!
One more game!
Just one more game!
I think I'm gonna see shogi in my dreams.
I won't be forced to play anymore!
Oh! So this is the royal capital's guild?
There are lots of quests here, too.
We were right to pay a visit here.
Touya, you haven't lost your touch
from playing shogi all the time, have you?
It's not like I wanted to play that much.
Anyway, this quest...
The one about defeating megaslimes.
We can accept it here, too.
Not that!
I hate slimy and sticky things!
Still a no, huh?
Oh, no!
What were you thinking about?
N-Nothing.
Then how about this one?
Yae, it's heading your way!
Understood!
Elze, how's it going with the One-Horned Wolves?!
I managed to finish them off.
Jeez, there were nearly twenty of them. Man!
Mistress Elze! Duck!
Linze! Freeze his legs with Ice magic!
A-All right!
There!
Entwine thus, Ice!
Frozen Curse: Icebind!
Multiple!
Strike true, Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance: Shining Javelin!
All done now.
That was exhausting.
There's really nothing here in the old royal capital, huh?
It'd be cool if you could find
the king's hidden treasure or something.
No, since they only relocated the capital,
they would be sure to take all their treasures with them.
I know that. I was just saying it.
Search: treasure!
You used Search?!
How'd it go?
At the very least, there's no treasure nearby.
I see. That's a shame.
But maybe there's something valuable here
that Touya just doesn't recognize as treasure.
You have a point there.
Search: historic relics!
It found something!
Huh?!
Wh-Which way?!
I'm sensing it in that direction.
It's big. What is this?
Big?
It's under this rubble.
But how do we...
Leave it to me!
Burst forth, Fire!
Crimson Eruption: Explosion!
It's taken care of.
Don't you think that's
going a bit too far, Linze?
The entrance to a dungeon?
Come forth, Light!
Tiny Illumination: Light!
What a creepy place.
Maybe it's haunted.
Wh-What are you saying, Mistress Linze?!
There's no way g-ghosts would show up!
That's right. They don't exist!
What's the matter?
So Elze takes the rear
at times like this, huh?
Shut up!
What is this?
Linze, can you read what this says?
No, I can't understand it at all.
It doesn't look like it's
ancient magic script.
Maybe I should take a picture of it.
Wh-What was that?!
Oops, sorry.
Oh, it was just your smartphone?
Looks like they're getting used to the smartphone, too.
SLO-MO                  VIDEO                  PHOTO                 SQUARE                    PANO
Hey, everyone, come over here!
There's something buried here!
This is... an Earth spell stone.
It's probably set up to activate some kind of spell
when mana's passed through it.
Some spell? Like a trap?
I can't say that's not a possibility, but...
Okay, then pass some mana through it, Touya.
Huh? Me?
You're the only one here with Earth affinity.
Well, I guess.
Wait, why are you all backing away?
Well, just in case.
To be on the safe side.
S-Same here.
What?!
That was an awfully gaudy way to open a door.
What's that?
Seriously, what is that?
Is it some kind of statue?
Glass?
It's too dim to see very well.
Linze, was the duration on the Light spell this short?
Huh?
I know I'm bad with Light magic,
but I can still keep up a spell for around two hours.
Huh? But it does seem like the light's fading.
It's definitely fading.
M-Master Touya!
Your Light's mana is being absorbed by that thing!
Huh?
No way... It's alive?!
This is...
This is bad! We've gotta run!
Gate!
Hurry!
What was that?!
I've never seen a magic beast like that before!
You think that underground space caved in?
It can't be!
Come forth, Fire!
Crimson Duet: Fire Arrow!
It absorbed my magic?
In that case...
What a hard shell!
Why, you...
What are we supposed to do about this?!
Okay, then... Slip!
Good!
Linze!
Don't cast magic on it directly!
You can affect it with indirect magic!
I see! All right, then!
Come forth, Ice!
Grand Frozen Mass: Ice Rock!
Boost, full power!
We did it!
You're kidding me!
It regenerated?
Big Sis!
Yae! Linze! Hold him still!
I'm on it!
Got it!
Healing magic!
Thanks. I'm all right now.
You shouldn't push yourself too hard.
It absorbs magic, and it's abnormally tough.
Doesn't it have any weaknesses?
There's nothing we can do if it can regenerate!
It's stealing our magic for regeneration?
Just like in shogi.
That's it! If we capture the king...
Elze, listen.
Can you do that?
I don't know.
But it's worth trying.
All right.
Aports!
Elze!
Boost!
How's that?!
Is it over?
Yeah, I think so.
I'm surprised you noticed that, Touya.
I just recalled the moment we found that thing.
It kept regenerating when we broke its body, right?
So I thought maybe that red ball
in its head might be its core.
You have sharp wits, Master Touya.
Should we be reporting this to the guild, then?
Considering this used to be the royal capital,
I think it's best to report to the national government.
Hey, why don't we try talking to the Duke about it?
I see. You found these ruins in the old royal capital?
Yes.
We'll dispatch an official expedition to investigate.
Of course, we'll look into that magic beast, too.
But the underground ruins collapsed...
I see...
But I did manage to get a picture of the relief.
Picture?
This.
Wh-What is this?!
One of my Null Magic spells for recording images.
You always amaze me.
If I can have some time, I can make a copy to give you.
Please do.
It's possible this might contain some clue
to the mystery of why the capital was moved.
You don't know why the capital was moved?
There's no record?
Unfortunately, none are left.
Is that so...
I'm sorry, but I'd like to request your aid in this matter.
Would that be all right?
Yes. It shouldn't be a problem
if we have to fight it again.
That's reassuring.
That sure was a lot of trouble.
We didn't find any treasure, either.
We can go treasure hunting another time.
Let's go home.
Next time, I hope we go somewhere well-lit.
Gate!
Drawing magic...
That's pretty useful.
Sorry.
Huh? Is he heading out?
Oh, Mister Touya!
To think you'd visit in this time of need!
God must have sent you to me!
What on earth is going on?
My brother has been poisoned.
What?!
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.