So, where are these ruins you want to visit, Leen?
I don't know the location.
Only that they're the "Niruya Ruins."
Niruya?
Hmm... My father might know.
Then let us make haste to see him.
Hold on, Mistress Leen!
Why is that girl leading us?
She really does as she pleases...
That's my hometown, Oedo!
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 9
Oedo, and the Immortal Gem
By the way, Yae, does Eashen have a king, too?
Technically, yes, but each region
is effectively governed by its lord.
I see.
What's the name of this region's lord?
Tokugawa Ieyahsu.
Ieyahsu?!
First Oedo and now Tokugawa...
It's similar down to that detail, too?
Is something the matter?
Not really.
What's that?
What are they doing?
They're palanquin bearers.
You pay money to ride the palanquin they carry,
and they take you to your destination.
Oh...
Touya, those people over there are wearing wooden shoes!
Wooden shoes?
Oh, geta.
You're very knowledgeable
for someone born outside of Eashen, Master Touya.
Huh? W-Well, yeah.
Still, something seems odd.
Is anyone home?
Yes, coming.
My, Mistress Yae!
Ayane! It's been so long!
Welcome home!
Mistress Nanae!
Mistress Yae has returned!
Mother!
Yae, I'm so glad to see you safe.
Mother.
Yae, who are these people?
Oh, they're my friends.
They've done a great deal for me.
Well, I thank you for that.
By the way, Mother, where is Father?
Is he at the castle?
Your Father isn't here.
He accompanied Lord Ieyahsu to the battlefield.
The battlefield?
Who are they fighting?
The Takedas.
Their armies suddenly advanced several days ago,
and the master left for Kawagoe Fortress
with Master Jutaro to hold them off.
So that's the reason the city seemed odd.
So, how fares the battle?
There are rumors that at this rate,
it's only a matter of time before Kawagoe Fortress falls.
Then my father and brother?
It can't be...
Master Touya! Use Recall again!
Yeah, let's go.
You have my gratitude.
I never expected we'd be heading to war.
Well, I'll come, too.
The ruins can wait.
I promise I'll bring your husband
and Yae's brother back home safely.
Don't worry.
Um, who are you?
Oh, uh...
Hey, hey, ho!
...I say!
There, huh?
I don't know about your father yet,
but your brother seems safe.
That's good, then.
We must hurry to their aid!
Hold it. Do you think you can rush in there
and remain unscathed?
But...
Can't you fly over there
with the wings on your back, Mistress Leen?
Impossible. They've degenerated.
I can only float a bit with them.
I see...
Don't worry.
I'll use Long Sense to check out the area
a kilometer away, then jump there with Gate.
Then I'll repeat that process.
That should be much safer.
But I'll go alone first.
Once I get into the fortress,
I'll link up with this spot using Gate, so wait here.
I see. That would be the safest bet.
Okay, I'm off, then.
What's that?
Master Jutaro!
They keep rising back up, no matter how many we defeat!
We can't hold them all!
What on earth are those soldiers?
There are rumors that they stop when their mask breaks,
but we're not certain yet.
Who are you?!
P-Please wait.
I'm not an enemy.
You're Yae's brother, Kokonoe Jutaro, correct?
I am indeed Jutaro, but how do you know Yae?
I'm her friend. My name is Mochizuki Touya.
Yae's friend?
Yes, that's why we're here to help you.
She's nearby, as well.
Yae's nearby?
Mistress Yae?
Can I see Yae?
Of course.
Gate.
Brother!
Yae? Is that really you?
Yes!
Wh-Who are these people?
They're my friends!
Every one of them is very reliable.
More importantly, how's Father?
Is he safe?
Yes, he's safe. Don't worry about him.
He is currently guarding Lord Ieyahsu.
That's good to hear.
Program: start.
Condition: touching the screen targets.
Activation Sequence: set all as spell targets using Multiple.
Program: end.
Come forth, Light!
Soothing Comfort: Cure Heal!
What? The pain's receding.
My wound's healed, too.
Wh-What just happened?
Master Touya's healing magic.
Magic?
By the way, what's with those guys wearing the demon masks?
I don't know.
They should be dead already, and yet...
Apparently, they'll stop if the masks are broken.
Possibly artifacts, then?
Artifacts?
Relics of ancient civilizations, and powerful magic items.
That thing of yours is an artifact as well, isn't it?
Well, either way, those guys in masks are trouble.
Sounds like it'll be best to eliminate them all at once.
You can do that?
Yes.
There's quite a lot of them, though...
Oh, well. Multiple!
What's that?
Master Touya, are you really...
Strike true, Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance: Shining Javelin!
Was that your doing?
Yeah.
It's just...
...not even surprising anymore.
Impressive as always, Master Touya!
Thank you, thank you!
Yes, that's right! I'm Mochizuki!
Thank you!
First, allow me to express my gratitude
for your aid in this matter.
I am the head of the Tokugawas, Ieyahsu.
No, please pay it no mind.
Still, to think you would be guarding Princess Yumina.
I'm surprised, indeed.
It's the result of my training!
And this man, the one who saved our fortress, is...
This is Mochizuki Touya.
He's my guard as well, and also my future husband.
Wait, I—
I...
I'm in a weird spot where I kind of am, and kind of am not.
So, about the Takeda army.
Do you think they'll back down after that?
They might attack us again, once they reform their ranks.
Still, between the demon mask soldiers
and their army's sudden invasion,
the rumors must really be true.
Rumors?
The rumors that Lord Schingen has already passed away.
And that, at present, the dark strategist
Yamamoto Kansukay is commanding an army of the dead.
He's probably using an artifact
or magic to manipulate corpses.
So do you think this will all settle down
if we can capture this Yamamoto Kansukay?
Most likely.
But Kansukay is holed up in the castle of his main camp,
and we haven't figured out where that is.
Then allow me to show you the way.
Who's there?!
I come with a secret message for Lord Tokugawa Ieyahsu.
I am Tsubaki, servant to General Kousaka Masanohbu,
one of Takeda's elite four.
You're with General Kousaka?
It seems the rumors are true, then.
What?
It would seem all of Takeda's elite four, aside from
General Kousaka, have been thrown in an underground prison.
He asks us to stop Kansukay and save the Takedas.
General Kousaka is pretending
to obey Kansukay in hopes of reclaiming the Takeda clan.
We're under no obligation to save the Takedas!
But if this keeps up, the Tokugawas are done for.
What shall we do, Touya?
Leave this to us.
I thank you.
But you'll be heading into the heart of the enemy camp.
True, even if we use Gate,
it'll be troublesome if they discover us too soon.
Hey, Leen, you said you use magic to make
the wings on your back invisible, right?
Could that...
Of course.
It can make the whole body unseen, as well.
Good.
Though we can't exactly infiltrate it in large numbers,
so we'll go with me, Tsubaki, and Leen.
Paula can stay here.
That works, right, Leen?
Yes.
Paula, stay here.
All right, then, let's go ahead...
Wait, wait!
You're going to sneak in there in broad daylight?
I guess you have a point.
In that case, I'd like to return home for a time.
I have to let them know that Brother and Father are safe.
It's probably a good idea to tell Laim
and the others we won't be coming home, as well.
Right now, we should prioritize delivering food
to everyone in the fortress.
You're all right.
It's hard to imagine you're
the talented man who just annihilated countless enemies.
Well, allow me to prepare horses in the meantime.
Oh, no, there's no need.
Tsubaki, can you picture the Takeda camp in your mind?
Why?
I'd like to read your mind so that
we can get there more easily.
All right.
Darling, do your best!
I'm not your darling!
Leen, can you give us your invisibility spell?
It's not invisibility. It affects vision...
Oh, whatever.
Distort, Light!
Directed Bending: Invisible!
You vanished!
I can still see Leen, though.
It would be inconvenient otherwise.
Oh, I can hear your voices.
That just leaves...
Gate.
Huh?
A barrier.
It must be blocking teleportation via Gate.
A barrier?
Kansukay probably erected it.
Would that negate our invisibility spell, too?
We'll be fine.
It only negates spells that target the premises.
I can get through the gate
without raising suspicion. Shall I destroy it?
Don't do that.
Once the barrier's destroyed, they'll be on alert.
True.
Then we'll follow Tsubaki through the gate to get inside.
That works, right, Lee—
Hey, Touya!
How can you take advantage of your invisibility like that?
Touya?
Huh?! No! That's Leen!
I've been in front of you this whole time!
No... Hey, not so...
There's more than expected here.
You hide it under clothes?
These are quite nice...
That's not...
Huh? Be more direct, you say?
Fine, then, you pervert.
I didn't say that!
Cut it out already!
Ow!
You're fine now.
I'll hit her to make sure she listens.
Hit my butt?
You stop talking!
Touya, you're so mean...
Huh?! Me?!
Jeez, Leen, what are you doing?
We're in the middle of an operation!
Are we even going to make it through this?
Can I?
H-Hold on!
Who's there?
General Baba, it's Tsubaki.
I've come to rescue you on General Kousaka's orders.
Kousaka's?
These two are guests of Lord Tokugawa,
Master Touya and Mistress Leen. They're here to help.
Don't worry.
All right.
So, where are General Naito and General Yamagata?
In the cells further back.
The cells further back? Got it.
Modeling.
You're capable of some rather
mysterious things, young man.
Yes, well...
Oh, General Baba, I'm glad to see you're doing well.
Looks like things are getting interesting, General Baba.
Young man, sorry, but can you...
Right.
What are we planning to do now?
Once I've helped you all get outside the castle,
we plan to capture Yamamoto Kansukay.
Hey, hey, take me with you.
I owe that bastard plenty of payback.
I don't mind, but...
Where's Kansukay right now?
I believe he'll be in the central quarter.
I can't find him. Is it because of the barrier?
Leen, how can we destroy that barrier?
There should be some talisman with magic power.
Oh, I know the place.
Let's pick up some weapons along the way.
We're gonna cut loose after this anyway, right?
That's definitely it.
The garden lantern is one of the talismans.
Okay, is everyone ready?
H-Hey, what are those?!
Are you doing that again?
It'd be a problem if we were surrounded after teleporting.
Strike true, Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance: Shining Javelin!
Was all of that your doing?
Well, yes.
Whoa, now... Are you sure you didn't
get Kansukay already with that?
No, I only defeated the demon mask soldiers.
I see. So that attack came from you four.
How did you pull it off?
We have no reason to tell you!
Just die already!
Lord Oyakata...
Oyakata?
Their lord. In other words, Takeda Schingen.
Kansukay, how dare you use Lord Oyakata like this?!
Lord Oyakata, please move!
That won't work.
Or will you attack your precious Lord Oyakata?
You scumbag!
Please stop this, Lord Oyakata!
Touya, what should we do?
I can't bear to see him in that state.
There's nothing we can do now!
I knew you wouldn't be able to
bear arms against your Lord Oyakata.
So I—
Young man, you...
Well, it's not like I owe him anything.
That's true, but...
That was pretty impressive.
But I still have this!
So long as I possess this Immortal Gem, I cannot die!
So you're using that gem's power
to make your masked soldiers undying, too?
Precisely!
This wonderful artifact gives me immense mana
and power over dea—
Aports.
When did you...
Sticky fingers.
This was the fastest way, wasn't it?
Well, this is no good.
It's cursed to corrupt the heart of its owner.
I'm surprised you can tell.
Don't underestimate the eyes of fairy folk.
G-Give that back!
Artifacts are very valuable items,
but it's best to destroy this one.
Huh?! Stop!
No.
Lord Oyakata is...
I see. So you're searching for the Niruya Ruins?
I've heard they're on the sea floor.
The sea floor?!
I've also been to an island near them,
and it was quite far from here.
That's all right.
Let's use Recall and Gate again.
Huh?
What? You don't like doing it with old men?
General Baba! How could you, when you have me?!
What a wonderful view!
Well, Father, Mother, Brother, and Ayane, I'm heading out.
Take care.
Master Touya, I'll never forget
this debt we owe you.
No trouble. I wish you all well, too.
Gate.
How pretty!
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.