Huh? Here?
This is way too huge!
So you received this instead of knighthood?
They said I had to publicly decline,
so I went to the knighting ceremony...
but then they suddenly offered this mansion.
Perhaps this was their goal from the start?
They got you good.
You think so, too?
It's quite a lovely home.
It's going to be hard work just
to keep a house this big clean...
It's too big for five people to live in.
Huh?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 6
Moving, and a Dragon
Huh? What?
Um, Master Touya...
Is it all right for us to live here with you?
Of course.
But this house was a gift to you from the king.
So wasn't it meant for you and Yumina to live in?
If it's a home meant for two people who love each other,
it doesn't seem right for us to live here, too...
People who love each other?
I like all four of you equally, and I consider you all family.
So there shouldn't be a problem...
Linze?
What's the matter, everyone?
I-I'll go look at the second floor!
A-And I'll go look at the attic!
I-I-I am curious about the kitchen, as well!
What was that about?
I see. You like all four of us equally, like family?
I suppose that's a step forward.
I, too, hope to be your bride
and share my life with you, Touya.
I have no intention of monopolizing you,
so this is acceptable, too.
I'll go speak with the others.
Huh? What? What's going on?
I really like all four of them, though.
Whisper
How strange...
This is a nice garden.
You like it?
Yes, very much so.
Touya.
U-Um, Touya...
Is it really okay for us all to live here?
Of course.
You won't tell us to leave later, will you?
Why would I do that?
You'll treat us the same...
as Lady Yumina, then?
Naturally.
Well, then, we shall all be living here together.
We'll move forward with what we
discussed once your minds are made up.
Yeah.
Yes.
Understood.
Discussed? What did you discuss?
It's a secret.
O-Okay...
It seems you're the one
with the least authority in this household, Master.
I am the butler, Laim. Pleased to make your acquaintance.
These ladies are temporary workers
sent here by the Maid's Guild.
My name is Lapis.
My name is Cecile.
Pleasure to meet you.
These two will oversee matters within the mansion,
and these two will be in charge of security.
Laim has been in charge of caring
for my father for many years.
Huh? The king?
Why is such a man coming to our home?
I've surrendered my duties in the king's service to my son.
I decided to spend the rest of my life serving
the man who saved my younger brother.
Younger brother?
His name is Leim.
He serves His Grace, Duke Ortlinde.
Oh! Leim from Sue's family!
Touya, what do you say?
If you recommend him, I'm all for it.
All right, if you would, please.
Thank you very much.
Now then, everyone, let's get to work at once.
Yes!
I can't believe the man who cared
for the king works for us now.
It just goes to show how much promise he sees in you.
Having a talented butler will be a great help.
Master Touya, His Grace Duke Ortlinde
and Lady Sushie have arrived.
Touya, I came to see you!
Another cute one's here!
Yumina, I heard you got engaged to Touya!
I was surprised.
I'm the one who was most surprised.
And here I was thinking of having you marry Sue.
Both my brother and Yumina are cunning.
You were thinking of that, Father?
Well, I'd welcome Touya, of course!
Then, are you interested in marrying Sue along
with Yumina, Mister Touya?
Please don't get carried away like that.
Well, I'll stand down for today.
For today?
Actually, I'm here with a different request for all of you.
What's that?
Recently, our nation has decided to form an alliance
with the Kingdom of Mismede.
This means we'll need to prepare a venue
for both kings to discuss matters.
But, while traveling to one nation
would be best for the discussions,
that naturally comes with dangers.
So with that in mind...
You'd like to use Touya's Gate, yes?
Indeed, Yumina. You catch on quickly.
But I can only use that spell
to travel to places I've been to—
Wait, you mean...
Yes. I'd like you to travel to Mismede.
I thought so.
I'm a commander of Mismede's troops, Garen.
I'm a member of Belfast Kingdom's
First Knight Squad, Lyon Blitz.
Soldiers from both nations will guard us until we reach the royal capital of Mismede.
Thank you for escorting us.
Letting us travel with you two will be a big help, Olga.
I was just about to return to my homeland, anyway.
I'm glad I get to journey with you all, as well!
First, we will head to
the city of Canaan within Belfast territory.
Then we will cross the Great Gau River
into Mismede territory.
We'll be sure to protect you on our travels.
We're counting on you, Sir Lyon.
Y-Yes!
This one!
Too bad.
The correct choices were this and this.
You're right!
I lose again.
You're amazing, Yumina!
Yae, switch with me.
It's nothing so grand.
Why don't you try playing shogi with Olga?
Dolan taught me how to play shogi back at the Silver Moon!
Then let's play something else over here.
I'm 17!
Oh, please...
So, the puss in boots became a noble
and lived happily ever after.
That was a good story, Touya!
What is it?
Someone is approaching. Several of them.
It's probably highway bandits.
Uh, bandits...
There are 28 in total.
Let me try something real quick.
Enchant: Multiple.
Yeah, it worked.
Now I can lock on to all of them.
Paralyze!
Wh-What was that?
I used a paralysis spell.
They should be unable to move.
What do we do with this lot?
Let's dispatch a mounted runner to fetch guards.
Sorry for the trouble, Sir Lyon.
Oh, no, this is my duty!
Please, pay it no mind.
Well, I'll go inform my men.
Oh-ho, I see how it is.
Oh, to be young.
To be young, indeed.
To be young, yes.
Yes, to be young.
When did you guys...
Do you think Mistress Olga is aware of Sir Lyon's feelings?
I think she is.
She doesn't seem as dense as a certain someone.
Huh? What?
He may be dense, but Touya's also too kind
to anyone and everyone.
Oh, I agree with that.
I think there's a problem
with the way he leads people on, too.
Do you get it?
Sit there, on your heels!
Why?
Just do it!
O-Okay...
Oh? Touya, look.
Lyon, getting a souvenir?
Mister Touya?!
No, ah, um, i-it's for my... my mother.
Yes! For my mother!
I figured I'd buy her something.
Oh?
Hey, Arma, pick something out.
I'll buy it for you as a memento of Belfast.
Really?
Then...
This one!
It looks good on you.
Thank you very much.
I'll take this.
Thank you very much!
Does Olga like brooches like this, too?
Uh, my sister...
Oh, she loves Elius flowers like this one.
She buys them often.
I see.
Well, Lyon, we'll be heading back now.
All right.
Splendidly done, Touya.
You figured me out?
I wanted a gift from there as well, though.
Sorry.
Well, so long as I receive
a ring on my finger one day, I'll be satisfied.
I don't know if that's...
Sorry, Touya.
Getting seasick isn't that uncommon.
Shall we rest for today and set out tomorrow?
No, I'm all right now.
I felt much better once I was off the boat.
You could have him carry you longer, Linze.
Big Sis, what are you saying?
What are you...
Was it embarrassing being carried all that time?
Oh, no, it's not that...
It's no use.
That's Touya, after all.
Huh? What?
Did I imagine that?
No, there was definitely someone observing us.
They've fully concealed their presence now.
I guess I should keep an eye out.
Everything is ready.
Okay.
My, that hair accessory is lovely.
Huh? I-Is it?
Thank you very much.
It looks so nice on you.
I would love to receive one from the man I care about.
Of course, if he'd show it with his actions, like
by hugging me tightly or something, nothing could beat that.
Well, let's get going!
It looks like we won't be
reaching Eld Village by nightfall.
Is there anywhere we can set up camp?
There are magic beasts in the forest,
but we should be safe in a group this large.
That's a little scary.
With Kohaku around,
the magic beasts won't even come close.
Thanks, Kohaku.
Okay!
Oh, is it time?
My hair hasn't finished drying yet.
Come on, let's get back before anyone gets suspicious.
Okay.
Touya!
What happened?!
I don't know.
The animals in the forest suddenly started carrying on.
Something big is coming...
from the sky!
A dragon...
All the way out here?
What's going on?
Dragons normally live in the sacred grounds
at the center of our nation.
They never leave that area and rampage,
unless there's an intruder.
Did someone enter the sacred grounds?!
Not necessarily.
On rare occasions, young dragons appear in villages
and go on rampages, too.
It's heading straight for Eld Village.
What?!
Yumina, stay here and take care of Olga and the others.
Okay.
Let's head to Eld!
Prioritize rescuing the villagers!
Strike true, Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance: Shining Javelin!
Kohaku!
Linze!
Y-Yes!
Here it comes!
That's it! Follow me!
You bastard! You dare insult my master?!
Kohaku, you can understand it?
"You tiny worms who dare interfere with my amusement,"
"I will rend your bodies to shreds
and eat you," is what it said.
The snot-nosed brat can't even speak human!
Amusement?
Sounds like an awfully selfish creature.
Linze, I'll knock him down.
Once I do, cut off his wings!
Roger that.
Multiple!
Strike true, Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance: Shining Javelin!
Come forth, Water!
Feel My Blade, Both Cold and Clear: Aqua Cutter!
Boost!
That was close.
Y-Yes.
This thing...
Boost!
Ow! This thing's too hard!
At least he doesn't regenerate, too.
Fall back!
Oh, no!
Slip!
Yae, Elze.
Buy me some time.
Linze, erect a big defensive wall of ice near me.
Kohaku, protect Linze.
Over here!
Come forth, Ice!
Eternal Frozen Ridge: Ice Wall!
Modeling!
Multiple!
Strike true, Light!
Sparkling Holy Lance: Shining Javelin!
Modeling!
Take this!
We did it!
We did it, Master Touya!
Brilliant!
Way to go, Master. I feel better now.
Another one?!
My comrade has caused you much trouble.
I apologize.
You can talk?
I am the red dragon who reigns over the sacred ground.
I came here to retrieve the one who went wild, but...
Red Dragon, tell the Azure Monarch to raise his kin right.
This presence...
It can't be... the White Monarch!
No wonder even the black dragon was...
Don't misunderstand.
My master was the one who defeated him.
This brat had the gall to insult my master.
He got what he deserved.
What?!
A human is master of the White Monarch?!
My apologies for the repeated rudeness.
I humbly beg your mercy.
Oh, well, I'm fine as long we know why he did it.
But just this once.
Make sure you give the young ones
a good talking-to so they don't do this again.
Yes, certainly.
Sheesh, what a hassle.
This is the problem with the Azure Monarch.
What's the matter, everyone?
What's the matter?
Touya, you were unaffected by that?
Yeah, it was nothing.
This is so unfair.
It's all right now.
I'm glad you're safe!
I'm beat...
Touya, here's a blanket.
Thanks, Yumina.
Are you awake?
Huh?
You're finally awake.
You slept well.
You looked so relaxed.
Um, did something happen?
Not really.
Yes, yes, that's enough now.
Rock-paper-scissors is a sacred match.
No hard feelings, remember?
I know.
Yeah.
What a terrible shame.
Were you competing over something?
Nothing at all.
Kohaku, what happened?
How shall I put it?
Just a battle among women.
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.