Wow, how pretty!
It's been forever since I saw the ocean.
It has, Big Sis.
I'll join you, then.
Hot!
Hot! Hot, hot!
Search: ruins
That's where the ruins are?
Yeah. It looks like they're submerged around here.
It feels nice and cool!
If only I had a swimsuit, I'd go swimming.
Hold on. Swimsuits exist?
They probably sell them at the store.
That's it, Touya! Let's return to Belfast and buy some!
But our goal is to investigate the ruins...
I don't mind, as long as they'll still help
with the investigation.
Well, then, since we have the chance, why not enjoy it?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 10
Ocean, and Vacations
The ocean! The ocean!
How thoughtful of you to invite us to join you
at the ocean in Eashen.
I figured we all might as well enjoy it together.
I couldn't turn down an invitation from Master Leen.
So she came unwillingly?
This is so nice!
Cecile, is this the ocean?
I can't see the opposite shore!
We're here!
Sorry. It took a while to get ready.
Thank you for inviting us.
Let's get changed into our swimsuits and go play!
Where can we go to get changed, though?
Why don't I make us changing tents?
I'll make some things to play with while I'm at it.
First in!
No peeping, okay?
I won't peep!
My, is Linze the older sister?
Shut up!
You're no better yourself!
Touya!
Wh-What do you think?
Yeah, all three of you look really good.
You mean it?!
But I still feel funny in this outfit.
Elze? What's wrong?
Huh? I-It's nothing.
Good for you, Big Sis.
E-Enough of this topic!
Let's go have fun!
All right, let's go!
Oh, Mistress Elze's the first one in?
Then I'll join, too!
There!
You've done it now!
Payback time!
Linze, come join us!
Got you!
Gulp...
Touya?
Y-You're not swimming, Linze?
Oh, I'm not a very good swimmer.
I see. Be careful you don't get heatstroke, then.
I will.
Touya!
Well? How do our swimsuits look?
Yeah, they're cute.
Hey, Touya!
The ocean is incredible, isn't it?
It's so big!
Is this your first time seeing the ocean?
Yeah! I'm gonna take a bunch of sand home
with me so I won't forget it!
Good idea.
This will help you remember faster.
Oh, it's me!
Amazing! What is this?
It's a tool for recording things we see.
Awesome, awesome, awesome!
You can do anything, Touya!
Naturally. He's my future husband, after all!
What? Really?!
Don't tell weird lies.
Go on, go play.
All right, let's go, Renne!
Okay, Sue!
They get along well.
D-Don't conceal your presence around us!
It's a habit from my day job.
An occupational disease, huh?
I know I need to be watching over Lady Sue and Renne,
but it took me a while to get changed.
Yeah... that must have been tough.
There weren't any swimsuits that fit perfectly,
so I had a hard time finding one.
This one's a little tight, too.
I don't need that kind of information!
Lady Sue, Renne!
Let me join you!
I wonder if they really float when they're that big.
Does what float?
Seriously, don't conceal your presence around us!
My apologies.
So, what floats?
Floating rings!
I was wondering if they were really floating.
They look fine to me.
Right!
So what's that?
I do still need to do my job.
I brought drinks for the ladies.
You should play some too, Lapis.
I'll take turns having fun with Cecile, so don't worry.
I won't let myself lose to you, Brother!
It's time to show my pride as the King of Belfast!
This is nothing!
Those three are always full of energy.
May you grow bigger, Big Sis.
Now, it's about time to head out.
Touya!
How does it look?
You look good in it. It's cute.
Thank you.
I chose it hoping you'd say that.
Well, shall we go swimming together?
No, I want to try searching for the ruins a bit,
so I'll join you after I'm done with that.
Then please be sure you do come
when you finish. I'll be waiting.
Yeah.
Same goes for our marriage.
The marriage... I completely forgot about that.
Why the long face?
I-It's nothing.
Is Paula going to swim?
She has Protection on her, so she'll be fine.
She won't get wet or moldy.
I should use that too, since I'll be diving into the ocean.
Protection.
Kohaku, I guess you won't be swimming.
You don't like water, right?
Don't assume I'm like ordinary cats!
What's wrong?
That girl isn't here.
That girl?
You know, the one whose chest you groped a few days ago.
Oh, Tsubaki?
Wait, I wasn't the one who groped her!
But you wanted to see it, right?
You wanted to see her in a swimsuit.
You just pictured it.
I-I didn't! Not at all!
You really are a man, Touya.
What's that supposed to mean?
Now then, let's go ahead and try to make a bit of progress.
With what?
You just said it yourself, remember?
Investigating the ruins.
Oh!
Let's try diving under for starters.
Oh, I'm not going.
For one thing, I don't intend to swim,
and I don't want to get a sunburn.
Then why are you in a swimsuit?
You threatened me into it.
Just what am I in your mind?
Are you all right?
Somehow.
I found the entrance to the ruins,
but I couldn't hold my breath any longer.
So the ruins are completely submerged under the ocean.
Well, what shall we do about that?
Is there any spell that would let us function underwater?
I've heard of one, but I never learned it
because I wasn't interested.
You should've learned it.
Charlotte, come over here.
Master Leen?
Do you know a spell that lets people function underwater?
Uh, if I recall...
Looks like you don't remember it.
Honestly, I wish your brain had
matured instead of your body.
What are you doing?!
You're wearing the swimsuit all day today as punishment.
Also, I'm not letting you return
to the royal palace until I do.
What?! But Master Leen,
you asked me because you don't remember either!
What a tyrant.
Master, you want to function underwater?
Yeah. Do you know a good way to do that?
I know of one who controls water of all types,
who could solve all your problems.
Who?
One on par with me, the White Emperor: the Black Emperor.
You can't typically summon a specific individual
with summoning magic.
We'll mix my spirit energy with Master's magic power.
If we use that method to summon,
they're sure to notice and answer our call.
Still, summoning the Black Emperor?
I'm surprised enough that this is the White Emperor.
I can't believe there's another one.
If you ask me, you're pretty out
there yourself for creating Paula.
Master, I don't know what they'll
seek in exchange for a pact.
Be careful, just in case.
Hey, you keep saying "they."
I thought we were summoning one?
The Black Emperor is a two-in-one being.
Well, you'll understand once we call them.
You who governs winter, water,
and the northern mountains, heed my voice.
Answer my call and appear before me.
Here they come.
Well, if it isn't the White Emperor.
It's been a long time. Have you been well?
It's been a while, Black Emperor.
I told you, just Black is fine.
You meanie.
So who's this young man?
This is my master, Mochizuki Touya, who named me Kohaku.
Your master?
You took a human like this as a master?
How far you've fallen, White Emperor.
Say what you will.
Soon he'll be your master, too.
Nonsense.
Very well, Touya or whatnot.
Let's test you to see
if you're worthy of forging a pact with us.
Sure, but what should I do?
Fight us.
If you manage to remain standing
with all limbs intact by sunset, we'll forge a pact with you.
Okay. Let's do it.
Touya, don't get careless
and let them pull a fast one on you.
Don't worry. I'll manage.
You're surprisingly calm.
I'll commend your courage, at least.
Let us begin!
Slip!
Enchant, Slip.
Program: start.
Condition: the effect of Slip wears out.
Activation Sequence: activate spell Slip.
Termination condition: release command from caster.
Program: end.
Wh-What?! What's that boy planning?!
You've set it to cast another Slip when the first runs out?
That's an infinite loop.
I remembered the time we went to defeat some slimes.
Well, guess I'll wait until they give up.
You keep slipping!
This'll keep going for a while.
Here I go!
There!
I won't let you!
I've got it!
There!
No way...
We did it!
Hide them with sand! With sand!
M-M-Master Touya! Help us!
Please don't call him!
We're lucky Touya wasn't here.
He really doesn't seem to be around.
Mistress Leen isn't around, either.
They said they were going to investigate the ruins,
so perhaps they both went diving under the sea.
I hope that's all it is.
I-It's spinning... The world is spinning...
P-Please, no more.
I've had enough of falling!
Oh, sorry.
Guess I went overboard.
I can see why White Emperor
acknowledged you as her master.
Mochizuki Touya, you are worthy of being our master.
Please, forge a pact with us.
Uh, if I recall, I need to give you
names like I did for Kohaku, right?
Yes. Please give us wonderful names.
Then how about Kokuyou and Sango?
Kokuyou?
Sango?
How about it?
I'll gladly accept the name Kokuyou.
Then I, too, shall accept,
and call myself Sango from this day forth.
As you see fit.
Hold it.
You'll cause trouble for Master if you stay in that form.
Change it.
Really?
Do we need to make ourselves smaller,
like White Emperor— I mean, Kohaku?
In that case, we can quickly... right!
You can float in the air?
At this size, we can manage it.
We can't move very fast, though.
Glad to have you, Sango, Kokuyou.
I, Sango, will prove myself to be useful.
I'll be helpful, too!
So we need to make sure you can breathe
when you enter the ocean?
Yeah. Can you do that?
That's easy.
Then let's do it at once...
or so I'd like to say, but let's save it for later.
Why?
I want to enjoy the ocean for now.
True.
If I keep you to myself too much,
I'll earn everyone's envy.
Everyone's?
Stare...
Go on and see them.
Well, Master, we'll go kill time in the meanwhile.
Okay, thanks.
You finally joined us.
Sorry, sorry.
What were you talking about with her?
The ruins.
That's it?
Huh? You don't believe me?
They trust me so little?
Were you blown away by Mistress Leen in her swimsuit?
I told you, that's not it.
Then, Touya, whose swimsuit looks the best?
Huh?
True, I'm super curious about that.
Huh? How did this happen?
Sue's... I guess?
Huh?!
Touya, are you...
I can't believe...
No!
I don't mean it like that!
I'm a normal, healthy guy!
I mean, small girls are, you know... uh...
That's...
Lady Sushie and Mistress Renne!
Touya, you really...
This is too much.
You've got it all wrong!
I just wanted to preserve our memories here!
Memories, huh?
I told you, it's not like that!
That's enough.
I believe you, Touya.
So could you start making it up to us right now?
O-Of course.
I know, let's go swimming! Let's go!
Come on. Let's go, everyone!
I'm coming right now!
Hold up!
So I'm number one!
Way to go, Sue!
I can't decide!
Okay, I guess it's about time to head to the ruins.
I'll go check them out by myself first.
If anything happens, return right away with Gate.
I will. Okay, you two, go for it.
Leave it to us.
Now you'll be fine.
Okay.
Incredible. Not only can I breathe, I can also walk normally.
It's even eliminating buoyancy.
We're able to freely manipulate water.
This is nothing for us.
I see...
Looks like a hall.
Maybe there's something here.
What's this?
Why don't you try passing magic through it?
They lit up.
What's going on?!
Master, where are we?
I don't know.
Who's that?
Nice to meet you.
I am the terminal that controls
this Aerial Garden of Babylon.
My name is Francesca.
Wait, um...
What is it?
Why aren't you...
wearing anything... down below?
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.