We're home!
Welcome home.
I'm back, Laim, Lapis, Cecil.
We've been so lonely with all of you gone!
Thank you for allowing us to return first with Gate.
Otherwise, it would've come out
that you're constantly guarding Yumina.
I bought lots of souvenirs!
Help yourselves!
Thank you very much.
I will cherish these for the rest of my life,
on the pride of my family.
You're making too big a deal out of it.
I'm beat.
Way too many things happened, huh?
Yeah.
I really ought to go easy
on the big adventures for a while.
Guess I'll take a bath.
Huh?
Okay, maybe we're at fault
for forgetting to lock the door, but still!
I wish you'd be a little more careful.
I thought you all were already done...
Did you learn your lesson?
Huh? Oh, yes!
Personally, I'd just prefer you take the proper steps first
before doing something like this.
Have you truly learned your lesson?!
I swear!
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 8
Daily Life, and Onward to Eashen
Modeling!
Master Touya, His Grace, Duke Ortlinde is here to visit.
Good afternoon.
Hey. What's this?
I was thinking of making a few bicycles.
They're very handy as a fast ride.
I... I see.
Did you need something?
No, I just wanted to thank you
for the recent matter with Mismede.
By the way, how long does it take
to make these "bicycle" things?
Well, it's my first time making one, so...
about thirty minutes?
I see...
Are you all right?!
Don't interfere!
This is my mount!
Uh, no, it's mine...
I will figure out how to ride this thing on my own!
Uncle?!
What's that?
A vehicle?
How strange...
Ow... This is harder than I expected.
Now it's my turn!
Face straight forward.
Okay!
Safe.
How am I doing, Touya?
I can ride around the garden now!
You're a quick learner, Yumina.
Look at me, Touya!
I'm this good at it now, too!
Sorry, let me ride it a bit longer.
Hey!
Big Sis!
This is surprisingly easy to ride!
Way to go, Elze.
You really are good at things like this.
I guess so.
I can do it, too!
They both got really good all of a sudden.
I'm not sure if I should say it's
thanks to you, or it's your fault.
Huh?
So that's what's going on!
Mistress Elze, Mistress Linze,
hurry up and let me ride it, too!
It seems I'm in first now!
He's carrying on more than anyone.
Ow... Sorry! Are you okay?
Yeah, and you, Big Sis?
Somehow.
Could you make one more?
A small one, for Sushie!
I'll pay for all the material costs, of course!
Okay, I'll head out to buy them now, then.
But I wanted you to see my skills, too...
I'm number one!
Wait up!
Sue definitely got her personality from her father.
Come this way!
You damn brat!
Caught you working our turf again, you bastard!
Thanks to you, the guards are cracking down!
Stop! I'll apologize for pickpocketing!
Too late for that now.
That's enough.
Who the hell are you?
Butt out, buddy.
If you're planning to gang up and harm a child,
of course I'm going to stop you.
Judging from your conversation,
you're pickpockets too, right?
So what if we are?
No reason. It just means I won't hesitate to shoot.
Though they're rubber bullets.
You all right?
Later, then.
H-Hey!
Thank you for rescuing me.
If you feel that way, then stop pickpocketing.
You might get caught next... time...
Are you hungry?
I haven't eaten in three days.
Come with me. I'll buy you something to eat.
Really?!
You're a girl?
Yeah. Call me Renne.
Where do you live, Renne?
No one place.
Some days I sleep in the park, others in a back alley.
And your parents?
My dad left to defeat a magic beast
about a year ago, but he never came home.
My mom died shortly after I was born.
I see.
Renne, would you be interested in working at my place?
Huh?
You wouldn't have to worry about food or a place to live.
But you would have to do proper work.
I'll even pay you for what your work is worth.
How's that sound?
You'll let me work for you? Really?
My condition is that you never pickpocket again.
Can you do that?
Y-Yeah! I promise!
Yeah, it looks good on you.
Y-You think so?
From now on, you'll be a servant of this household.
When guests are present,
be sure to address Master Touya as "Master."
Yes, Laim.
Now, Renne, time for you to learn the job.
Okay.
I'll be back, Master Touya.
Work hard!
Yes!
What a strange child.
Really?
So, Master Touya...
Where are the materials for the bicycle?
I forgot...
So this is Mismede!
It's bustling!
Thank you very much, Touya,
for listening to Sue's selfish request.
Well, it's right next door with Gate, anyway.
I'd love to ride through this town
on the bicycle you made for me.
Don't. You'd stand out.
Touya...
There's Arma.
Huh?
Arma!
Touya!
Hey, what a coincidence.
Yes. I didn't know you two were in Mismede!
Are you out shopping, too?
Yes. You as well, then?
Yes.
Sue, this is Arma.
This is Sushie.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, a pleasure to meet you, too.
What's the matter, Touya?
Just... that.
Big Sis?
Is she out on a date?
Probably.
We should follow her!
Huh? You're tailing her?!
Sounds fun! I'm going, too!
Sue! Jeez...
So, apparently, there was a tortoise and a hare...
Do you know why?
Yes, I do.
How innocent.
What is he doing?
He wants to hold her hand,
but he's not sure if that would be a good idea.
He should just hold her hand if he wants to.
Indeed. Why won't men just take our hands?
Right, Touya?
Well, because it's embarrassing...
They're going into that store!
So they liked bananas.
Wow.
We'll expose ourselves if we go in, too.
Touya, can't you do something?
There is something I could do,
but taking this peeping any further would be, well...
This may be a huge event in my sister's life!
As her little sister, I feel I need to know what happens.
Long Sense.
So you'll be returning to Belfast in a few days, Sir Lyon?
B-But after this, there will be good ties between
Belfast and Mismede, so I'll have more chances to come visit!
SLO-MO                  VIDEO                  PHOTO                 SQUARE                    PANO
Please tell me when you do.
Big Sis seems happy.
I think there's a rather strong chance here, don't you?
How nice!
I'd love to try going on a date, too!
You're too young yet, Sue.
Even I haven't been out on a proper date yet.
Then you and I should go on a date together, Yumina!
That wouldn't be a date.
Then what if Touya were with us?
Heavy...
Whoops.
Sorry. Are you hurt?
I'm sorry. I was in a hurry.
Arma, are you all right?
That's... Olga and the young knight from Belfast, huh?
I see. So that's what this is about.
Exactly.
Anyway, what brings you to a place like this?
Visiting the castle town
to clear my mind is a hobby of mine.
Your ministers will be furious again.
And then the flowers bloomed.
How pathetic.
When I was young, men were bolder!
Watch it!
What are you doing?!
Stop!
Who are you?!
Let him go.
Aren't you ashamed of yourselves,
ganging up on one person?
So gallant!
Hard to believe he's the same hesitant man from before.
You bastard!
Get him!
Oh, no!
Let's go!
But if we go out there...
Wh-Who are you?!
Someone helping this young man here.
Do you think we went a bit too far?
No, it's fine.
Um, Mister Touya, right?
Huh?
No one but Mister Touya wears a coat like that,
and your voice matches his.
Shoot.
Lyon! Are you all right?!
Beast King?!
Gulp!
Accel!
Not fair!
Time for me to Acc—
Would you mind staying and chatting?
It's your fault for not being clear, Lyon!
Your feelings for Olga aren't even serious, are they?
That's not true at all!
I am serious!
So you earnestly want to date her, then?
Of course!
So, you heard him.
Th-Thank you...
for choosing me.
Then you'll go out with...
Yes.
Yahoo!
Congratulations, Big Sis!
A-Arma? What are you doing here?
We did it!
That's great!
Mister Touya, what's going on here?
By the way, how old are you, Mistress Olga?
I'm home.
We've returned.
Welcome home.
You have a guest, Master Touya.
A guest?
Paula?!
Did you walk here from Mismede all by yourself?
Of course she didn't.
She came here with me.
Leen? What are you doing here?
And Charlotte, too?
I'm researching some things.
I led her here.
Touya, who is this woman?
Oh, I guess this is your first time meeting her.
This is the elder of the fairy
folk in Mismede. Her name's Leen.
Despite how she looks, she's far older than the rest of us.
Fairy folk? But...
Oh, I'm using Light magic to render my wings invisible.
In this country, they'd stand out too much.
My, is that so?
But what brings you here?
I heard something in the palace
that I wanted to ask you about.
It's about the crystal magic beast
that you defeated a few months ago.
Huh?
Hey, who's that girl?
One of the fairy folk, apparently.
That haughty woman?
I thought the fairy folk were cuter.
Ahem!
So, will you tell us more?
A runner came from Lairesse,
a village in western Mismede.
They said they discovered
an odd crack in the sky several days ago.
A crack?
It intrigued me, so I visited the village
with a platoon of soldiers.
However...
So when I did some research into that monster,
I learned that you all defeated one, which surprised me.
Plus, I heard from Charlotte.
She says you can use all Null Magic?
You blabbed?!
Sorry!
I can't go against my teacher!
Teacher?
How fortunate she is to be my apprentice.
If she hides things from me,
a simple punishment solves things.
Yes, I'm fortunate.
By the way, this is the magic beast.
Apparently, it appeared from the crack in the sky.
It's shaped differently than the one we fought.
What are these things?
I've heard legends that, long ago,
demons called "Fraze" nearly destroyed the world.
It's said that those demons had translucent bodies.
You think these crystal monsters are Fraze?
That I don't know.
Well, thinking about it by ourselves won't get us anywhere.
Indeed.
By the way, I'll be staying here
in this nation as Mismede's ambassador.
I'll be visiting often, so be ready.
Also, Touya, I hear you can use Gate?
Yeah. Though the hard part is
that I can only jump to places I've been before.
There's a Null Magic spell called "Recall."
It's a spell to read the thoughts of others.
Using it with Gate should allow you
to jump to places in the memories you read.
Wow, that's convenient.
There's somewhere I'd like you
to take me using that spell and Gate.
Where do you want me to take you?
Far east, as east as one can go. To Eashen.
Eashen?
I'd like to investigate
the ancient ruins said to be in that nation.
Are these ruins related to the Fraze?
No, not at all.
I'm simply interested in them.
That's why?!
Master Leen is a self-serving
fairy who follows her curiosity.
Sorry, I'm joking!
By the way, you're from Eashen, aren't you?
If you read her mind, you should be able to go to Eashen.
Hey, wait a moment!
"Read her mind?" You mean my mind?!
Don't worry.
Recall can't let one read memories you don't want seen.
S-Still...
Recall requires the caster to touch the target to activate.
I hear the best form of contact for it is a kiss.
A k-kiss?!
I'm joking.
Yes, yes, come here and face each other.
Then hold hands.
Yes, now press your foreheads together.
Yae, picture the sights of Eashen.
Touya, the chant.
Recall.
I can see it.
I'd like you to open up a Gate. Would you mind?
I-I know, I know!
Oh, I have work left to do in the royal palace, so...
I see. Good work.
She ran away.
Gate.
It's exactly the spot I saw.
Is this...
I'm certain.
This is my homeland, Eashen.
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.