Why are you all looking so upset?
It's our first mission since Kohaku joined us.
I'm excited.
I can't get motivated for this mission.
I can't believe the magic beasts they want us
to investigate are slimes!
And they want us to investigate
a slime researcher's castle, no less.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Do you hate them that much? They're only slimes.
I just inherently dislike them.
Especially the green slimes that melt clothes.
You too, Yumina?
I know having your clothes melted is wonderf—
I mean, humiliating, but...
They haven't been seen in over ten years, right?
I feel like it wouldn't be
that big a deal to leave them be, then.
They're not harming the nearby villages...
You'd leave the villagers to spend their days in fear?!
Can we call ourselves proper adventurers with that attitude?
No, we can't!
That is true, but...
If slimes were to attack any of the neighboring villages,
we'd all regret it, wouldn't we?
Touya, you aren't thinking
about anything improper, are you?
No way!
Jeez, Yumina, I'd never think about anything like that...
...much.
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Stop te wo kazashita dake ja
Stop! Merely raising your hands
Stop
Life nanimo kawaranai
to the sky will not change your Life.
Life
Shine hikari no sasu basho he
Shine! Cast your gaze toward
Shine
manazashi wo uchikonde
where the light shines.
hito wa daremo ga minna
Everybody lives
tabibito no you ni ikiru
as a traveler,
chikai wo
Carve out
chi
ka
i
wo
(chikai wo)
(carve out)
(chi
ka
i
wo)
kizande
new vows
ki
zan
de
(kizande)
(new vows)
(ki
zan
de)
hate nai sora he to hanate
And release them to the limitless sky!
sono te de tsukame
Grasp it with those hands!
sono te de tsunage
Connect it with those hands!
sono sekai wa semasugiru kara
That world is too small as is.
sono ashi de yuke
Keep going with those legs!
sono mimi de kike
Listen with those ears!
sono riaru wa tsukurimono deshou?
That reality is just an imitation, right?
shou?
kono te de tsukame
Grasp it with these hands!
kono te de tsunage
Connect it with these hands!
kono mirai wo uketsuideikun da
We will go on to inherit this future!
ima wo hikikae ni shite
Giving our present time in exchange,
Carry on Carry on
Carry on, carry on.
ii ka iku zo Fly High
Are you ready? Let's go, fly high!
High
Chapter 5
Slime Castle, and a New Function
It's a little creepy in here, but it's safe.
Come on, everyone else i—
Master Touya?!
Ow...
It wasn't safe at all!
No, I'm fine. It just hurt a little.
Touya, the washbasin!
A slime?
But it's a slime I've never seen or heard of before.
Does that mean this is a newly created one?
What use would that be?
His research documents might be hidden
somewhere in here, so let's look.
There's only the leather cover.
The contents must have been eaten by slimes.
Maybe it wound up food for a green slime?
This one wasn't eaten.
A notebook?
Looks like a record of research results.
The properties of many different slimes are written here.
Let's take that notebook with us.
It might prove useful somehow.
We've finished searching the first floor,
so let's return to the hall and head up to the second.
I want to go home already.
He's definitely plotting something.
Um, Touya...
What are those?!
Green slimes!
Come forth, Fire!
Hail of Red Stones: Igni—
Linze, stop!
You might burn down the whole building!
Let's burn it down!
Kohaku!
Leave it to me.
And here we go!
Oh, no! They're coming closer!
Second floor! Evacuate to the second floor!
What's the meaning of this?
Maybe they've established a territory or something.
Anyway, we're safe.
Let's hurry up to the second floor.
I can't wait to leave those things behind—
Ow!
Hey, what is this?!
It's slimy!
Over there!
What kind of slime is that?
I'll look it up.
"Lotion slime."
"When it senses danger,
its body secretes a lubricating fluid."
"Harmless to humans."
"Failed creation."
That's a failed creation?
Are you sure he's not failing on purpose?
Sorry!
H-Hey!
You saved me.
Thanks, Kohaku.
It's nothing, though your wife and—
Jeez, what is this?!
T-Touya!
No... Help me!
Hold on, I'll save you!
Gate!
Those things really do have their individual territories.
Is everyone all... right?
And this was my favorite outfit...
How awful.
It melted more than half of my skirt!
M-My bindings got melted, too.
Th-This is a bit of a problem for me...
Thanks to this slimy stuff,
you can see right through my underwear, too!
I've had enough!
Don't look at me!
Hey! I can't help it!
Good job!
Next time we see a green slime,
we're making sure we crush it!
It seems like he was trying
to create some kind of special slime,
and mass-produced failures in the process.
Right.
He wouldn't know the special trait
of a slime until it was created.
We should just burn the whole castle down.
Purify it. We should purify it!
While I do agree with that,
should we really do such a thing on our own authority?
The fortress has already been abandoned.
I doubt my father would complain.
This is getting into risky territory.
What is all this?
Well, I wouldn't know...
What is it?
Well, it looked like their chests moved just now.
Huh?!
What are you saying?
Honestly, men are so...
No, it's true!
It's soft...
"Bust slimes."
"They attach to women's chests and mimic them."
"Their preference is to attach to
and accentuate smaller breasts."
"A step closer, but a failed creation."
Closer to what?!
Shred, Wind!
A Thousand Blades Born of the Gale: Cyclone Edge!
I'm still growing...
Huh?
I'm still growing.
Y-Yeah, of course.
Okay, looks like we'll be safe here.
Was this the slime researcher living here?
Probably.
Let's see... "It's complete."
"Now my... no, the dream of all men has come true."
"I have nothing left to regret."
"Ah, I can see Heaven."
What the heck?
Touya, there!
It's changing shape into something!
Huh?!
Hey, what are you looking at, Touya?!
No, no! Don't!
M-Master Touya! Look away!
Don't look!
Purify.
Purify it.
Must purify.
Purify it for sure.
So the "men's dream" that researcher wrote of
was to enjoy the servitude of a harem of beautiful, naked women.
How dumb.
Well, that was kind of awful.
Master.
Next, I'd like to observe a human town.
Why not?
But before that...
Slime researcher...
Thank you.
So cute!
It's quite lively.
This is the center of this town.
Master, isn't that Mistress Yae over there?
Huh?
Yae, who's the kid?
Master Touya.
It seems she has gotten lost.
Mommy!
I've been asking for her name,
but I can’t get an answer out of her.
What is your name?
Lim.
I see. Lim, you say?
Search: Lim's family.
Any luck?
No. At least, they're not within Search's radius.
Enchant, Search.
Search: Lim's mother
@-_/        ABC       DEF
GHI         JKL       MNO
PQRS       TUV      WXYZ
SPACE
ENTER
@-_/        ABC       DEF
GHI         JKL       MNO
PQRS       TUV      WXYZ
'":;
SPACE
ENTER
@-_/        ABC       DEF
GHI         JKL       MNO
PQRS       TUV      WXYZ
'":;
SPACE
ENTER
@-_/        ABC       DEF
GHI         JKL       MNO
PQRS       TUV      WXYZ
'":;
SPACE
ENTER
@-_/        ABC       DEF
GHI         JKL       MNO
PQRS       TUV      WXYZ
'":;
SPACE
ENTER
Yes! It worked!
Ready to go see your mom?
Mommy!
Lim!
So, Master Touya...
What did you use your smartphone to do this time?
You can use Search to look for various things,
but its range is small, right?
This can find what you're looking for over a wide range,
but it can only search by
building names and such.
Oh-ho!
So you used your Enchant spell to combine
the better aspects of Search and your smartphone!
Exactly.
With that combination,
I can search for anything in the world.
Wow! That's incredib—
I-In that case, I would like you to search for my brother!
Your brother?
So, why do you want to search for your brother?
I haven't seen my brother since I left on my journey,
so I've been worried about him the whole time.
Then first, tell me more about your home.
Very well.
There's a shrine nearby,
and there's a big cherry blossom tree in our garden.
In Hashiba?
Yes, that's it! And my brother?
Hang on a sec.
What characteristics does he have?
He has a scar on his cheek.
He's in the dojo.
He's moving around, so maybe he's in a match?
That certainly sounds like my brother.
He really loves the sword,
so much that he often forgot to eat.
You must love your brother, huh?
Yes, I do.
He's strong, kind, and generous,
and I love him a great deal.
Speaking of which, you and my
brother are somewhat alike.
Like your quiet nature, and your generosity.
It's an honor to hear that I resemble your beloved brother.
Yes, indeed, my beloved...
I-I-I j-j-just meant to say that
you resemble my brother,
not that I love you as well or anything!
Just, I mean, you kind of, sort of,
slightly resemble my brother...
Here's your order.
Master Touya, i-it's here!
Let's eat!
I can taste the salt!
Yae? Yae...
Our food budget...
Enchant: Long Sense.
Search:
Messages
Maps
Albums
Camera
Settings
Contacts
Compass
Camera
This worked, too.
L-Linze is...
There.
Touya, do you have a moment?
Y-Yes!
Wh-Wh-What is it?!
Is something the matter?
No, nothing!
M-More importantly, what do you need?
I went to the antique shop today to learn a new spell.
Why's that?
I couldn't use my Fire magic
the other day in the slime castle,
since it was indoors.
So I wanted to take this chance to learn various spells.
Oh, that makes sense.
And I found this there.
Cutter... Sword... Storm...
What's this?
A spell scroll.
But some characters are in ancient magic script,
so I can only read part of it.
Then...
Modeling.
Enchant: Reading Ancient Magic Script.
Touya, what's that?
You should be able to read it now.
Oh, incredible. I really can read it.
So what does it say?
Bubble Bomb... An attack spell.
Touya, I'd like to try it out at once.
Would you come with me?
Come forth, Water!
Ballistic Bubbles: Bubble Bomb!
Yes!
Good!
I'll try it one more time!
Linze! Are you all right?
I-I'm all right.
I'm just out of mana.
Come forth, Water!
Ballistic Bubbles: Bubble Bomb!
Wh-What is it?!
Transfer.
My mana is... recovering?
It can't be... In an instant?
My, you did?
I had her teach me yesterday.
You, the one who can use every affinity?
It's "Transfer," a Null Magic
that allows you to pass your mana to another.
Leave it to me!
The archmage Charlotte will give you thorough instruction!
Thank you very much!
All right!
Come forth, Water!
Ballistic Bubbles: Bubble Bomb!
It really is difficult.
I just can't seem to grasp the concept of this spell.
I see...
If only I could visualize exactly
what "Bubble Bomb" means...
What?
Huh?
What "Bubble Bomb" means?
There's meaning in the unique name of each spell.
You have to visualize that meaning
when you chant the spell.
Oh, in that case, "Bubble" is like the foam in liquids,
and "Bomb" is an explosive.
Explosive?
Uh, it means something that explodes.
In other words, something like an exploding bubble.
An exploding bubble?
I can't visualize that at all.
Why don't you try imagining a soap bubble?
That's probably the closest to it, I think.
A soap bubble...
Come forth, Water!
Ballistic Bubbles: Bubble Bomb!
I did it...
Thanks to you, I managed to perfect it.
Thank you very much.
No, it was your own effort bearing fruit.
I only helped out a little bit.
I'm stuck...
What do I do?
It's so hard.
I'll handle this.
Come forth, Water!
Ballistic Bubbles: Bubble Bomb!
I'll have to buy a replacement.
I think you should.
Even if you repair it, it might just break again.
Then, Touya, take me to the royal capital.
I'm not likely to find a good replacement in this town.
Thank you very much!
We look forward to seeing you again.
This sure is the royal capital.
There's a lot of good stuff here.
Though it's more expensive, too.
This gauntlet's surprisingly heavy.
Elze, let's head into that alley and use Gate to...
Huh?
You want that?
Huh?! Oh, T-Touya...
Um, th-this is, uh...
Yes, for Linze! I thought it'd look good on Linze!
She seems like she'd enjoy clothes like this, right?
Unlike me.
But if it looks good on Linze,
I think it'd look good on you, too.
What are you saying?
There's no comparison between me and Linze!
Really? You're both cute.
C-Cute?!
Yeah.
Y-You don't need to flatter me.
I understand myself best of all.
I'm not the type of girl
who looks good in things like that.
Then try it on and we'll know.
Let's see if you can try it on!
Huh? Hey... Touya!
Ker-zing!
Ba-bump...
See? It doesn't look good on me, right?
I told you so.
Huh? What are you saying?
It looks great on you!
Y-You think so?
Could we get this outfit?
Yes.
H-Hey, Touya!
I'm not buying this!
No, I'm buying it.
As a present for you.
Oh, Big Sis...
Is it strange?
It looks very good on you!
It looks cute, Mistress Elze!
Yes, you look lovely.
R-Really?
Touya bought it for me.
Wow! Let's have him buy some for all of us!
Huh?
I like that idea!
Me, too.
When shall we go shopping?
Huh?!
Yumina, you have a letter from the royal palace.
The royal palace?
Touya, they'd like us to come to the royal palace.
Why's that?
They want to grant you knighthood as a reward
for solving the incident the other day.
Knighthood?!
Is that something I can decline?
Decline?!
Yes, that's possible.
But you would need to state your reason
for doing so in a public venue.
So I have to go either way...
I get to return home with Touya a little early.
harisakesou kikoechau
My pounding heart is ready to burst.
kodo no oto ga
As I listen to it,
dare yori mo dare yori mo
More than anyone, more than anyone,
kimi no mae ja kawaiku itai kara
I want to be attractive in front of you.
masa ni Dangerous
Just dangerous.
Dangerous
sono egao mujaki sugiru ne
That smile is just too innocent.
sono egao
That smile
kakusenai yo mitame yori
Your appearance can't hide it.
uso ga heta na no
Are you a bad liar?
sowasowa
I am anxious...
fuwafuwa
and light-headed.
chotto matte junbi undouchuu
Just a moment. I am warming up.
hajimete wa donna aji
What is the first time like?
tashikamete hoshii yo
I want to know!
Kiss Me!
moshi kamisama ga iru no nara
If God exists,
kono kimochi ga todoku no nara
If these feelings reach you,
kirakira no mahou wo kakeru yo
I will cast a sparkling spell that
kotaete junjou Emotions aru
Responds to my pure emotions.
daitan na koe ga tsuyogaru no
Acting tough with a daring voice,
me no mae no kimi ni todokechaun da
I want to confess in front of you.
gikochinai mama de
Stay awkward.
sugu ni tsutaetai yo
I will tell you soon.