Even if the world doesn't need me,
I'll keep living for someone who does.
That's all I need.
But my custody rights might've been
at risk for a while there!
"Custody"?
After that, things were a little hectic
with the move and everything,
but I think keeping busy
helped me to bounce back.
How could I not, with Tohru there for me?
Uh-huh...
Seriously, Tohru is so cute!
Like, the cutest in the world—no, the universe!
But Katsuya Honda...
You don't want to go see him anymore?
I wonder how much time and effort it'll take
for you kids to find your own answers...
Her words sounded ridiculous
to me back then.
Because I'd always felt like I was
born to be an object of contempt,
and that I continued living
only to hurt other people.
Kyo-kun.
Kyo-kun!
Are you crying?
Kyo, why are you crying?
Don't tell me that
you're in love with Tohru Honda?
You're wrong.
I can't afford to love her.
Never.
Kyo-kun, this is Tohru Honda.
What is she doing here?
I know her.
Yes.
I knew it from the beginning.
Who you were.
And who your mom was.
A long time ago.
When my master had just taken me in.
What's your deal?
You're too young to dye your hair orange!
Is that natural or what?
Wh-What's your deal?!
Mind your own business!
Don't even talk to me! I'll kill you!
Whoa, what a little punk you are!
How cute!
Who are you callin' cute, you old hag?!
Man, the mouth on this kid! Adorable!
You're gonna get kidnapped
if you don't stop bein' so cute.
Better go home.
Your mom will be worried—
I don't have one! She died!
And your dad?
I don't need him! Wish he'd die!
After all, he wants me dead too!
I see. That sounds lonely.
Apart from my master,
I didn't think this kind of person existed.
Each day, my mother would look at me
with those scared eyes.
My father detests me.
The entire Soma family despises me.
After living in such denial,
she appeared to me like a small ray of hope.
I wondered about things like
what kind of person Tohru was.
Today, I wanted to show you something.
This is my treasure,
Tohru.
From the very beginning,
I knew her.
But I didn't say a thing.
I acted as if I didn't know anything.
I couldn't tell you about it.
Because...
It's not your fault, Kyo.
You did nothing wrong.
But you can't go outside.
There are bad things waiting outside.
Stay in the house with Mom, okay?
Let's live inside forever.
Do what your mother tells you, or else...
I'll never forgive you.
I'll go in the house and wait for you.
You'd better get inside now,
or else something even scarier will happen.
Kyo-kun—
I don't want to see it.
I don't want to think about it.
Not yet...
And since then...
This memory of when I saw your mother dying.
I chose to hide it inside of my heart.
Hanajima.
Can you... uh... see ghosts and stuff?
Why the sudden inquiry?
No reason, just wondering.
Ultimately, living humans are the strongest.
That goes for waves, as well.
The waves of the dead are most likely very weak,
so those waves are drowned out by the stronger
thoughts of living humans around them.
As they are now.
Right now, your waves are screaming.
Why do you feel such regret in this graveyard?
I'm sorry.
No one will forgive me.
No one will ever forgive me.
Then...
Then why...
Why...
Am I still looking for her?
Tohru!
Huh? K-Kyo-kun?
What happened? You're back so soon.
After high school, you'll be locked away.
Just like the previous Cat before you,
until the day you die.
I won't wish
for her to be mine anymore.
I have no hope left.
I swear to myself.
So I beg you,
let me...
let me be by her side
for the time that's left.
Until the very last day,
the very last moment.
Well then, what do you want?
Will you ever admit the truth?
Or do you intend to keep deceiving yourself
for the rest of your life?
Will you stay on this path?
Locked in your castle all alone...
until the day you die?
I... I don't want that!
I... don't...
She... doesn't... want that?
I'll never forgive you.
Ta-da! This is... Tohru!
Thank you!
Are those shapes going to grill okay?
Not to worry! You can leave it to me!
Kyo! The food's almost ready!
Kyo?
Could he be asleep?
He'll show up eventually.
They showed up in my dream
to stamp out those thoughts.
To remind me...
"Know your place. Don't fool yourself."
Because I thought maybe...
just maybe...
Tohru loved me back.
Who the hell was I kidding?
Kyo-kun!
Please, there's...
something I'd like to tell you.
Kyo-ku—
Me too.
There's something I've been
wanting to ask you for a while.
If I've got the wrong idea,
go ahead and laugh.
Make fun of me as much as you want.
Do you...
Do you... love me?
Are you stupid?
I thought you loved your mom best.
Was that a lie? Is that all just...
gone now?
I can't do this.
I shouldn't have been around her.
Why did I ever wish for this?
Being close to her in the time I had left...
If only I'd known
it would turn out like this.
Kyo-kun!
I don't want to say it.
I don't want her to know.
I don't want to admit it.
But... this just isn't fair.
Please listen! I—
You don't know anything!
You don't know what I did!
I pity you for loving me.
I'm so, so sorry for you.
I'm sorry.
She could've lived. If I'd helped.
Your mom didn't have to die.
I... knew your mom.
That day...
The day of the accident,
I was standing right there,
and I recognized her right away.
Her profile... the color of her hair...
They were the same as when we first met.
I was trying to decide whether to speak to her,
when I saw a car speeding toward us...
I thought, "Oh, shit, I have to help her."
If I grabbed her arm
and pulled her back against me...
But... But I'm not human.
If I caught her in my arms, I'd turn into a cat...
and everyone would find out what I am.
So I let her die.
Everything is my fault.
She said she'd never forgive me.
She was lying in a pool of blood,
and she noticed me standing there and said,
"I'll never forgive you."
At least, that's what it sounded like.
I can't forgive myself.
I'll never forgive you.
Your mom was right to say that.
And I don't want you to forgive me either.
Not now.
But at that moment...
I won't.
Is that what you want me to say?
More than that...
My mom... I don't believe she
would really tell you that.
I can't believe it, but...
But if she truly did say that, then... I...
I...
have to go against Mom!
Kyo-kun, isn't there any way
you can accept that I love you,
no matter what?
Half-hidden behind his orange hair,
his eyes were screaming.
I'm... disappointed in you.
"I'm sad. I'm sad. I'm sad."
Kyo?! Stop!
Seeing you like this
hurts me much more
than being separated from my mom.
That's why...
Tohru?
Wait.
Wait. This is wrong.
No, this isn't what I wanted!
Tohru... wait!
This is...
Don't cry.
Tohru?
It's okay.
Don't worry.
It's... all going to be okay.
Never mind. It's all right.
I get it. It's okay, so... no need to talk.
...let me reach you.
Where were you?
Why didn't you come to the hospital?
You're running away?
Say what you want.
Me being there would only hurt her.
I can't protect her.
She's better off with you.
I see. So that's how it is.
This is why I didn't want boys.
Hey, can I order pizza?
You can't protect her?!
What does that even mean?
Should you be able to catch her
before she falls off a cliff?
Or brilliantly save her from getting
hit by a car—would that satisfy you?
That'd sure be impressive.
Who do you think you are,
some kind of superhero?
You're just a stupid cat!
Shut up! When did I ever say any of that?!
I'm sure someone as perfect
as you could pull that off,
but if I could be like you,
I already would be!
I wanted to be like you!
I wanted to be you!
Fine, fight all you want.
I don't care anymore.
Can I get nuggets, too?
Screw you.
Screw you, screw you, screw you!
Screw—
So did I!
I wanted to be like you!
I admired you so much.
And you...
And you just had to go and say it first!
Easily, like it's nothing!
Screw you!
But,
you're only you, and I'm only me.
We can only be ourselves.
We have to accept ourselves,
and... face who we are.
You were protecting her!
You were doing just fine, dumbass!
You made her happy!
Maybe it was just the little things,
and maybe it's not like a hero's super powers,
but you made Honda-san smile
when you were with her!
Do you seriously think I could
do the same thing?
Cut the crap!
Open your eyes and realize
there are things only you can do!
So quit making her cry!
Get your damn act together!
Why are you still sitting there?
The great Yuki you admire so much
just gave you a pep talk.
Dumb cat.
Damn it.
I really hate that guy.
But,
after what I said...
will she still accept me?
And what about me?
Do I still really love her?
What do I love about her?
Why do I love her?
How much do I...
Oh.
None of that matters.
I love her.
I just... love her. Like crazy.
Toh—
My feet aren't listening to me.
They just carried me away from Kyo-kun.
It's strange. This isn't right.
It's not what I planned.
When I saw him again, I had meant...
to smile.
P-Please, wait... just a minute...
Please! One second!
Stop it! Come on, stop crying!
I don't want to upset him.
I don't want him to hate me.
I don't want him to be...
even more disappointed in me.
I was only thinking about myself.
I just confessed my own sins,
said everything I wanted to say,
and I completely ignored your feelings.
And then I ran even though I know
that sometimes in this world,
you never get the chance to see
someone again to apologize.
I know that,
I'm sorry I made you cry.
I'm sorry I hurt you so much.
This is the last time.
I'm fine with that.
I don't need another after this.
Will you give me one last chance?
I want to be with you.
If I'm going to keep living,
I want to do it with you.
You, and no one else.
Because I love you.
D-Does that mean...
you'll let me stay by your side?
I-I can hold your hand, and be with you?
You're already holding it.
Even if it's been said dozens,
hundreds, thousands of times...
Even if the words are a worn-out cliché...
They're still true. This really is...
like a dream.
Kyo-kun.
Just so you know,
that was our second kiss.
Huh?! Wha... Wh-When did...?!
Figures she doesn't remember.
You gotta remember it on your own, okay?
Otherwise, it's like it never happened.
Okay!
Can I... hold you?
I know I'll transform as soon as I do...
and being together means sometimes
you'll suffer because of this weird body of mine—
Kyo-kun.
Haven't you realized?
I...
really love you.
I love you, Kyo-kun.
And this love is totally invincible.
I see.
Then... I guess that makes me invincible too.
Nothing to be afraid of now, huh?
Not as long as I have you!
Hey, you! Is your hair real?
"Hey, you" is pretty rude.
Call me Kyoko. I'm Kyoko Honda.
Huh? Her name's like mine.
How 'bout you? What's your name?
Not telling.
Aha. Guess I'll call you "squirt," then.
Squirt? What's a squirt?
A squirt's a squirt.
But Katsuya Honda...
You don't want to go see him anymore?
I wonder how much time and effort it'll take
for you kids to find your own answers...
Come by again sometime, squirt.
Honda
Family
I've decided that when I graduate,
I want to get away from here.
No, I don't mean that in a weird way.
I'm not trying to run away again.
My whole life, I've avoided people
and tried not to engage with the world.
But things are different now.
I'm a normal human being,
and I can live a normal life with you
and be part of this world.
Honda
Family
That makes me so happy.
So I want to engage more.
I want to test myself...
someplace I've never been before.
With you by my side, if that's okay.
When you leave here, where will you go?
To a dojo run by someone Master knows.
It's a long way from here.
I can train there while I work.
See, when I take over
Master's dojo someday,
I'll have outside experience.
I'm sure I'll be able to use what I learned.
The good and the bad.
I know I sound childish and naive saying this.
It'd mean taking you away
from people who love you.
But I want to find the real me, so—
Yes.
I want you to find the real Kyo too.
I bet Master-san was happy when you
asked him about this, wasn't he?
Hearing you talk about the future,
finally seeing you determined to live...
It makes me happy too.
So of course I'll go with you.
What? Are you sure?! It's really far away!
You won't be able to see your friends
all the time like you can now!
If you need time to think,
and if you don't like the idea, you can say so—
Believe it or not, I'm no pushover when it
comes to what's really important to me.
I'm actually quite stubborn.
Well, I guess maybe you are, but...
That's right. I decide things for myself.
So I'm going to disagree
with you about one thing.
Mom doesn't hold a grudge against you.
Even if she really did say
she'd never forgive you,
she didn't say it out of hatred.
I'm sure.
Honda
Family
I'm absolutely certain.
So that's me, standing my ground.
I'm going with you, Kyo-kun.
Yes, I'll be sad to leave everyone.
But being apart from you
would be so much worse.
I want to be with you—
by your side, always.
I never want us to be separated,
and I don't want to wait.
So please take me with you.
Squirt...
What should I do? Tohru hasn't come home.
I looked for her, but I can't find her.
I can't find her anywhere! She's gone!
Don't worry!
I'll...
I'll find her, I swear!
You wait at home. I'll help her.
I'll protect her for sure!
That's a man's promise!
A man's promise.
Thank you.
I'm taking her with me.
You good with that?
I'll keep my promise.
Hey, squirt!
I'll take a rain check on that promise!
I know I'm really late, but...
I'll protect her for the rest of my life.
So we're good, right?
Right now, even though I hear your voice,
it doesn't sound like you.
You're in a form I've never seen, and it scares me.
But... But from now on, I want to understand.
Just like you listen to me when I'm discouraged,
from now on I want you to share
with me when you are!
I want you to tell me when you're hurting,
or scared, or feeling weak,
and let me worry about you!
Because... Because I want to keep living together.
To eat, study, and worry...
All those things. I want to continue to...
...continue to live life with you!
This is how...
I've always acted like an idiot.
But I realized that
if we don't get lost at least once,
we won't be able
to find the right way.
And this, no matter the era.
It's the same for everybody.
I'm happy
I gave birth to you, Tohru.
Since you're here,
I can smile and be happy everyday.
Then...
I must have been born to meet you!
That'd make me even happier!
It would make me so happy...
See you later, Tohru.
Fruits Basket
Wait, what's this?
Disgusting.
We should call the police.
Don't go any closer.
Come on, let's go...
What d'ya think you're
starin' at, you old hags?
Want a broken nose, huh?
She's so scary!
Her parents haven't raised her at all!
Even before going to middle school,
she was a tough kid.
She hung out with delinquents,
and only did bad things.
Her father didn't care about his family.
Her mother only cared about how she
and her husband looked.
They never went out together.
They rarely ate together.
She had never been hugged as a child.
Get out. You're a disgrace!
There are people in this world who have
a purpose, and people who do not.
You are the latter. Such a disgraceful child.
Dear...
Never step foot in this house again!
Kyoko.
Kyoko-chan, why?
How did you turn out like this?
Do you know how many times your father
has taken his anger out on me, because of you?
Do you even know what all
the neighbors say about us?
Please... Tell me why...
You never should have given birth to me then!
Who...
Who asked you to give birth to me?!
She couldn't trust her parents,
or her friends.
It hurt her.
At night, when she rode her bike,
she felt the urge to burst into laughter
and into tears, simultaneously.
She felt like she could go anywhere.
And in fact, she could go nowhere.
Katsunuma!
What's with that look?
You finally come to school,
but you think you're still too cool.
Call her parents.
In middle school, there were very few days
when she could actually go to class.
Come with me. We need to talk.
So meeting him this very day
was a total coincidence.
STUDENT COUNSELOR'S OFFICE
Sensei!
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
The trouble you cause everyone?
You're even dragging down
our good students with you!
Just shut the hell up!
Did'ya think I'd be afraid of ya?
Huh?
Idiot, cut it out!
L-Listen!
You're staying here
until your parents arrive!
Don't you run away, you moron!
You can't even handle me!
Call my parents?
You can wait, they won't come!
Why...
Are you so frustrated?
Huh?
Who the hell are you?
If you just want to scold me,
piss off, asshole!
I don't want to scold you.
However, I am interested
in what's irritating you.
None of ya' business.
Get lost!
I understand, but I'm curious.
It's everything! Shut the fuck up!
Everything!
Everything pisses me off!
Them...
And you!
Absolutely everything!
Absolutely everyone!
I hate you all!
You treat me like garbage
but you're no better than me.
It's not like you have any value.
You... everyone should just disappear!
People like you should just die!
Die!
Just die!
Get lost, just disappear!
Kill yourselves!
But...
You want people to care about you, right?
You want them to notice you,
to need you,
to listen to you,
and to accept you.
And you want...
to be loved, don't you?
I'm... the same.
How...
did I turn out this way?
Me...
How did you turn out like this?
This is...
what I want to understand the most.
Why...
Why am I...
When did she make a wrong turn?
What was her mistake?
I'm so sad... so lonely...
She just wanted to be someone
who could love, and be loved.
However,
she wasn't able to become this person.
Do you feel sad?
Well, then...
Let's get out of here, together.
W-W-Wait...
By the way,
I am Katsuya Honda.
Nice to meet you.
My first impression was
that he was a weird teacher.
Hey, is this alright?
Is what alright?
You're a teacher...
Isn't this dangerous for you?
Don't worry.
I'm just a not-so-motivated
teacher-in-training.
Huh, you're not a teacher?
She couldn't figure out his politeness.
Was it real, or was he a hypocritic
behind a façade?
She didn't know.
It was the first time they met, and still...
He invited her in a restaurant.
It was very unusual for her.
Why...
are you bothering with me?
Well...
Why do you think I am?
I interested you?
You could say that,
No-Eyebrows-san.
D-Don't touch me so casually!
Of course, my apologies.
Here we go.
That day, the one thing
she was certain about
was that the ramen was delicious.
On the inside, she was suffering,
but the ramen they ate together...
was really delicious.
The other teachers...
Did they tell you off after that?
You did take me out of school...
Eh? Not really.
I just said you were sick
and that I sent you home.
Actually,
I still benefit from my father's prestige.
His prestige?
He's retired now,
but my father was a teacher.
He taught in this school for many years.
Apparently he was a great teacher.
As his son,
people are very careful around me.
They all think that I'm going to
be a great teacher too.
That doesn't sound great...
I don't like it...
but sometimes it's not so bad.
If I do things properly,
the reputation will come in useful.
When I bend some rules now and then,
I'll probably be able to get away with it.
Maybe you're not such a great guy after all...
Thank you.
That's not a compliment!
Well, I've got to go
give my afternoon classes.
Are you skipping class?
Obviously.
I'd like you to see me
giving my class, just once,
No-Eyebrows-san.
I have some now!
I drew them with eyeliner!
You should have noticed!
I did notice.
You are beautiful with eyebrows,
No-Eyebrows-san.
Like I said, I do have eyebrows!
So stop calling me that!
Despite how he looked,
he had a strong character,
but at the same time could be so cold.
However...
This isn't good, he's making me so confused.
He's only playing with me.
But she was charmed.
Since that day, she's started
going to school more often.
But she wouldn't go to class.
Because they could meet at lunch.
How's the training going?
The students like you?
Everything's fine.
Getting people to like me is my specialty.
What a load of crap!
You're great at deceiving people!
Thank you.
That's not a compliment!
No more fights with your classmates,
okay No-Eyebrows-san?
I know!
She would wait eagerly for lunch.
Katsunuma!
Why didn't you attend yesterday's meeting?
Don't you wanna fight anymore?
Next time you don't show up,
the bosses won't just let it slide.
I wonder if Sensei's asleep right now.
I come in everyday with my drawn on eyebrows...
what must he think of me?
Why does he come to see me?
Does he... have a girlfriend?
Hey, what are you doing right now?
Honda-sensei, these glasses are fake!
Why do you wear lensless glasses?
I think it makes me seem more like
a teacher, don't you think?
Huh, no way!
You're so weird!
Tomorrow,
my internship ends.
I'll have to leave this school.
I... I see.
So, you're going to become a teacher?
I'm not.
I wanted to live up to my father's
expectations by interning as a teacher.
However, I do admit I was curious
about playing the role of a teacher.
But in the end, I now know this profession
isn't suited for me.
Plus I am a rather eccentric person.
You admitted it!
I can't change that side of me.
My father was very strict.
Very firm about etiquette and so on.
So I learned how to fit in,
to please him and his peers.
I was never the real me,
I just blended in.
People were kind to me.
Do you hate... your dad?
I'd rather say that he was like a wall.
But...
my mother passed away recently,
and the wall seems to have shrunk.
Things changed between us.
This man... is lonely.
His current self is lonely.
Otherwise, he wouldn't be telling me this.
A dull conversation, isn't it?
Huh? No!
It's not!
It's not at all!
I want to know more.
I want to know more about him.
But...
I won't see him anymore.
Thanks for everything...
Sensei.
A-At least on your last day,
I'd have like to see you giving your class.
But...
the classroom is scary.
There's no place for me here.
I don't get along with the other students.
Thinking it could change was...
I-I know I caused you a lot of trouble,
so it's probably despicable
to say goodbye like this.
But it's really a shame.
I wanted to see you...
Now then,
I'm gonna take you wherever you want to go.
Huh?
The sea! It's the sea! The sea!
The sea!
You look like a puppy, No-Eyebrows-san.
But it's the sea! The stupid sea!
Haven't heard it called that before.
Sensei.
Thank you.
You're really kind.
I'm not sure how true that is.
Really?
I think you're very kind.
You cared for me like you would a stray cat.
You didn't reject me or let me down.
Sensei...
I really love you.
I'll...
I'll become a better person.
I'll study a lot, and I'll go to school.
I'll give it my best.
My childhood was a loss.
The way I lived until now was a waste.
Even if I don't get on with people my age...
I want
to be a normal human being,
and live as a normal girl.
I wonder if, right now...
I could confess to him
without being embarrassed?
Thank you.
You're talking like this is goodbye.
But it is.
This... is the end.
Brat.
There are so many more places we can meet.
Do you think that this small place
is all there is in this wide world?
You really are a brat.
Moreover,
it can be difficult... to study alone.
At that moment,
she didn't understand
why she would see him again.
She was very happy,
and very curious at the same time.
Sometime later, Katsuya was employed
by a pharmaceutical company.
I like research,
especially thinking over things.
I hate that stuff.
You say that, but you've
never wanted to try.
Well, your ability to memorize isn't bad.
Keep it up and you should pass the high school admission tests.
Really?
I like your new hairstyle, it's beautiful.
I told you to stop making fun of me,
you're getting on my nerves!
On every weekend, he would help her study.
But one day,
she got her punishment.
If you want ta leave our group,
you'll have ta give us a good reason.
You're really stupid.
Did ya really think you'd live
a normal life?
Before she realized it,
she was laying in a hospital bed.
Policemen and teachers came and went,
but her parents found
excuses not to visit her.
What a waste...
He even helped me study...
I don't have the right
to ever see him again.
And so, she missed the exam, and had one sentence circling around in her head.
A terrible sentence.
"You reap what you sow."
Get out.
You're no longer a part of this family.
Actually,
you're no longer our daughter.
Live if you want. Die if you want.
Never bother us or cause us trouble again.
So this is reaping what I sowed.
Until now I'd always lived as I wanted to.
Now I reap.
So if a child doesn't live up to expectations, their parents can just disown them?
S-Sensei?
So only a perfect child who makes no
mistakes deserves your acknowledgment?
Do you consider yourselves to be so faultless?
Or... are you so irresponsible that you think you can just abandon your child?
Sensei, please, it's okay...
Who are you to interfere
in our family's business?
I don't really want to
be giving my opinion on this subject,
but you are still the parents
of the girl I would like to marry.
Marry? This girl?
You can't be serious!
But I am.
More serious than you anyway.
Are you against us?
Some people have strange tastes.
Do as you wish.
This girl's no longer a part of this family.
Dear!
I'll probably be over in a few days
so you can sign the marriage documents.
Just don't cause any trouble.
Dear!
Get out of here!
Let's go.
I didn't know where you were,
so I was starting to worry.
Sensei...
I called your mother who told me you
were getting discharged today.
Sensei!
I had no idea what'd happened to you.
K-Katsuya!
What you just said...
You're not... serious, right?
I'm serious.
I apologize for the irregular proposal.
I-I'm fine!
Why are you doing so much for me?!
I don't want to be a burden on you!
You can just leave me here...
I'm okay...
Really... I'll be okay!
So...
You don't have to go so far for me!
This is unexpected.
Do you think I said all of that out of pity?
You don't believe me?
But... But...
I just don't understand at all!
I don't understand why you chose me!
You cried...
You cried when you said you were lonely...
You were so human
that... I fell in love with you.
I used to be like you, where I thought
everyone else were just scumbags.
But I've never been able to
cry so honestly, like you did.
Actually, when you were
a high school girl I had to be careful.
But I've never planned on letting you go.
Choose me.
If you still don't trust me,
and if words can make you feel more secure,
I'll repeat it for you as much as you want.
But you have to want me.
Choose me, Kyoko.
Katsuya, are you a pedo?
Where did you learn that word?
It's your fault for not being born earlier.
You're right,
you're definitely not suited
to be a teacher.
Thank you.
That's not a compliment.
No! No way!
It's not happening!
Never, ever, ever!
I also don't really care...
But it is uncommon for a woman to hate weddings this much.
Who'd want to wear something like that!
I don't need this lame ceremony
to be with you!
I get it, I get it.
We got married.
No one congratulated us.
The entire Honda family
opposed this marriage.
Except one man, Katsuya's father.
There is nothing greater than the happiness we feel
when we're with the person we love the most.
However, you are both still young.
You have to accept that people
won't agree with this marriage.
After a while, bit by bit, little by little,
they'll see your relationship's authenticity.
This way, you can prove to people
that you are happy together.
There's no way he's strict!
I was ready to have a fight with him!
I told you it'd go smooth.
Do you want to eat with me?
We can have sushi.
We decided we wanted to live by the sea.
This is unusual, you reading magazines.
Do you want a ring?
No way.
I'd rather have this!
When you come home tired from working,
I'll make you a nutritious juice!
Well, well...
I'll have to get used to weird flavors!
Don't even think o' talkin'
until ya taste it, you jerk!
They would go on lots of holidays together.
It didn't really matter where they went,
as long as they were together.
Huh? Is he already home?
Welcome home,
No-Eyebrows-san.
I'm back!
It's usually the other way around, isn't it?
It's not a bad change.
We treasured each other's life.
You're pregnant?
You went alone to the hospital?
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
I... don't...
have the confidence to have...
a baby.
I'd be happy to have your child.
But...
a child...
is a human being, right?
Am I...
Am I even capable
of giving birth to a human?
I can't say I've lived
a good life until now.
So, giving birth...
and raising a baby, can I even do it?
What if... our child is unhappy, because of me?
What if they're bullied, or hurt, because of me?
If he cried, I...
What if he tells me he never
wanted me for a mother...
Who...
Who asked you to give birth to me?!
Why did I say those things?
Back then, I didn't understand the pain my mother would have felt hearing that.
If my own child said that to me,
I'd want to die.
I said... horrible things.
I've been fine saying to others
things that would hurt myself.
Since you know this child will be
a human being,
it'll be alright.
Because we're human too,
let's remember what made us happy,
and also what made us sad.
We can't forget that.
We'll embrace them.
We'll listen to them.
If they do something wrong,
we'll properly teach them
why those things are bad.
And if... we ever lose control of ourselves
and end up wronging that child,
we'll apologize for that,
and hug them again.
Together.
That's how we'll raise them.
I wasn't alone anymore.
We were together.
I want to have our child,
No-Eyebrows-san.
Me too.
So she was born.
The most precious human in the entire world.
Tohru.
Let's go for a walk, Tohru.
You gave her a bit
of a masculine name, didn't you?
Katsuya says it's "hidden flavor."
"Hidden flavor?"
Like when you add salt to a sweet food,
and a really good taste comes out.
That's the kind of girl
that he wants her to be.
That's another unique one,
both logical and nonsensical.
But it's Katsuya.
But I can understand what he means.
In a way.
So does he help you out with the baby?
Of course!
He's very talented
at getting her into the bath.
You'd be surprised if you saw him!
Katsuya, huh?
When he told me he was getting married,
I was very happy.
He'd never been able to show any affection
or interest in anything.
He wanted to show me he
could actually love someone.
People are mysterious...
As people meet other people,
all sort of possibilities are born,
good ones and bad ones.
I was not a good father.
I suffocated him for so many years.
It can't be helped that he resents me.
However...
He was finally able to be happy,
by meeting you, Kyoko-san.
Thank you, Kyoko-san.
Father, Katsuya doesn't...
Katsuya doesn't hate you!
If he did, he wouldn't visit you like this!
Kyoko.
Ah, yes?
It's getting a bit cold,
did you bring Tohru's coat?
Yeah, it's in my bag. Hold on, I'll—
That's okay, I'll get it.
Calmly, quietly, time slipped by.
From a very young age,
one could easily recognize Tohru.
Ah! Tohru!
What happened?
T-T-Tohru's face, her face!
I'm so, so sorry, Tohru!
Does it hurt? It hurts, right?
I'm so sorry!
B-Blood...
You made the terrifying woman
known as "Crimson Butterfly" faint.
You're really something, Tohru.
After Tohru was born,
the three of them often went out.
When Katsuya held Tohru in his arms,
his face was so gentle, it almost made me cry.
I wanted this overwhelming
happiness... to go on forever.
Your business trip is almost over, isn't it?
Thankfully.
Jeez, you still have a cold?
I told you to go the hospital!
I don't have the time to go.
That's not good! I'm worried!
I'm going to come see you.
It's okay.
If you catch my cold too, it'll be trouble.
I'll go tomorrow.
Is Tohru doing well?
She's good. She's sound asleep right now.
That's good to hear.
Someday, why don't we make
a sibling for Tohru?
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Alright, I'll give you another call
when I'm on my way home.
We'll be waiting.
Get to sleep so you feel better.
And go to the hospital.
Okay. Don't push yourself too hard either.
Sleep well, No-Eyebrows-san.
This must be Daddy, Tohru!
Daddy!
Hello?
Yes.
What?
In the morning, by the time
his coworkers found him, he was already...
His cold had worsened.
He died too soon.
There was so much he hadn't seen.
What was his wife doing?
Neglecting him when he caught a cold.
Probably having fun somewhere.
This is why we were against this marriage.
I bet she was cheating on him.
What will happened to the child?
Poor Katsuya-kun.
He never should have married that girl.
Go on.
Once more.
Blame me.
Just finish me off.
Again...
and again...
Blame me... until I just
can't stand up anymore...
It was so fast.
Katsuya was incinerated,
and turned into smoke and white bones.
It was so fast.
I'm very sorry to disturb you
and make you come out here.
We were going to gather all his belongings
and send them to you,
but we thought Honda-kun would be happier
if it was his own family getting them.
This is the room that Honda-kun was using.
Everything's just as it was before he passed away.
If you need anything,
I'll be in the other room, so please reach out.
He's not here, he's not here anymore...
He isn't anywhere!
He's not here!
Katsuya...
Don't leave me!
Don't leave me alone!
Katsuya.
He isn't here anymore.
I can't see him ever again.
???
Why does the sky turn bright?
??? Zehi ???
??? Couple ???
Why can those people laugh so happily?
??? Hai ??? san ???
??? Haiiii ???
Why does the TV give weather forecasts?
??? Nihon ???
??? Sawa ???
Why?
??? Sore ??? dont have to properly translate this one, can just make shit up and fade away
Why didn't the world end
with Katsuya when he died?
I don't really remember it.
After Katsuya died,
I was empty.
Despair was shining overhead like the sun.
I'll just say this clearly.
Don't you dare think of coming back
to our house with Tohru.
We will not hesitate to turn you away.
Did you call just to tell me that?
Yes.
Dad, you once said
"There are people in this world who have a purpose,
and people who do not," right?
Well, that's a lie.
It's a lie.
This world
needs
no one.
Parents,
teachers,
important people,
adults, and children,
me,
and even Katsuya.
No one is needed for this world to spin.
No matter who dies,
the world won't actually care.
It still continues unabated.
The sun rises and sets.
This world doesn't need anyone's existence.
But, it's very sad
that we feel lonely.
That's why we need other humans...
without a doubt.
Someone who needs us,
and someone that I need,
that I want to meet.
Katsuya.
To me, you were such a special person.
I needed you.
I loved you.
I had finally met the one.
Welcome home.
No matter where I go,
no one will be waiting for me.
Then, let me ask you a question!
The world's third greatest—
...capital held the annual—
You're such a fool—
As we can see from the table,
it's very good for the body!
I can feel it, there's
so much power behind you.
But don't worry! There's nothing to be scared of!
It seems to be your husband, who passed away!
Huh, my husband's here?
Yes, I think he's here to see you.
Your husband has passed?
Yes, he was very ill.
Your husband is always worried about you.
You can't keep on crying on forever!
He will stay by your side to protect you,
and encourage you, so you must stay strong, okay?
I want to see you, too...
I want to meet you.
Where are you?
Where should I go to see you?
How can I follow your footsteps?
No-Eyebrows-san...
Mommy!
Mommy, hurry up!
Hang on, I'm trying to find the tickets.
Ah, here they are! Thank goodness!
Come one, we'll be late for the train!
It's okay, relax!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Now, now, there's no need to rush!
Tohru...
When did I last talk to her?
I can't even remember talking to her
or hearing her voice recently!
What's she been eating?
I've been so consumed
with grief that I forgot about her!
I remember Katsuya's dad
came by a few times.
Tohru!
You're home...
I-I'm...
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm home.
Sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I'm home!
I'm so sorry
for making you wait!
Thank you!
Thank you, Tohru!
I have always,
always,
been stupid.
If we don't get lost at least once,
how can we ever find
the answers to our questions.
Even if the world doesn't need me,
I'll keep living...
I'll keep living for someone who does.
At least, that's all I need.
I wonder how you'll live from now on.
And Tohru...
I wonder how much time and effort it'll take
for you kids to find your own answers...
Please, be happy.
Please, someone...
Someone...
I pray you'll be happy.
I pray you'll be loved by many people.
Live the kind of life you
can be proud of in the end,
even if you get lost
or make mistakes along the way.
Live so that when it's your time to go,
people will say "you fought well."
Have lots of happy times and sad times,
and everything in between.
That's how...
I want you to grow old.
Tomatoes, cabbage,
eggplants and green peppers!
I got so many summer vegetables!
I could cook them for tonight's dinner!
Kyo-kun!
Hey.
You're finally home, Kyo-kun!
Yep, I'm back.
Are you heading home too? Let's go together.
Sure! You're back early today!
That's true.
Heya, stop spinning around.
Welcome back!
Yup, I'm here.
What's in the bag? I'll carry it for you.
It's okay, it's not heavy!
A woman at my work gave me
this before I left.
??? oishii tomato ???
The same happened to me too.
Fish.
Fish!
They gave me that, telling me I worked hard.
???
To them, we're still kids.
No, I don't think that's the case!
It's because we work hard!
I mean it, Kyo-kun!
You're doing your best!
Oh, thank you...
Hey, are you sure—
Trust me!
I already told you I won't give up!
Stubborn as always.
But...
You're doing your best too.
I know it.
Ready to go home?
Yep!
By the way, this is going to be our first summer
together since we moved here, right?
Sure is, time flies.
We'll go back and visit everyone soon.
That's a great idea!
Master-san will be very happy!
You say that, but I call him all the time,
like just yesterday.
We'll also visit your family grave too.
Of course!
If I never met you on this planet
And live today just being plain myself
I would have never known
How to feel precious about the world like this
I jumped over the paddle
The kite floats in the sky above
If I knew the magic to turn
My weakness I secretly hid in my chest
Into a strength to protect you
Then, that's your
Eyes
and
Smile
mi
and
love
Eyes
Eyes and Smile and love
and
Smile
love
na
ka
nai
Rain
Rain
Please don't cry
Rain, so that it won't overflow
Here, look up at the sky
There's a beautiful rainbow
Something good will happen
I'll let your sorrow
Fly away on that kite
My swaying feelings wouldn't stop
cchi
ja
nai
You'll never be...
cchi
Alone
I'll be next to you
That's...
Eyes
and
Smile
mi
and
love
Eyes
Your Eyes and Smile and love please don't cry
and
Smile
love
na
ka
nai
Rain
Rain
Rain, so that it won't overflow
There's a beautiful rainbow
Something good will happen