Why were the metapowers,
so called Quirks,
introduced to the human race in the past?
Why was the first metahuman, the Shining Baby,
born into this world?
It's all a tragedy.
Quirks are not a blessing for humanity,
but the beginning of the end.
As it is written in the
Quirk Doomsday Theory,
as generations pass, Quirks mix and evolve,
until eventually,
no one can control them anymore.
In these times,
where 80% of humanity is sick with Quirks,
the remaining 20% who are still pure humans
will also have relations with Quirk holders,
decreasing their numbers.
Extinction is in front of our eyes.
We, Humarise, must take action now!
Even if it means to dye the Earth in blood.
For humanity's salvation.
For humanity's salvation!
Now, let us begin.
You there.
You don't have a Quirk, right?
Congratulations.
You have been saved.
Otheon
The group claiming responsibility for
the terrorist attack the other day is Humarise.
It's an ideological group founded by Flect Turn,
who advocates for humanity's salvation.
The device used in the attack
has been conjectured to strengthen
the Quirk factor triggering substance, Ideotrigger.
The device will hereafter be called
the Trigger Bomb.
Japan
The mission of our all-star hero team
is to search all 25 Humarise branches
around the world, at once.
Egypt
After restraining their members,
collect the Trigger Bomb held at that
location as soon as possible.
France
We expect the members at their facilities to resist.
There is also the danger that they
will use the Trigger Bomb,
America
so we must refrain from asking for help
from local law enforcement.
I would like you to carry out this mission
promptly and with care.
All Might.
Heroes, the success or failure of this mission rests on your shoulders.
Let's get back the smiles of those who
live in fear of terrorism!
Hero teams,
start the mission!
Team A, we're going to collect
the Trigger Bomb before it can be set off!
Roger!
That's it.
Humarise's Otheon headquarters.
The mission of those of us in Team B is to
gain control of the facility, and capture their leader, Flect.
Don't let your guard down.
Who do you think you're talking to? Huh?!
Stop!
We're not letting you in here!
If you resist, I won't go easy on you!
Clair, look for the Trigger Bomb!
Got it.
Voyance!
I can't believe they're using Quirks here!
Bakugo, most of their members are Quirkless!
Don't be too rough-
I know!
Stun Grenade!
Endeavor, something's strange!
I can't find it anywhere!
What?
Team B, what about Flect?
We'll be through shortly!
Once you've captured him, get him to tell you where the Trigger Bomb is!
Roger!
In that room is Flect Turn.
Damn it!
Their leader is gone! Check the premises!
Humarise France Branch
In the end, even after searching all Humarise
buildings around the world,
we could not find any Trigger Bombs.
Humarise America Branch
Yes, we interrogated the members
we captured,
but no one knows where
the Trigger Bombs are being kept.
In fact, they didn't even know it existed.
Humarise Singapore Branch
It sounds like it's the same for members
from the other branches too.
All-Star World Heroes' Team General HQ
There is a high likelihood that the terrorist attack
was carried out by those under the direct control
of Humarise's leader, Flect Turn.
Director, there might be another facility that
we don't know about.
Did they guess what we would do and move the Trigger Bombs ahead of time?
All teams stand by in your respective countries,
request more heroes, and find Humarise's secret base!
I have to deliver this.
At this rate, the world will be destroyed!
Otheon Airport
Roro, Lala, I need to go to work soon.
Make sure you guys—
We'll study!
And if I don't come home till late?
We'll make food!
And if someone weird tries to talk to you?
We'll definitely ignore them!
Good.
Good!
But I don't think I'll be that late today.
Yay!
Pino!
Okay, I'm off then.
Have a good day!
Old man, you got work for me?
Pickup's on East 3rd Street.
It needs to be delivered to the Chinese restaurant in South Grove.
How much will I get for it?
Hah, like you are in a position to negotiate.
Just do it for the asking fee.
Okay, okay, I get it.
Hey, that's my bike-
It's stolen anyway, right?
I'll give it back to it's owner later!
Don't just do whatever you want, damn kid!
Now, time for work.
It's so lively here.
That's because it's the biggest city in Otheon.
I don't care if we're standing by or whatever,
but why do I have to run errands?!
We're the lowest ranking on our team.
Huh?!
The only reason we're on the World Heroes Team
is because we're doing our work
studies at Endeavor's Agency.
We're like freebies that were
just thrown in.
But since we're on the team,
we need to give our all so we can protect everyone.
The ideological organization, Humarise.
The damn organization that's obsessed
with a damn delusion.
What the hell's with the
Quirk Doomsday Theory?
They're seriously taking a
cock-and-bull story like it's the truth.
It's a jewelry thief!
Catch him!
Damn it, heroes!
See you at the usual place!
I'm leaving the case to you!
You bastards to the right!
Got it!
Move! Move! I said move!
Blackwhip!
Todoroki, the thief!
Leave it to me!
Serves you right!
That was a pathetic blast!
Let me show you a real one!
So late.
It better not have been fake information.
Here.
W-What?
Ha, that doesn't work on me!
That took longer than expected.
Todoroki!
Midoriya, he doesn't have the case!
Did he throw it somewhere?
They're working with someone!
Found him!
Too bad!
He's already over there?!
He's pesky!
Blackwhip!
In that case...
How you doin'?
Thank you!
He couldn't have gotten that far yet!
It's a million years too early
for you to catch me!
Wait!
An accident?!
Midoriya!
I'll take care of that.
Thanks!
I-It's okay.
I'm going to be late!
Crap!
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
What a terrible day.
Aw man, my best clothes are ruined.
It's all that damned hero's fault.
Actually, was there even a hero
like that working around here?
Oh well, it's not like I'll ever see him again.
Why did you come after me?
Why did you run?
I was in a hurry because of work.
What kind of work?
Business discussions.
Despite how I look, I'm a skilled
salesman, you know?
Can you please not get in the
way of my work?
Will you show me what's inside
of that case?
How much will you give me?
Huh?
If you want something, of course you have to pay for it.
I just want to check its contents.
You're not a hero from this country are you?
Is it really okay for you to do hero work in a
foreign country without permission?
W-Well...
You've got no authority here, so can you please
stop giving me orders?
Or should I tell the police that I was chased
and interrogated for no reason?
Maybe I will.
I'm glad you understand.
If you want to do hero work so badly,
you should do it in your own country.
Later.
Wait!
What now?
I just want to see what's in the case.
If you want to see, then pay me.
I will, so show me.
100,000 euros!
That's too much.
Then let go!
Just a peek!
Cut it out!
Huh?
Where's the jewelry?
Good work.
Hey, come over here!
Take a look at this.
What's with all these holes?
These...
I see. Got it.
We will take measures as well.
Please continue tracking.
Thank you very much.
Don't forget, Beros,
the only atonement for those possessed
by the devil of sickness,
is to participate in the salvation of innocent humans.
I understand.
I'm so deeply sorry!
Wow, is this what they call a Japanese dogeza?
Well, I'm just glad you don't
suspect me anymore.
I mean, I'm sure heroes make mistakes
sometimes too, right?
Hey, hey, what's going on?!
This isn't what's supposed to be in it!
Shouldn't it have jewels inside?!
Don't tell me, back then...
I took the wrong case!
A-Anyway, I'm don't have time for this,
so I'll be on my way.
You're sweating a lot.
Are you okay?
Shoot, I have to hurry up
and get back there!
But, will the case even be there?
If someone picked it up and looked
at what was inside,
they would have definitely pocketed it!
I'm dealing with villains here.
"Oops, I lost it" isn't gonna cut it!
What do I do? What am I gonna do?!
Um.
Are you sure you're alright?
Huh?!
I'm fine.
Oh, but—
Police?
Why?!
They're too prepared!
Put your hands up and kneel over there!
I-I...
Please wait a minute! He's—
I didn't steal anything!
Stop!
We have permission to shoot! Fire!
Face forward.
Grit your teeth!
Why would they suddenly fire like that?
I thought I was gonna to die.
They came after us?
Other people might get caught up in this!
They're coming after us!
Shoot—
We need to hurry and get away.
Otheon Team Standby Hotel
You idiots!
We're in the middle of an important
mission right now!
You should leave everything else to the local heroes!
Heroes are supposed to save
those in trouble, right?
We didn't learn to assign importance to jobs during our work study.
You're not even sorry?!
Well, what happened to Deku?
He's following someone who was working
with the jewel thieves.
But he's not picking up his phone at all.
Slackers!
I shouldn't have brought you with me even if you were doing your work studies!
Midoriya
It's from Midoriya.
Midoriya, do you have the
suspect and the case?
We were suddenly attacked by the police!
What did you do?
I don't know!
They didn't say anything before they
started shooting at us.
When we tried to run away,
we were attacked by someone who
looked like a villain, and—
Calm down, tell me what happened in order.
Um, I chased the guy who ran away with
the case and caught him,
but there wasn't any jewelry in the case
he was holding—
Endeavor, this is bad!
Deku...
...any information.
Once again, according to police reports,
the suspect who is thought to have killed 12 people
is the Japanese hero, Deku,
the alias of Izuku Midoriya.
He has been put on the nation-wide wanted list.
There are also reports that he has an accomplice.
Hello? Hello? Todoroki?
Midoriya, what did you really do?
I didn't do anything!
You're on the wanted list as a
mass-murder suspect!
Wh-What do you mean by "wanted list"?
We'll look into that on our end.
You just get away from there immediately.
They'll track you using the GPS.
Once you turn off your phone, don't forget to take out the battery.
That surprised me.
You were able to contact
your friends, right?
Why are you taking out the battery?
When are they coming to get us?
A-About that...
We have an emergency call from
the Otheon team!
Apparently Deku's been put on the wanted list!
Young Midoriya?!
How could that happen?!
Japan Team Standby Hotel
It says he killed 12 civilians in Otheon.
That's ridiculous!
Egypt Team Standby Hotel
But it's intel from HQ.
Wait, wait. There's no way Midoriya could do something like that! Right?!
Yeah, this has to be some kind of mistake.
That's right!
France Team Standby Hotel
I can't believe it.
Deku would... Deku would never do such a thing!
Ribbit!
I'm sure there's something behind this.
Yeah, yeah.
Don't worry, Endeavor and the others
are also acting.
What's going on?!
You're a murderer and I'm your accomplice?!
When did we end up being buddies?
Explain yourself!
I don't know how
it ended up like this either.
Oh, it's all over.
My life was already rock-bottom.
What'll happen if I fall even lower?
This is the worst.
This is all your damn fault!
Do something! You're a hero right?
The police fired without asking any questions,
and we were even attacked by a villain.
That means they don't care if we
are dead or alive.
In other words, they're not after us.
After this?!
It's no good.
There's nothing special here.
Wait, what are you doing?!
They're after the case, right?
In that case, if we give it to them,
everything's settled.
Yeah! It's as simple as that.
It's not that simple.
They'd probably want to silence us, since we know about the case.
Wait, wait, wait!
Don't think about it so negatively.
Right! Let's burn the case.
And then we can say, "Oh, it burned up!"
That wouldn't change anything.
Then let's first go to the police.
Eh? What then?
"If you want the case,
then give us a million euros!"
That would make us real criminals!
We can't give in to despair!
Come on, let's just hand over the case.
They won't go so far as to kill us.
You're overthinking this.
If this case is related to some sort of a crime,
then we can't just hand it over.
Don't get me involved in your justice!
We're already both involved.
They wanted to kill us.
If we don't know the reason,
then it's dangerous to act rashly.
Then, what should we do?
We'll run.
Huh?
No matter what the situation is, we can't
fight against the police.
The ones chasing us are Otheon's police.
If we cross the border into the
neighboring country, Klayd,
then they shouldn't be able to
do anything more.
We have to hurry and leave before it's too late.
What about the villain?
What if the villain chases after us?
If that happens, I will do everything
to protect you.
I think running away is for the best.
Ah, right? Alright, I get it!
I'll go to the border or wherever
you wanna go!
We can head toward the border on that bus.
If we hang onto the back, it'll be free.
We can't do that, we have to pay.
We're wanted criminals.
It'll be over if someone reports us.
Oh, jeez!
Alright, we've got a free ride.
We're comrades now, hero.
Delaware Smash... Air Force!
I paid in advance for two.
So riding on the roof is okay?
Uh...
Otheon Police HQ
Commissioner General!
I would like you to present the evidence you have
which makes you suspect Izuku Midoriya
as a mass-murderer!
Otheon Police
Commissioner General's Office
The case against Izuku Midoriya is still pending.
I can't talk about the investigation.
Especially not to you, a fellow
Japanese hero.
Japan's number one hero, Endeavor.
Someone gravely afflicted with Stage 5.
For humanity's salvation.
Shoto!
I got the report back from a
detective friend of mine.
How is it?
The car you saw which was
attacked by a Quirk,
was carrying a member of Humarise.
Humarise?!
Where is he now?
He's in a coma in critical condition,
in the hospital's ICU, guarded by police.
So we can't talk to him, huh?
There's also one more thing.
It looks like the stolen jewelry
was all over the scene.
It can't be...
It's a message from Midoriya.
What does it say?
Keep eating
lunch with strawberries
and make sure
you eat the
dinner in the fridge too.
"Keep eating lunch with strawberries and
make sure you eat the dinner in the fridge too."
He's telling us to eat strawberries?
Isn't this a coded message?
So that's it.
Keep eating
lunch with strawberries
and make sure
you eat the
dinner in the fridge too.
K-L-A-Y-D.
Klayd.
He means the neighboring country,
Klayd, right?
Midoriya's heading there.
I'm going to Klayd.
Got it, I'll inform Endeavor.
Bakugo, let's go.
What's gotten into you?!
It's about that damn Deku, right?
Yeah, I'll tell you later.
First, we have to give those guards the slip.
Don't order me around!
I hope Todoroki and the others
can figure it out.
The secret hidden in this case.
It looks like... we managed to lose the police.
Hey.
It's okay for me to make a phone call, right?
Y-Yeah.
They didn't have anything about you
on TV so I think it's alright,
but try to make it short.
Got it!
Hello, Stanleyk here.
O-Old man!
Hm? Is that you, Rody?!
Uh, sorry to call out of the blue,
but can you go to my house and tell my
little brother and sister that I won't be home for a while?
I'll pay you later so—
You idiot!
I have no obligation to do that for you.
More importantly, I got a complaint
that the delivery wasn't made.
Well, that was—
I don't want to hear any excuses.
It's not that!
If you don't want to die, then hurry up!
Got it?!
I don't have the goods.
Damn it!
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
Huh? The cases got switched?
Yeah. The case with jewelry
stolen by the villain.
Midoriya said it got mixed up
with another case during the chase.
The case Midoriya has now, used to
belong to a Humarise member.
So that's why the police are chasing
that damn Deku, huh.
Probably.
That case is probably pretty important.
If it weren't, then the police wouldn't
be moving at such a large scale.
So there are even Humarise members
among the police too.
Yeah, we have no idea know where
Humarise will show up.
We'll have to act carefully.
Don't order me around.
As expected, there's no transit system
going to the border.
We'll have to get a vehicle somewhere,
or walk.
Walk?! There's no way!
Do you know how heavy this is?
If you get tired, I'll carry you
on my back.
Helping people in trouble,
that's what my strength is for.
I'm already in trouble so can you
hurry up and help me?
Yeah, I'll definitely help you.
Okay, here I go!
Big Bro, me too!
Here.
Me next!
Me too!
Wow, Rody!
Dad, welcome back!
I'm home.
Hey, the puzzle this time is hard!
How do I solve it?
Okay, I'll give you a hint.
You can solve it based on that.
Dad, this is your...
It's a present.
Thanks for always taking care of Roro and Lala, Rody.
I heard the father of that family ran away.
On top of that, he became a
member of Humarise.
That crazy group that thinks
Quirks are a sickness?
They were responsible for the
incident the other day too.
He was a famous engineer, wasn't he?
You can't judge a book by its cover.
Kids, don't play with them anymore.
You don't know what they'll do to you.
Okay!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Big Bro.
I'll always stay with you, okay?
No matter what I have to do.
If this case is related to some
sort of crime,
then we can't just hand it over.
Hello?
What is it?
Don't tell me...
Are you with the police?
Hand over the case.
This means I'm free, right?
Where's your friend?
Huh?
You both know, right?
This case's secret!
N-No, we don't!
We don't know anything!
My little brother and sister are waiting for me!
Please!
Let me go home!
Air Force isn't...
Then!
Smash!
I-I'm...
Y-You...
H-Hold on tight.
Damn it!
Hang on, I'll get some help
right away!
I-It's not that deep.
My phone's dead though.
Sorry,
can you pull out the first aid kit
from my backpack?
Y-Yeah.
That villain's tough.
Once we treat this, let's get
away from here.
Why did you protect me?
Why?
I took the case.
I betrayed you.
Instead of protecting me, you
could have taken the case and run.
I wouldn't do that.
I was carrying the jewelry the villains
stole this afternoon.
I'm one of those criminals which heroes hate!
I can't leave someone who's
in trouble alone.
I can't help but feel like I
want to help them.
It's not worth it to get
hurt over that.
It's enough if I'm able to
help that person.
I don't get it.
It's what I've always admired.
I want to be a hero who can
save people with a smile.
I want to be like All Might.
By All Might, you mean
the hero famous around the world?
Yeah, he's my teacher.
Seriously?
You wanted to be like All Might,
so you chased that dream and became a hero.
You and me are completely different.
Huh?
I can't think about the future.
I don't have the leeway to say nonsense
like "I want to be a pilot."
It's all I can do to provide for
my younger siblings.
I-I'm—
Don't say anything! I don't want your pity.
Heroes.
I used to think they were all just people
who wanted attention
and wanted to make money under the
guise of helping people.
In reality, heroes didn't come to
the town I lived in.
Because they wouldn't make
any money there.
But I guess there are heroes
like you around too.
The more you help me, the more I wonder what I'm doing with my life.
I'm so lame.
I'm lame too.
I've been wanting to be a hero since I was little,
but people kept telling me that I couldn't do it,
that I couldn't be a hero.
I couldn't use my Quirk properly,
and I was at the bottom of my class.
I'm always being helped by my classmates.
I'm still lame.
That's why I want to become cool,
to become a hero who saves people with a smile.
That's Pino.
Pino?
I'm Rody, Rody Soul.
What's your name?
I'm Izuku Midoriya.
My hero name is Deku.
Deku?
That's easy to remember.
Yeah, I like it.
Let's get some sleep, Rody.
Yeah, we should, Deku.
I deeply apologize.
They got away just as we were
about to get them.
All my men are currently pursuing them.
Can we mobilize the army?
Unfortunately, I don't have
the necessary authority for that.
Continue the search.
Understood.
For humanity's salvation.
A villain?!
Rody?
Oh, did I wake you?
Where'd you get that car?
I borrowed it.
It's too hard to walk.
I even wrote a note saying that
I'll pay later.
In the name of the Heroes Association.
If I could've borrowed a Cessna,
we could have gone straight to Klayd, though.
A Cessna?
Rody, do you know how to fly one?!
I'm just kidding. Get in!
Hey, Deku.
Yeah?
Once we figure out the case's secret,
I can go home, right?
Of course.
You have a younger brother, right?
And a younger sister.
What about your parents?
My mom died right after she had
my sister, the youngest.
That's why my dad did his best to raise us.
But then he disappeared suddenly.
Disappeared?
Do you know about Humarise?
The terrorist organization.
Yeah. After people found out that
our dad was a member, things got bad.
Our friends stayed away,
we were kicked out of school and our house,
and I couldn't even get a honest job.
I see.
I resented my dad.
I resented him so much,
but then I stopped caring.
Now, my little brother and sister
are more important.
I want to let them live a honest life.
Oh, they're so cute.
My little brother's so smart, and
my little sister's really cute.
Yeah.
She'll definitely be a beauty
when she grows up.
Road! Watch the road, Rody!
As usual we still
Carry our respective sadness
Let's pray again
For tomorrow to arrive
Unfulfilled, we
Embrace so many roles
Let's share each of them
With someone
Melting in the incredible speed of passing scenery
Everything faded
The young flower vendor standing in the street corner
Reminds me of you
Ah, the sound of the bells echoes
Hey, it's not the end, but the beginning
You may have forgotten it all
But I hope you're out there smiling somewhere
Smiling somewhere
Man, your Quirk's so useful, Deku!
Hey, Rody.
Hm?
You have a Quirk right?
What kind?
I don't want to say.
S-Sorry.
You won't laugh, will you?
I won't!
Promise?
I promise I won't laugh!
My Quirk is...
It's heavily guarded.
I don't think we can go in from
the front without fighting.
Our only choice is to go over this.
Get on. Hurry.
Deku, take this.
Rody.
It'll be hard for you to carry me
with that injury, right?
This is as far as I go.
But the car's out of gas.
I can't leave you alone in a place like this.
You know how fast I can run, right?
I'll eat some berries or something
and wait for you here.
Hurry up and figure out the case's secret
and come back for me.
Rody.
I'm counting on you, hero!
Them again!
I can't fail again!
Use these!
Damn it! What's with those guys?!
Delaware Smash
Air Force!
Rody!
Are you okay?
Yeah, somehow.
The case!
Rody!
Take it, Deku!
For humanity's salvation!
This ice...
Todoroki!
This is like the Hosu incident,
your messages are too hard to understand!
Where are you looking?!
H-Help me! I'll do anything!
Then tell me what I want to know.
F-Fine!
You traitor!
Damn it. Bakugo, get her!
Don't order me around!
I-It's out of control!
Just come quietly!
For humanity's salvation.
Get over there now!
Rody, are you alright?
Yeah, somehow.
Where's the case?!
Midoriya, is this it?
Thanks Todoroki,
but how'd you find us?
Thanks to the flashy gunfire,
I saw you from the train.
Is he the one you were talking
about on the phone?
Yeah. He's being
treated like a criminal like me.
His name's Rody.
Thank you for earlier.
More importantly, the case!
It's about Humarise, right?
What? Humarise?
Yeah, that's why we came here.
We thought we might be able to
get some important information from it.
What is it, Midoriya?
This...
Hm, what is this?
How does it work?
It's not that one?
It'll just go back to how it was before.
This is hard.
Hm, that's not it.
Give that to me! I'll just blow it up!
You can't do that, Kacchan!
Deku, can I see that for a second?
Do you know how to solve it?
I did a puzzle like this before,
when I was a kid.
Um, uh, like this.
All right! Got it!
What's this?
It's an information chip.
Okay, there should be a town at the
foot of the mountain.
Let's look into it.
The target has gone into the
neighboring country of Klayd.
I don't have the authority to follow him there.
No matter.
If he's in Klayd,
then he won't be able to come here
while the plan is being carried out.
The time has come to put the
plan into action!
For humanity's salvation!
This is an emergency!
Humarise has started streaming an
internet broadcast.
Pull it up!
We, Humarise, will rise to action
to protect the pure humans called Quirkless
against those attacked by the disease of Quirks.
The humanity salvation devices
which we developed
have been set in 25 countries around the world,
and have already started moving.
Seriously?!
Humanity's salvation will come
two hours from now.
Two hours?!
However, we are not merciless.
If you wish to prevent
the plan from going through,
we will tell you the countries where
the humanity salvation devices have been deployed.
What does this mean?
Even if you do not believe in what we do,
you should have an equal chance.
Director, all 25 countries where
the Trigger Bombs have been deployed
match up with the 25 zones where
Humarise's branches are located!
It could be another trap.
Even if it is...
Give the hero teams standing by marching orders!
Yes, sir!
People are panicking in all zones
where there are Trigger Bombs!
The panic's also spreading to locations
outside of those zones!
The roads are all experiencing gridlock!
This is bad!
Suneater, you extricate the injured.
Red Riot and Real Steel, secure an
evacuation route.
Roger!
Chimera Kraken!
Let's do this!
Red Gauntlet!
You need to evacuate!
Please hurry!
Cementoss!
Let's go Mic!
Okay, everybody!
We've got a path for you, so go on down!
It's alright, don't panic!
You saved us!
Thank you!
We're counting on you, search team.
We'll definitely find the
Trigger Bomb. Got it?!
Roger!
Ribbit!
Leave the evacuation here to us!
We'll focus on finding the Trigger Bomb.
Right!
Tsukuyomi, leave the evacuation
to the American team.
We'll search for the
Trigger Bomb from the sky!
Roger!
Go, Fierce Wings!
Look in every nook and cranny!
Tokage, take these sensors
to look for the Trigger Bomb!
Got it!
We'll definitely find it!
Momo, let's head to the next spot!
Right!
Can we really find the
bomb in such a wide area?
Hello! Hello! Hello!
Salaam?!
Don't be found, be the finders!
Follow me!
He's so fast!
He's not paper thin for nothing!
Clair, where's the Trigger Bomb?
It's not in this area.
Let's move to the next zone!
Shoto, what are you doing?
Hurry up and come back!
Neighboring Country - Klayd
Wow, there are so many.
Where should we look first?
Move!
Where's the newest timestamp?
It's this file.
My name is Alan Kay.
I'm one of the scientists
Humarise kidnapped.
Kidnapped?
Humarise took the families of
many scientists as hostages
and forced the scientists to develop
Quirk Factor Triggering Bombs.
The first terrorist attack used the bomb
to gather top heroes
at places where Humarise
branches are located.
Next, they are planning to use
the Quirk Factor Triggering Bombs
to eradicate those heroes.
After losing its top heroes,
society would collapse.
Using the chaos surrounding that,
they would wipe out Quirk holders
and turn the world into
one with only the Quirkless.
That is the true goal
of Humarise's Flect Turn.
I hope my voice will reach the heroes.
Take this key that my colleague,
Eddie Soul, who was also kidnapped,
made in exchange for his life,
to disarm the bombs.
Please! Save the world.
I repeat,
the organization advocating
for humanity's salvation,
Humarise, has set bombs in different
locations around the world.
They have released an announcement
declaring that in two hours,
one hour and 52 minutes
to be exact, the bombs will explode.
In the areas where Humarise have
placed the bombs, panic has taken over,
and heroes have been working to direct people
to safety and remove the bombs.
The areas in danger of being affected by
the bombs are the following.
You've got to be kidding me!
My house is in the
affected area in Otheon!
It can't be.
Big Bro.
We should send this to HQ and have them
order the hero teams to retreat—
We can't do that.
The heroes are still looking
for the Trigger Bombs.
Even if they themselves
are the targets for them.
Even if they know that it's a trap,
as long as there are people who need help,
the heroes would never leave
them and run away.
It's a plan thought that far ahead!
Then we just have to stop the bombs
with that disarming key.
But how?
Move!
The answer has to be in here.
You're an idiot if you make a key without
telling people where the door is!
Which point wasn't part
of their crime announcement?
This is where their damn base is!
Kacchan, where's the
Trigger Bomb control system?
I'm working on it, damn nerd!
The underground
area furthest in the back.
We know where it is,
but it's more than 400 kilometers away.
We can make it.
I have an idea.
Klayd Airport
Don't worry.
I know the basic controls.
This is no time to be chirping!
We'll definitely stop the Trigger Bombs.
We'll crush those crazy bastards!
We'll definitely protect the heroes,
and the world!
We just received a transmission from Shoto,
a hero who was sent to Otheon.
He said he obtained a
disarming key for the Trigger Bombs!
Where is he now?
He's heading to where the main system
of the Trigger Bombs is, in a hidden Humarise facility.
Young Todoroki. Young Bakugo.
Young Midoriya.
Shoto is heading over
to disarm the Trigger Bombs?!
We should go support him!
We can't.
Our first priority is bomb removal.
Endeavor!
What is it?
I found the Trigger Bomb!
Where?
It's stopped in front of
the North Gate of Otheon Tower.
It's inside a large semi!
Heroes near the tower,
head over and remove it!
Roger!
Clair?!
This is...
Shoji! They're saying Midoriya and the others
are heading over to disarm the bomb!
Don't lose focus, Jiro!
What we should be doing right now
is performing the mission we were given.
R-Right!
I've found the Trigger Bomb!
It's in the third carriage of that train!
All right!
A villain?! Why?
Man, it's guarded?
Uravity! Froppy!
Take the Trigger Bomb somewhere safe!
Ribbit!
Yes, ma'am!
I believe Deku and the others
will stop the bomb for us!
But we'll do what we can do right now!
Move!
The teams have found the Trigger Bombs,
but they're meeting resistance
from Humarise and can't remove them!
There are less than 30 minutes left.
The heroes are also
all fighting desperately.
I'm counting on you, future heroes!
We're close!
Purge the gravely afflicted.
That's their base!
I'm gonna land, so hang on!
Rody, you turn back after this.
Why?!
Commoners like you should stay put.
From this point on..
this is a job for heroes!
Small fry should just stay put!
Some of their members have Quirks, too!
It's not just the mercenaries?
A sound wave?!
Kacchan!
I know!
Midoriya!
Bakugo, we'll leave this place to you!
We won't let you go!
Don't tell me what to do!
Stop!
We're taking a right at the end here!
All right!
Just a bunch of small fry, huh?
Why are you damn villains helping
Humarise, huh?
We have been chosen by Humarise!
We will work with them and
live in a new world!
So you're just trying to save yourselves?
That's so selfish.
You damn villains!
Die!
They're fast!
Those guys just do whatever they want.
You're Rody Soul, right?
Todoroki!
Go on head!
There's no time!
I'll take care of you all at once!
Flashfreeze Heatwave!
Fire didn't work?!
He isn't aware of himself,
is he using Trigger?
Is he rotating his Quirk
to control the flow of water?!
Smash!
Damn it!
Even the explosion itself was cut?!
Don't act like this is nothing!
At point blank!
Too bad!
All that moving around's annoying!
That laugh.
I can't stand it!
Small fry like you don't get it, huh?
I stocked up on grenades
while I was fighting.
You've turned into real crazies now!
Hurry! Hurry!
Don't get in my way!
This is the room furthest back.
That means the Trigger Bomb
control system is through those doors.
Go away.
This is not a place where someone gravely afflicted like you can enter.
The leader of the organization,
Flect Turn.
This is a holy place that will
bring about humanity's salvation.
This isn't the salvation of humanity.
The Quirk Doomsday Theory
hasn't been scientifically verified!
It's just a popular belief!
How can you accept something
so uncertain without questioning it,
and do something so terrible?
Pure humans are being threatened
by the disease of Quirks.
As time passes, they mix,
evolve, and go out of control,
driving humanity to destruction.
That's not true!
Whether someone has a Quirk or is Quirkless
doesn't mean they're sick or anything!
We're all alive. We're all human!
The gravely afflicted are beyond help.
I must be the one to do it after all.
I will definitely stop the Trigger Bomb!
Smash!
I-It was repelled.
No, this shock and force.
It feels like a Smash.
That's right.
I was born with a disease.
A disease that won't go away,
that reflects everything.
I knew it.
His Quirk lets him
reflect anything he receives.
And it's the kind that's always activated.
You've got a Quirk, too,
so why won't you believe in them?
He can even reflect long-distance attacks.
Believe in them?
You fool.
Because of this disease,
I was never once held by my parents.
Even my close friends,
and those I gave my heart to
left me, who reflected even their feelings.
Since I reflect everything,
I couldn't even choose death for myself.
A Quirk that cannot be
controlled only leads to pain.
And people's bodies and hearts were being
crushed by the evolving Quirks!
I'll stop using my Quirk just at
the moment of impact!
Even if it's reflected!
H-He focused all the impact into one point.
Then...
I'll run all out and head
toward the control system!
I reject myself.
I will eradicate the disease
called Quirks from this world.
And then, I will save
the pure humans from destruction!
Poor thing.
In five minutes,
the first step toward the salvation
of humanity will finally begin,
through the death of many heroes.
I won't let you.
I will definitely stop the Trigger Bombs!
Then you'll die with your friends.
Uraraka.
Asui.
Kaminari.
Sero.
Mineta.
Kirishima.
Shoji.
Jiro.
Yaoyorozu.
They're all fighting desperately.
To stop the Trigger Bombs.
To protect everyone's smiles.
Think.
A way to defeat him!
R-Rody, why?
It's fine now, Deku.
I-It's dangerous.
Get away... from here.
I will, once I give this to those guys.
Th-The disarming key?
Rody?
I was told
that if I did, they'd stop just
the Otheon explosion.
Rody, no.
We'll definitely stop it, so...
How are you gonna stop it with
your body like that?
There's no time.
The bomb's gonna explode.
It's game over.
Rody.
So I'll just protect
my little brother and sister.
Deku, I'm a worthless delinquent.
I can't protect everything,
take on everything, like a hero like you.
The world or my family.
If it's only one or the other,
then I have to choose.
It was like that for my dad,
too, wasn't it?
Yes.
Your father, Eddie Soul,
helped develop the
humanity salvation bomb.
Eddie.
Take this key that my colleague,
Eddie Soul, who was also kidnapped,
made in exchange for his life,
to disarm the bombs.
Please, save the world.
What do you mean by "helped"?
You took us, his family, as hostages
to make him do what you wanted.
Thanks to that, he was able to make
the correct choice.
And you're the same as your father.
You made the correct choice
to protect your loved ones.
I'm the same, too.
I chose this plan because I love humanity.
Rody, don't!
Rody!
Rody.
It's time to give up, hero.
This is how people are betrayed.
It happens to me, too, all the time.
It's nothing to cry about.
Rody...
Hey, Rody. You have a Quirk, right?
What is it?
You won't laugh, will you?
I won't!
Promise?
I promise I won't laugh!
My Quirk is...
Pino!
All right! All according to plan!
Deku!
You fool!
Rody!
How impertinent.
Deku!
Kick that damn bastard's butt!
I'll stop the bomb! Go!
Go, hero!
Go!
I won't let you go!
I will never let you get past me!
Rody, you have a Quirk, right?
What is it?
She's my Quirk.
Pino's actions show my true intentions.
Really?
No matter how much I lie,
Pino gives away how I really feel.
It's really not much of a Quirk, is it?
That's not true, Rody.
Not being able to lie
is a really wonderful Quirk.
Damn it! I can't react
fast enough on my right side.
You've finally
shut up!
This time,
I'm really gonna drive it in!
Howitzer
Impact!
You idiots.
I-I'm losing consciousness.
That's...
Make it in time!
I won't let you get in Midoriya's way!
Flashfreeze Heatwave!
You can even manipulate flames?
Then, here's the biggest move
I can do right now.
Flashfire Fist
Jet Kindling!
Midoriya.
Make sure
you stop them.
Like... my dad.
Like...
Deku.
Rody?!
For both father and son to die in vain.
There's no saving scum.
That's not true!
Rody, my friend,
is not scum!
It's no use.
You still don't understand?
It's only natural
that I believe in Rody!
I believe in heroes!
Cover Endeavor!
Shoto,
leave this place to me!
Go, Fierce Wings!
Get out of harm's way!
Hawks, a new Trigger Bomb
has been discovered!
What did you say?!
We're done dealing with it here!
What about the remaining Trigger Bombs?
Currently, there are two more!
Wait!
A new one's been discovered!
There are a total of three!
We definitely won't give up!
Right, Bakugo?!
Get this up in the air and—
Ribbit!
Ochaco!
The Trigger Bomb!
I won't give up!
Deku would never—
Like Midoriya and
the others would ever give up!
So we won't give up either!
I will definitely not give up!
That's right.
Heroes won't give up!
Like we'd ever give up!
Has his power increased?
No.
That's not all.
The amount of force is decreasing!
Of course.
There's a limit to his reflecting Quirk!
In that case,
I'll surpass that limit!
Don't tell me...
I've reached the limit of my Quirk?!
I-Is that possible?
You gave up.
If you didn't give up,
if you kept trying,
you might have been
able to get along with people.
But you called it a disease,
and then gave up and despaired.
You stopped trying!
Shut up.
We know what it means to never give up.
We're always telling ourselves this.
Shut up.
Go beyond
Plus Ultra!
Shut up!
Detroit Smash!
A hero
can always break out of a tough spot!
All Might...
Young Midoriya!
A hero has a lot to protect.
That's why...
we can't lose!
United
States of
World Smash!
It's
too late.
Even though,
we're past the time limit,
there's no explosion.
It stopped.
Did they... disarm it?
Yeah, they did it.
Good job, everyone.
Thanks, Rody.
I'll get you to a hospital soon.
Deku.
l-l protected my family,
like my dad, right?
Yeah.
I stopped the bombs, right?
I took on everything like you, right?
Yeah, you did.
You're amazing, Rody!
I'm so cool!
The terrorist attacks that shook the world
were successfully prevented
through the work of the hero team.
The leaders of Humarise who spearheaded the attacks
are also being arrested one after another,
and the incident is on
it's way to being resolved.
The case was closed
without a single
Trigger Bomb exploding.
The heroes protected the world to the end.
But, it wasn't just them.
The one who really saved the world,
who never gave up...
Day of Departure
Rody?
I thought you weren't getting out
until the day after tomorrow?
They said I'm fine already.
I'm glad.
If I had died like that,
I could've become a legend, though.
Don't say something so unlucky.
Hey, what are you going to do now, Rody?
Just going back to my normal life.
Of course, I'm not choosing either a simple
or an interesting one, I'm gonna get both.
Yeah.
We will now begin boarding
for flight NNY224.
It's time to leave.
Don't ever come back to Otheon.
When I'm with you,
nothing good ever happens.
Go be a hero in Japan.
I'll come back and visit.
Don't ever come back.
The stillness of a city with nothing
The uncertainty of a hand holding nothing
But with just myself
And these two eyes
I hold the remains of a dream
Old man, got a job for me?
A respectable one, if possible.
One of my employees quit.
Help me out.
What should I do?
The awkwardness of a room with no sound
My days without are so vapid
Yet once again
I rise up with just myself
To this reality that spreads out before me
Though we may be struck by heavy rain
Words we hold onto alone at night
Restless
Compassion and sadness are surely
In short, empathy
Maybe that's where our souls exist, see
Already awake
Kicked the door open and
Ran through the morning sunset skies
Right now, the sound of you out of breath
The city streets at dawn veiled in dew
Moving forward every day, in rumpled fashion
Crossed an asphalt ocean
You'll see freedom lying just beyond
Over there, the world shouts out
Incessantly
Scenery instilled in us from our birthplace
Negate a destiny linked to irises and skin
Just dreams of a future where all is accepted
Dreams
Though at times we may face strong winds
The tears you spilled all alone
Compassion and sadness are surely
In short, empathy
Maybe that's where our souls exist, see
Already awake
Kicked the door open and
Ran through the sunset skies
Right now the sound of you out of breath
The city streets at dawn veiled in dew
Moving forward every day in rumpled fashion
Crossed an asphalt ocean
You’ll see freedom lying just beyond
Over there, the world shouts out
Incessantly
Your name