It was quite sudden.
If she wasn't feeling well, she should have called us.
I bet she didn't say anything
because she thought you were busy.
Grandma was always like that. You know that, right?
Daisy.
Are you blaming...
me for this?
Not really.
I just think...
Grandma must have wanted to see you more.
She must have wanted to see you more.
Because...
Grandma...
she loved you so, Mom.
She...
lost her own mother when she was still young.
Letters?
Those are the letters Grandma received
from Great-Grandma after she died.
Letters from someone who had died?
She asked a Doll to be her scribe,
so Grandma would receive
a letter every year on her birthday,
even after she was gone.
A doll? Are there dolls who can write letters?
A long time ago, there was a man who made
a typewriter for his blind wife.
He called the machine an "Auto Memoir Doll."
Later, people began using the word "Doll"
to refer to women who worked as scribes.
Scribes? They wrote letters for other people?
Yes.
Back then, many people couldn't read and write.
Later, more people learned how to write
and telephones became common.
Fewer people send letters now.
That job probably doesn't exist anymore.
Back then, when a person wanted to
write something special or difficult,
they'd ask a Doll to do it.
Grandma really treasured those letters very much.
I see.
We have to go back now. Our patients are waiting.
Yes.
You too, Daisy.
I'm going to stay here a while longer.
Grandma would be lonely without anyone here
after the funeral, right?
Daisy.
Why don't you leave, Mom?
You always put your job before family.
That's not true.
I care about Grandma.
I care about the both of you a lot!
Come, I'll take you to the station.
Daisy.
We'll come back after work.
Grandma.
I said an awful thing to Mom again.
Though I know...
Mom has a really hard job.
"Anne, happy eighth birthday."
Many sad things may be happening.
And you might be feeling overwhelmed right now.
But don't lose hope.
Even if you're sad and feel like crying...
don't forget:
Your mother loves you very much.
Anne, happy tenth birthday.
You must have grown up quite a bit.
But I'm sure you still love reading and dancing.
Have you outgrown riddles and bugs?
Happy 18th birthday.
You're grown up now.
Are you in love?
I can't give you love advice.
But I'm sure whomever you choose is a wonderful person.
Happy birthday, Anne.
You've lived for 20 years now.
That's amazing.
But remember, even adults
are allowed to complain sometimes.
Whenever you're feeling down,
remember that I am with you.
Anne.
I will always...
always...
be watching over you.
Anne.
She received a letter like this...
every year on her birthday?
Great-Grandma...
must have been really worried about Grandma.
A newspaper clipping?
Who is this person?
Those letters were written...
by a Doll who was very famous back then.
She wrote a love letter for a princess once.
She also wrote the lyrics
for an opera performed by a popular singer.
And she even wrote the script
for a play of a famous playwright.
She worked for a postal company in Leiden.
But she quit when she turned 18.
Afterwards, there was no news about her.
The name of that Doll was...
Violet Evergarden
I picked her up on the northern front.
She doesn't have a name.
Hey! Say hello!
You can't treat a child like that!
Gil.
She's no child.
She's a weapon.
Just a tool, a tool of war.
Would it be okay if I gave you a name?
Violet.
I have a feeling you'll grow into
the name when you're older.
Don't be a tool.
Be a person who embodies her name.
Violet Evergarden.
Come forward.
The writer of this year's hymn to the sea...
will now present the hymn to this year's goddess of the sea,
Ms. Irma Felice.
The hymn to the sea was very good.
Violet.
You must have truly worked hard on it.
Yes.
It was different from a normal letter.
The sea is boundless.
It is home to many organisms.
It is abundant and beautiful.
However, it doesn't have
achievements, status, or personality.
It was hard to write praises for it.
Well...
Okay!
I'll write it next year!
You can't write the hymn to the sea
unless you're selected to do it.
I'm gonna start writing lots of great letters
and make sure they choose me!
Right, Violet?
Yes. I hope they choose you.
Leave it to me!
Yes.
Violet Evergarden.
Mr. Mayor... and the mayor's wife.
Violet, this is the Mayor of Leiden
and his wife.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
If a client requests it, we shall go anywhere.
Representing the Auto Memoir Doll service,
I am Violet Evergarden.
You're so beautiful. You really do look just like a doll.
Yes.
I've heard so much about you.
It was I who recommended you to be
the person to write the hymn for the sea
for the Festival of Thanksgiving.
The public oath you wrote for King Damian...
of the Kingdom of Flugel was a kind of public love letter.
It was quite beautiful,
as beautiful as you are.
When I wrote the oath for the coronation,
all I did was put the visions
and aspirations of the king into words.
Although you describe me as beautiful,
there is no correlation
between the words I write and myself.
I mean no offense.
Violet, in other words...
In other words, I am giving you a compliment.
Right now, you are a Doll, but before that,
you were a brave soldier who saved Leidenschaftlich.
I didn't save Leidenschaftlich.
It was the countless soldiers who fought.
But... the war claimed so many other lives.
I too took many lives.
Therefore...
I am not a person who deserves praise.
Should we eat?
I want yakisoba.
Try something else for a change.
Okay.
Violet.
Erica.
It's been a while.
Hey, you look like you're doing well!
Yes.
President, it's been a long time.
How's being the playwright's assistant?
The same playwright that Violet scribed for, right?
Yes.
I introduced Erica to him after we went to see his play.
I asked if I could be his apprentice.
He writes and rewrites things all day.
It's hard keeping up with the typing.
But I'm learning a lot.
Do you want some yakisoba?
Benedict, we're trying to have a conversation.
Don't talk to me like that. You're so mean.
Would you like to walk around the festival with us?
I'm sorry.
Thank you for inviting me.
But we have a rehearsal for next month's play.
Did you write the script!
Yeah.
It's a small play we'll do at the community theater.
But please come see it.
I'll be going now.
See you later.
Okay.
It goes to show, anything's possible if you wish hard for it.
Not everything no matter how hard you wish.
What should you do then?
I'm going to excuse myself too.
I have a lot of work to do.
You can take the day off.
It's the festival!
No.
It'll interfere with my planned work schedule.
I'll go back now.
Major.
Major?
Save yourself.
Leave me here.
You have to run.
I won't let you!
I won't let you die, Major!
Stop!
Just stop!
You have to live.
Violet.
Be free.
With all my heart.
I love you.
Dearest Major Gilbert,
I had a flashback about you today.
No matter what I see, and no matter what I do...
my memories are connected to you.
As time passes...
and the past fades away...
my memories of the time we spent together
still come back to life.
You kept me by your side.
When I was unable to do anything,
you taught me how to live.
And you gave me...
the words...
"I love you"...
for the first time.
That's why I can't help writing to you again like this.
I hope...
this letter will reach you someday.
And I pray that my wishes will come true.
That comes out to three Corse in change.
Thank you very much.
It weighs 1.2 Leib. That will be 11 Corse, please.
Hello. This is the CH Postal Company.
If a client requests it, we shall go anywhere.
Representing the Auto Memoir Doll service,
I am Iris Cannary.
Yes.
She's here.
Thank you for waiting.
The schedule of the Doll you requested
is booked for the next three months.
Could I help you instead?
Oh... I see.
I understand.
I'll make your reservation for three months from today.
Yes... that's right.
Goodbye.
Iris.
Don't give the customers that attitude.
They can't see my attitude over the telephone.
Your emotions show in your voice.
All right.
You have lots of reservations too, right?
Not as many as you, Cattleya.
At this rate, I'll never move up
from third place around here.
Thanks for your hard work.
Oh, president, good evening.
This week has been busy, right?
I hope you get some rest over the weekend.
I'm going on a business trip this weekend.
I've been asked to be the secretary
for the commerce treaty with Gardariki.
Oh, that's right.
I'm planning to attend the mayor's wife's party.
I'm going to look for new customers.
You all work too hard.
I recently took up tennis.
I was looking for someone to play with me.
Don't you have any sense of crisis?
We must work hard while we still can.
People will stop sending letters someday all
because of that horrible machine.
They'll finish building that radio tower soon.
When that happens, everyone is going to get a telephone.
You're right.
A lot of things are going to change.
Our postal company will gradually change as well.
Someday, a Doll's job will be considered...
old-fashioned.
It will become obsolete and disappear.
That's exactly why we must work while we still can!
Violet, are you going to the party too?
No... I...
Don't make me bring my rival to the party!
Yes.
Don't make her do that.
I have my own plans for the weekend.
All right!
Come on! Why can't you hit less hard!
I would if I were playing with a girl,
but it's just you today.
Everyone's so busy.
Even Violet turned me down.
I think it's nice she's going out for a change.
But it's nice having her around.
It helps me get attention from girls.
When I'm out delivering, people ask me,
"Are you from the CH Postal Company?
Where the Doll named Violet works? Introduce me to her."
Don't use Violet for your own dirty motives!
But...
I wonder where she went today.
You're so overprotective.
Captain.
So it was you...
who's been leaving flowers for my mother every month.
I should've come tomorrow,
on the anniversary of her death,
but your other relatives might come.
Did I trouble you?
No.
But you didn't need to come all this way.
It's your day off today.
I was able to come because it's my day off.
Are you here on his behalf?
I'm not doing this on behalf of the major.
I came of my own free will.
How many years have gone by since the end of the war?
You understand, right?
He's not...
Forget Gilbert.
Forget him.
It is...
too difficult to forget.
As long as I'm alive...
I can't forget him.
Hey!
Violet.
No. That flower is not a violet.
It's called a pansy.
I see.
You know a lot.
Even if I never see him again.
"I can't...
forget him."
My ribbon.
Hello. CH Postal Company.
Um... Can I speak to a Doll?
I am a Doll.
Really? I have a job for you.
Can you come to my place?
Our company is closed today.
What? Really?
I see...
Pardon me, but by the sound of your voice,
you sound quite young.
What does age have to do with writing letters?
Don't Dolls go wherever you ask them to?
Is that a lie?
No. It's not a lie.
Then come over!
Who is it?
I'm the Doll from the CH Postal Company.
Oh, come in!
Excuse me.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
If a client requests it, we shall go anywhere.
Representing the Auto Memoir Doll service,
I am Violet Evergarden.
You really came.
I came as you requested.
You look young. Are you up to it?
I'll do my best.
Yuris!
Brother!
We're here!
We're coming in!
Just a moment!
Hide! Hurry!
Hurry!
Brother!
Yuris, was someone just here?
No.
Oh, really? I thought I heard someone talking.
How are you feeling?
Stop asking me the same thing every day.
Are you okay?
If I were okay, I wouldn't be here.
Forgive me.
Brother!
I'll read you my story book!
I don't read story books. That's so stupid.
Your brother isn't feeling well.
It's worse than that.
I've had three surgeries
and have been in the hospital for a whole year.
Yuris, Lucas said he wanted to come visit you.
He said he wants to see you.
I don't want him to.
Why not? You two were so close—
I said I don't want to see him!
What's this?
It's so old—
No! Don't touch that, stupid!
It...
belongs to someone...
who came to visit the person in the next room.
I'm just holding on to it a bit.
I'm tired now!
Sorry.
We're going for a walk now.
Good idea.
You get some sleep now.
We'll come again.
Sorry.
May I come out now?
Would you please explain...
why I had to stay hidden?
Young master.
You can call me Yuris.
All right, Yuris.
I want to write something without my mom,
dad, and brother knowing about it.
Write a letter?
Yeah.
Letters for the three of them.
Letters for them to read after I'm gone.
So I want you to hold onto them for a while after we finish.
Don't send them right away.
All right.
You know what I mean? Can you do stuff like that?
It's not a problem.
I handled a similar request in the past.
There was a girl who was a little younger than you.
Her mother wrote letters to her...
so that she'd receive a letter from her...
every year on her birthday
for 50 years even after she was gone.
For 50 years? Does that mean there were 50 letters?
Yes.
Even now, she still receives one of those letters every year.
I'm sorry but I can't afford that many.
My money's in that tin. Write as many as it will pay for.
So how many can you write?
If it's three letters...
I can write around 20 characters per letter.
Just 20 characters?
"Dear Mom...
Take care.
Yuris."
That's so short! Even I can write that much!
I need...
I want the letters to make
my mom, dad, and brother feel better
after reading them!
Yuris.
That is the standard fee.
My company has a special discount for children.
Therefore, the money in your tin will be enough
to pay for any letter you want me to write.
Is that really true!
It's true.
You're making it up!
I didn't make it up.
This special provision was created
so we can perform our duties during times of emergency.
It's our emergency provision.
I don't really get it.
But... It sounds cool!
It means "good!"
All right, let's get started!
Your hand.
I lost it in the war.
I was also in a hospital a few years ago.
Can you write letters with it?
It took a while to learn how to use this artificial hand.
But I can use it fine now.
I can even do gestures like this.
You're kind of funny.
People always just say to me:
"How are you feeling?" "Are you okay?" "Go to sleep."
You're different from Mom, Dad, and the nurses.
How am I different?
People are always worrying about me,
feeling sorry for me...
and being overprotective.
You know, I'm tired of that stuff.
Understood. I will try to eliminate
those three elements from my emotions.
You really are funny.
All right. Well...
Write me a letter.
Write one to my father.
Your father?
Yeah.
My father went off to the war.
He went to a country called Leidenschaftlich.
He said he'd come back soon, but he hasn't returned yet.
That's why I want to tell him that I,
my brother, and my mother are all safe.
Can you write me a letter?
Let's invite Violet out for dinner.
Okay. Let's go to that one place.
That restaurant...
we all went to when Violet first got here.
It's you.
Captain Dietfried.
Lt. Colonel Hodgins.
No, I should call you president.
I always forget that the war has been over
for many years now.
What do you want?
Well...
Violet!
Captain.
Please excuse my...
impertinence.
No. Don't worry about it.
Here.
Is that my...
Did you come to give that back to me?
I noticed you dropped it.
So the place that Violet went to was...
The graveyard...
where the major's mother is buried.
Captain.
Thank you.
All right, then.
Let's dump our stuff and go eat!
Good idea.
Violet, will you join us?
Okay.
Hey!
My family has decided to get rid of the boat we owned.
The boat?
Yeah.
My brother...
sailed in it many times when he was a child.
It contains many of his books and the toys he played with.
If there's anything you want...
Could I have them?
It's a bunch of junk, really.
I'm going!
I'm going wherever the boat is docked!
I didn't know you went to her grave every month.
Should I have told you?
No.
You don't have to.
You're free to do as you like in your free time.
You're going...
to visit the boat?
I'll tell you when I go.
I said you don't have to tell us.
Violet.
Shall I go with you?
I'll be fine.
You may eliminate your pity, concern,
and overprotectiveness of me.
She said she'll be fine.
Shut up! Just be quiet and eat!
Violet's right.
You can't worry about her all the time.
Of course I'm worried.
Dietfried, that bastard.
He's playing on Violet's broken heart.
He could be good for Violet.
They can share their memories of the major.
That man took advantage of Violet being an orphan
and used her as a tool during the war.
Is that why he shouldn't talk to her?
Even if he's not like that anymore?
Are you saying they should lick each other's wounds?
Would that be such a bad thing?
Violet still has feelings for the major.
I'm worried she's going to be crushed
by those feelings unless we do something.
The captain may...
bring comfort to her in a way that we can't.
You know...
if I ever have kids someday,
I hope it's a boy.
My nerves won't be able to handle a girl!
This is one of the books he was crazy about.
He played many games with our father.
Did this belong to the major?
No.
That's mine.
Excuse me.
You don't have to be so formal.
Yes.
You and the major must have sailed...
this ship often when you were children.
Yeah.
Our father took us out.
My father was devoted to the military,
but he liked sailing as well.
That's the only thing I inherited from him.
This is our family's flower.
What does it matter?
What?
What did you just say?
That's what you wanted to show us, right?
You wanted to show us this,
so you could tell us to become like you.
Brother.
You just wanted to show us...
that this is our only choice!
Brother!
You, your father, and all of us in the Bougainvillea family
have no choice but to join the military!
Father, stop!
Don't hit Brother!
I'll do it!
I'll grow up to be like you!
Since I was so rebellious...
Gil had no choice but to listen to our father.
It's my fault. He couldn't choose his own life.
But I still treated him horribly.
I have... no siblings in my family,
so I don't entirely understand.
However, I can understand...
how someone could...
have complicated feelings...
for someone they're close to.
You understand how other people feel?
Sorry, I wasn't trying to be sarcastic.
I know.
Is it okay if I keep the book and this board game?
Yes.
Let's go now.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
We've both lost something important.
Both you...
and I.
Sorry about the other day.
For saying you'll never see him again,
and telling you to forget him.
I can't forget him either.
After all...
he's my little brother.
Yes.
If I could see him again...
I would apologize for many things.
And many things I would talk to him about.
Yes.
Next, the letter for my brother.
I wonder what I should write to him, though.
Sion's still only five.
Why don't you tell him how you felt
when he was born?
Yeah.
I was so happy when he was born.
He was so warm and soft, like a freshly baked loaf of bread.
But then...
Did you start to feel like he stole your parents from you?
Did you feel jealous when your
parents praised him instead of you?
You're right.
But you thought he was adorable whenever he chased you.
How did you know that?
I've heard other people talk about it.
Okay. After you write that, add this next:
"Live a full life in my place.
And in my place be good to Mom and Dad.
Have Mom and Dad...
spoil you in my place."
To me, it seems like you're saying things you don't mean.
What you really want is for your father and mother
to spoil you yourself.
You know everything.
I've written a lot of letters.
Words, attitudes, and feelings all have
an outside and an inside.
I've begun to understand that what you see...
on the surface isn't everything.
And sometimes you have to tell people...
your true feelings, or they'll never know.
Look.
How is this?
Thank you.
I'll hold on to the three letters and keep them safe.
Give them the letters on the day I go to heaven.
I'll ask the hospital to inform the post office.
Yes.
Hey, can you do a pinky swear?
A pinky swear?
Yeah.
You link pinkies...
with each other.
And you swear...
to keep your promise.
Thank you.
Your finger is so cold.
Even through my glove.
I'll probably go cold before the winter comes.
Still.
I think your letters will warm...
the hearts of your parents and brother.
I'll make sure I give them your letters.
Well, then, I've fulfilled my duties.
Wait!
There's one more...
letter I want to write.
Is it for Lucas?
I was listening from under the bed.
If there's something you want to tell him,
it's best to do it while you can.
You think so?
Yes.
I was...
unable to ask and say everything I wanted.
To whom?
The person...
who gave me "I love you."
Did that person die?
I believe...
that he's still alive somewhere.
What did you want to tell him?
That I understand...
what "I love you" means.
You understand? Is that all?
Lucas said...
he wanted to visit me.
But I told him not to.
Lucas and I have been close since we were little kids.
We always played together.
But then...
my arms and legs...
began...
to wither.
I don't want him...
to see me like this.
I'll put...
those feelings...
in the letter for you.
As for the fee...
Yuris!
I'll get the nurse!
Let's leave the letter to Lucas for next time.
Sorry.
No problem.
Are these all the "lost letters"?
I took them from Roland.
I thought I'd return the letters whose senders we know.
So? Are you asking me to help you since I'm the president?
Young people these days don't like working overtime.
Look how hard I'm working.
You should make me the vice president.
You should go to accounting school first.
Our vice president must understand the account books.
Whoa! Now, I know how to get promoted!
Then I might get serious.
Isn't this...
Yeah.
This is the shelf where we keep recent mail.
This handwriting...
What's wrong?
No.
The sender's address is on the Island of Ecarte.
That island used to be occupied by Gardariki.
It gained independence after the war.
Why did you want to meet with me?
President.
The other day...
Is it about that Doll who works at your place?
Did she say something?
No.
Don't worry.
She left after she visited the boat.
She said that you'd be worried about her.
She said she'd tell me before she went.
You're not her guardian.
You have no right to control her.
You bastard! How dare you say that!
Sorry.
I was wrong.
This is the only way I know how to talk.
I didn't come today talk about Violet.
Isn't this...
Can you look into it?
President.
Sorry to disturb you so late.
I need to talk to you about something.
What is it?
I... haven't confirmed it yet.
But...
it's possible I'm wrong.
The major?
Is it the major?
Yeah.
Have you news of him?
Have you received new information...
about Major Gilbert?
Are you going to go now?
Yeah.
It might be someone else, but I'm going.
All right! We'll take care of things here!
Violet... Are you okay?
Am I okay?
Is it okay if I see the major?
Is there anything wrong with me?
It's been so many years.
Do you think the major will recognize me?
Come on.
Violet.
What should I say when I see him?
Tell him how I'm doing now?
Or tell him my feelings?
Will I be able to articulate it?
Am I being foolish?
Violet.
It's going to be a long journey, right?
Why not write a letter on the way there?
We're back, Daisy.
Sorry for being so late.
Daisy?
"I am going to Leiden for a while."
The country eventually nationalized...
all the postal companies.
The one she worked for was turned into a museum.
I wonder where she went after she quit.
Please take your time looking around.
I'm sorry. I didn't notice you there.
No problem.
If you have any questions, please ask me.
Okay.
Actually, I used to work here
a long time ago as a receptionist.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Excuse me.
What's this stamp?
Oh, yes.
This stamp is only issued on the island of Ecarte.
The island of Ecarte?
Did you say you used to work here?
Yes.
Oh, sea of blessing
Sea that connects to the entire world
The seagulls dance, in your skies
The fish swim, in your midst
The shellfish burrow, in your bottom
You give light
You nurture life
You pour out love
We continue to live close to you
Until we cease
We entrust our bodies to you
In the present In the past
And in the future
It's supposed to be a ritual for giving thanks to the sea.
But it's become a day to mourn those who didn't return.
No one returned from the war.
The only people left on the island
are the old, the women, and the children.
They died at war instead of at sea.
I must apologize to our ancestors.
Our fathers were killed by those Leiden soldiers, right?
Yes.
I wish everyone in Leiden would die!
The hymn they just read
was dedicated at the Festival of Thanksgiving in Leiden.
They say it was written by a famous Doll.
Violet Evergarden was her name.
Everyone!
Come! It's time to eat!
Come on. Let's go!
Let's go!
Teacher!
I love you!
Let's go!
Come on!
Major.
It's been such a long time.
I've thought about you...
every single day,
every single day while I couldn't see you.
I hope that my prayers will be answered...
that my wish will be granted...
and that I can see you again...
someday.
Violet.
Can you wait here for a while?
I'm going too!
If...
Gilbert really is...
here now...
We don't know his current situation.
So—
I don't care!
You may not care.
I don't know about him.
I heard he's not using his real name here.
It's a small island.
He likely doesn't want to spread rumors.
Can you wait here?
I'll wait.
If I can see him again,
I'll wait as long as it takes.
It's your first time here. Why don't you take a look around?
Understood.
I don't know who he is.
Hello!
Hello.
Whose father are you?
I'm not...
Then who are you?
You look creepy.
No. I'm from the postal company.
Oh! Then are you here to deliver a letter?
Yes.
Look! I've got something for you!
He's scared!
Let's go back!
I don't think I can handle a boy either.
Are you someone's sister?
I'm—
Are you a post-person?
Yes. That's right.
I knew it!
This is for you!
Here!
An insect.
A praying mantis.
Aren't you scared?
It's missing...
one of its front legs.
Just like Teacher Jilbert.
Is he also missing...
his right eye?
You know a lot!
He's your teacher?
He's your teacher, right?
That's right.
Is your teacher...
doing well?
Yeah! He has no right hand but plays the bars with his left.
And he can run really fast!
Yeah! He's really fast!
Right?
Can you...
please tell me more about him?
About your teacher?
Okay!
Our teacher... he's really nice!
He explains things over and over if you don't understand!
Who is it?
Come in.
If there's something you don't understand...
I never thought that...
You survived.
Gilbert.
I go by the name "Jilbert" here.
I see.
Sorry for visiting you so suddenly.
How did you find me?
You wrote a letter for a kid, right?
All the undeliverable letters get returned to the post office.
We check them a final time
before returning them to the sender.
I came across your letter by chance.
Why...
are you here?
After the battle...
I awoke lying in a hospital bed.
I didn't have my ID tags,
so they sent me to a hospital run by a monastery.
I worked at the hospital for a while.
Then instead of returning home,
I roamed around for a time.
I came here...
a year ago.
I wrote letters at the children's request,
and started teaching at this school.
I know my duty was to notify the military.
That doesn't matter.
Did you know that Violet is alive?
Yeah.
Then why didn't you come see her!
Violet!
She's been waiting this whole time!
I made her unhappy!
She's...
better off without me.
She's here...
as well.
She's waiting outside right now.
Do you have any idea how much she wanted to see you?
I can't see her.
Gilbert.
Never again.
My friend...
He's dead.
Gilbert Bougainvillea is dead.
That's what everyone thought.
And as the years went by, everyone accepted it.
Therefore... let me live a different life.
Gilbert—
We're...
in the middle of the grape harvest season.
I'm going to help them.
All the men on this island left for war.
And none of them returned.
Hodgins.
Please.
Leave.
I'll return.
I'll come back.
Do you...
Do you hate me?
I don't understand your question.
Have I failed you in some way?
If there's something I'm doing wrong,
I'll fix it! Please tell me!
No.
That's not true.
It's my fault. I said you're not a tool.
But I still...
I still... used you.
Of course you can use me! I'm your weapon!
The battle is turning against us!
What should I do next?
Major! Give me your orders!
President!
It's him!
It's really him!
I talked to the children.
Did you not see him?
I did.
Was he hurt anywhere besides his arm and eye?
No.
Then...
I can see him, right!
He said...
he can't see you.
Is he still working?
I'll wait until he's finished.
That's not it.
Then I'll wait until nighttime.
Violet!
Then...
then tomorrow.
Right.
I'll go see him tomorrow and try to talk to him.
He must...
he has to see you.
Does...
that mean...
not that he can't see me?
But that he doesn't...
want to see me?
Why not?
I can't really explain it.
He said it's better that way for you both.
It can't be.
I...
Violet.
Violet!
Once you're done, it'll be easy
to move the grapes to the top.
You've been a big help.
It looks like we'll have heavy rain.
Major!
I found him.
Major.
Major!
I'm sorry I came...
to your house.
Major.
If you've been alive...
why haven't you contacted me?
Why didn't you come to see me?
I want to...
Major, I want to see you.
I want to continue talking where we left off.
I've begun to understand...
the meaning of "I love you."
Go away.
Go away!
I'll wait.
I'll wait here...
until I can see you.
You don't...
need me now.
And...
if I'm with you...
I will remember...
taking you to the battlefield when you were so young...
how you...
lost both of your arms...
because of my orders.
Major.
Do you regret...
that I exist?
It must be...
that I am...
causing you pain.
I can understand...
how you must feel now, Major.
I don't understand everything.
But I understand...
a little.
You idiot!
You can have these.
We are grateful.
There was nowhere else for us to stay.
It's a small island. We don't even have an inn.
Violet said this lighthouse functions as a post office as well.
I see...
how the season has come again
with the bloom of this flower.
"The prince's eyes were like blue sapphires.
The sword at his side was decorated
with sparkling red rubies."
You've gotten pretty good at reading.
Violet.
Stay by my side.
Stay by my side at all times, Violet.
Okay.
Are you from the Leiden postal company?
Yes.
Is Violet Evergarden the girl
who was with you just now?
Your postal company got a call from the hospital.
There's a boy named Yuris who is in critical condition.
Yuris?
Who's that?
He's one of my...
customers.
Give them the letters on the day I go to heaven.
Yes.
I'm going back.
I'm going back to Leiden.
Violet!
You can't go back in the middle of a storm!
The boats can only leave tomorrow morning at the earliest.
You'll see Gilbert.
Right?
I want to see him.
I want to see him!
But!
I made a pinky promise!
Yuris.
I promised him.
And there's still one letter I haven't written yet.
But it's going to take you at least three days to get back.
Can't you go faster!
I'm going as fast as I can!
Benedict and Iris left for the hospital
to deliver the letters you were keeping.
Good.
Excuse me.
Yuris.
The Doll is here.
You want her to write a letter, right?
Vio... let?
I'm Iris. I came instead.
Violet is somewhere far away right now.
She is reuniting with the one who's dear to her.
Is it the person...
who taught her "I love you"?
That's right.
He's still alive.
Good.
I've heard about you.
You want to write Lucas a letter, right?
Yeah.
What do you want me to write?
Yuris!
Yuris.
You'll be okay.
Yes! Please connect me!
Please!
Yuris.
It's Lucas.
What am I supposed to do
with this?
You say, "Hello."
Yuris!
Yeah.
Hello.
Lucas.
Yeah!
Lucas, I'm sorry I told you not to come.
And that I didn't want to see you.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing!
I...
I was sad when I heard you didn't want to see me.
But I thought it was what you wanted.
So I tried hard.
But...
I couldn't help myself.
And I went to the hospital many times.
And I saw your face in the window a little.
Sorry...
for saying something...
so mean.
No.
I'm not...
mad at you at all.
Yuris.
We've always been friends, right?
Let's continue being friends forever.
Good.
Thank you.
That horrible device comes in handy sometimes.
Yuris!
She wasn't... able to write the letter.
But he was able to speak...
with Lucas on the telephone one last time.
And tell him...
what he wanted to say.
"I'm sorry."
"Thank you."
And they delivered the letters you wrote...
for his parents and brother.
"Mom,
Your...
pancakes were so delicious.
If I had eaten more vegetables,
I could have... made you happier."
"Dad,
It was fun going fishing and camping.
Mom... Dad,
I'm so glad...
I was born as your son.
I love you.
Yuris."
There's also a letter for his little brother.
Me?
"Sion.
Sorry for the times I got mad at you or was mean to you.
But... I was really happy
when you were born."
"Thanks for letting me become an older brother.
Live a full life in my place.
And take care...
of Mom and Dad in my place.
Have fun with them.
And have them spoil you...
my dear brother.
From your older brother."
Thank you, brother!
I'm so happy!
Mom and Dad are you happy too?
Yeah.
Yes.
Thank you.
Yuris.
They said Yuris was glad you
were able to meet the person...
who is dear to you.
Let's visit him again in the morning.
If he doesn't come out, I'll kick down his door
and give him a good thrashing!
No.
If he's to be struck...
then I'll do it.
What?
I'm kidding.
I'm going back to the postal company...
on the next boat.
I'll return to writing letters.
There is much work I have left.
Violet.
The major is alive and safe.
I thought I'd never see him again.
But I was... able to hear his voice.
I'm...
That's...
enough for me.
All right, give it a try.
There it is! It's coming up!
That's amazing.
This will make things a lot easier.
It's the old man and the girl from the postal company!
Old man?
Hey! Our teacher made that machine!
Isn't it great?
Look, there's a lot!
Can it hold more?
It's great!
Awesome! I wanna try it.
Right?
It's amazing, right?
Yes.
Will you...
please give this to your teacher?
Okay! I'll make sure I give it to him!
Bye!
It's not your burden to bear alone.
All the young men from our island left.
And lots of people died in the war.
We're probably all to blame.
We all thought our lives would be better...
once we won the war.
We all hated the people from Leidenschaftlich.
But...
we all suffered in the end.
All of us.
If you have a home somewhere else
you should go back.
No.
I'm staying here.
Staying forever.
Having you here is a big help to us all.
Hey!
Have you finally been able to
choose your own path on this island?
It sure looks like a nice place.
Brother.
You've been living a carefree life.
And you didn't even come to our mother's funeral.
They were fond of you, unlike me.
Sorry.
Meanwhile, Violet has been visiting
our mother's grave in your place.
She still visits every month even now.
I was...
planning on apologizing to you...
if I ever saw you again.
But right now...
I ought to stuff you in a sack...
and drag you off to see Violet!
I shouldn't have...
taken her in back then.
Then what did you really want to do?
I wanted her to have...
fun while she was young...
to be able to enjoy...
pleasant things...
to allow her heart...
to be inspired...
by beauty.
I wanted...
to provide her with that.
But I...
It's for you.
Read it.
Dearest Major Gilbert,
Please forgive me for visiting you so suddenly.
This is...
my last letter...
to you.
The reason...
I'm alive today...
and learned how to love others...
is all thanks to you.
For...
accepting me...
I thank you.
Thank you for reading to me.
For teaching me how to read,
and showing me many things...
I thank you.
For the brooch you gave me...
For always...
always keeping me by your side...
I thank you.
With all my heart...
For giving me "I love you"...
I thank you.
Hearing you tell me "I love you"...
has been like a guiding light in my life.
Since I've learned what "I love you" means...
I wanted to tell you that I love you.
Major.
I thank you.
Thank you.
I thank you for everything.
Your voice is my guiding light
A sparrow cries out
We all struggle...
with being true to ourselves.
Looking for me within a nameless sky
I will head for tomorrow in this cradle woven from kindness
I will carry the Bougainvillea family name.
You may be free.
Be it a day of rain or a day of sunshine
I will be there to protect you
Go.
A treasure more valuable than all
A nameless flowers lies in peace
Violet!
Major?
Flapping the wings that we were given
Gilbert.
Let's promise to never stop flying
As we're not alone
Major!
Violet!
I only have one wish
Which is for your happiness
I will head for tomorrow
Be it a day of rain or a day of sunshine
I will be there to meet you
Your voice is my guiding light
Major.
Violet.
I'm not your master or your superior officer anymore.
I hurt you.
I'm not...
the man you think I am.
I'm not a good master...
or a good person.
I don't...
deserve you.
But even now...
Still...
Still I...
I love you.
I...
I want you to stay with me.
Violet.
I...
Major.
Violet.
Don't cry.
You see?
I'm...
I'm about to cry too.
I want to wipe away your tears.
Please.
Lift your face.
I...
Major...
I love you...
Violet.
I've always wanted to do this.
After wrapping up her remaining work...
she quit her job at the postal company...
and took over the postal service
at the lighthouse on the island.
Afterwards, the post office moved to the main street.
Once telephones became common,
the Dolls ceased their work.
But I'm sure she wrote many letters...
for the people who lived on the island.
Meanwhile...
This stamp was issued
by the CH Postal Company Memorial Foundation,
and is only sold on this island.
The island holds the record
for the most letters sent each year per person.
A long time ago, it used to be
a job done by women called Dolls.
There was a popular Doll who lived on this island
and who everyone loved.
Her name was...
Violet Evergarden.
She had also written letters
which my grandmother received.
If there's something I can't say...
maybe I could tell them in a letter.
I want to tell them my true feelings.
The people I want to tell my feelings...
are... only here in this moment.
Dad.
Mom.
Thank you.
"I Love You"
Violet Evergarden