A hypno beast?!
It made Lenia open the door?!
Hold it off, Raiga!
All right!
Edgar, tank for us!
Got it!
Raylorka Sladseld!
Anti-magic birds!
Kuroki can't use magic until we take them down!
If we lose track of them, it's over!
Follow them!
Okay, it's all yours!
It's not looking good, Uncle!
You're right about that.
Without magic enhancement,
I score a D, or C at best, in P.E.
I'm basically useless.
A score of C or D on what scale?
It's not an F, which probably means he was actually trying.
Bringing back memories, Edgar?
Yeah, this isn't gonna be like when he was carrying us.
He might have a scary face,
but we've trained hard to catch up to him.
That's...
They're talking about you!
Huh?!
They really look up to you!
Huh? Nah! Y-You think so?
His strength is the real deal.
A-Aw, shucks...
The gigant hunter, Doldor Rexdol!
M-My bad. Wrong guy, I guess.
Sorry, Uncle.
I'm gonna take a bathroom break.
You two keep watching without me.
But Kuroki sets a high bar for us too.
No kidding. Kuroki really packs a punch.
Kind of a weird guy, though.
Uncle!
C'mon, Uncle!
They're praising—
I don't care!
Just go and watch without me!
Uncle!
I'm sorry, Uncle.
Uncle from Another World
Uncle from Another World
Uncle from Another World
gets
to
decide
The
way I
should
and
shouldn't
live?
[UNCLE]
[UNCLE] Th
[UNCLE] That
[UNCLE] That's c
[UNCLE] That's comp
[UNCLE] That's complet
[UNCLE] That's completely
[UNCLE] That's completely fi
[UNCLE] That's completely fine.
GET HOME
GET HOME
Sold cheaper than a scouring pad
He's not coming out.
Is he gonna be okay?
I believe in Uncle's strength.
Uncle will come back from this!
You're right!
So, let's keep watching and just have faith!
So let's go! Let's get to it! Hurry!
Come on now.
Let's see.
Let's go with wind, fire, then ice.
DEAD?!
Uncle!
He's alive!
Whoa, smooth!
Uncle?!
That's gotta hurt!
Just made it.
But what was that attack?
That was Elf.
Uncle!
Are you feeling better?
Yeah, I'm good.
That was Elf's new weapon.
The scabbard she rushed out to get.
Huh? The scabbard?
Long-distance heavy piercing mode.
How useful.
A monocle! And a ponytail!
The scabbard's badass, but why the monocle?
That's an ancient artifact too.
No, orc face. Over here, geez!
Silly boy.
Here! Over here!
Wait, he ran off!
Jeez, what's his problem?!
Perhaps because she's elven royalty,
she hunts humans for sport.
Gosh, I can't see him anymore!
Wh-What's he doing?
This one's Elf's fault.
Aw, he's out of sight! It's not fair!
I almost forgot, but what's the deal with those birds?
Golly, why's he hiding from me? How could he?
Shutting down magic seems like a big deal!
From what I heard later,
their breath has some magical property to it
that inhibits the spirits' activities.
Wow, so that's how it works!
Sounds like a fantasy story!
In reality, the spirits are more like
"That bird's breath stinks,"
"I don't wanna work," and so on.
So that's what it is.
Their breath just stinks.
Regsuuid Zaldohna!
They said, "It's still stinky,"
and "I really don't wanna work."
How bad is the anti-magic bird's breath?
The spirits are pretty stubborn.
Anyway, after that I made it back to Alicia's group, but...
Go away!
They're totally hypnotized!
Alicia!
Kuroki!
Oh no, you're burned!
O God, grant thy healing light!
Appreciate it!
Can you un-hypnotize them with your wand?
No way!
The wand is great, but holy magic
is based on healing the mind and body!
I'm powerless in the face of plain old violence!
That's how it is!
Does it have a hidden activation switch?
Elf's sword has one to activate a special function.
A-A switch?
Like... what if it twists?
K-Kuroki, what are you—?
This light... is harmless?
Y-Yes! It looks like it.
Is this light the wand's area of effect?
Alicia, try to undo the hypnosis again.
O-Okay!
Just...
Th-This spell works by synchronizing
my mental tranquility with the target,
thus pacifying th—
Huh?!
What'd you say?
I can't hear you!
Um... I just mean...
Please don't stare at me...
Oops! Sorry.
That'd definitely make it hard to cast the spell.
O God!
Let the inner waves of these minds led astray
become one with mine!
What was I doing?
Hypnosis?
I did it, Kuroki!
Alicia!
Armor Piercing Titan!
My technique?!
Alicia!
You okay?!
Huh? D-Did I...?
Uncle, what was that?
A side effect of using the wand
was that she gained additional powers.
She became able to use the techniques of her friends.
Not only that, but due to it being holy magic,
the technique had more power behind it.
For real?
She's coming into her own as a hero!
Wait!
Crap. Flaming hell beasts!
There are so many!
They're so easy to snag when they move in a straight line.
Finally.
Raylorka Mibald Bagl Hild!
The Spirit of Water
is boiling with rage.
Brace yourselves.
Bagluuid!
Much better.
We truly can't thank you enough!
You're truly the heroes!
It was nothing!
We gotta retrain.
Mister!
I'm sorry for being scared of you.
No, it's really not a big deal.
For the time being, I patched up the wall with a barrier.
You might wanna check on the baths, though.
It feels so much more open!
We can promote a "have a drink
while watching the sunrise" package!
Yeah, we'll be filthy rich!
Woah, this barrier's crazy strong.
That's a heck of a spell you used.
I made a huge barrier once.
Glad the experience came in handy.
Yay!
We finally get a competitive edge
for our boring and outdated inn!
How can you say that, Lenia?
Is that how you've felt this whole time?!
You're right about that, Lenia!
So yeah, that's basically the wrap point
for the action there.
Good to know it all worked out in the end!
Wait, wasn't this supposed to be a story
of you getting told off for erasing people's memories?
That's right, so it was!
So after the fight,
I took another long soak in the spring.
Fast-forward.
R-Right.
Excuse me...
I forgot to tell you I was coming in.
The monsters burned the partition
between the men's and women's baths.
Anyway, fast-forwarding...
Don't touch it!
Raylorka Mibald Bagl Hild
Sherion
Lugardos Golet
Raylorka Mibald Bagl Hild
Sherion
Lugardos Golet
Raylorka Mibald Bagl Hild
Sherion
Lugardos Golet
Water Serpent, elevate thy enemy and consume
Protect
Thunderous lightning hammer
Water Serpent, elevate thy enemy and consume
Protect
Thunderous lightning hammer
Water Serpent, elevate thy enemy and consume
Protect
Thunderous lightning hammer
Kuroki!
I'm covered!
Phew.
Did you think I didn't have anything on?
Well, we are in a hot spring.
It wouldn't be unexpected.
There's no way I'd be naked!
Icuras Cuora!
So fast!
Uncle?!
I-It's not because I saw something dirty.
Of course not.
You got your memories back, right?
People in real life don't get nosebleeds
from seeing something naughty.
Thanks.
I let my guard down.
Looks like I had erased my memory of seeing Alicia naked.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
Yeah, I know.
You're not interested in young girls like me, are you?
You think so?
I'm only 20 myself.
Of cours—
W-We're the same age?
Aren't you at least in your 30s?!
I'm 20.
Barely past 19.
Wh-Which month were you born?
I was born in August.
November.
He's younger than me?
Alicia's older than Uncle.
She looks way younger. I wouldn't believe it either.
B-But my birthday may not be all that accurate.
Huh, why's that?
I don't have any memories from before I was 9.
Kuroki, could you use
your memory-displaying magic on me?
11 years ago in August, please.
Sure.
Icuras Elran.
My first memory
is of blood and a carriage.
The goblins were taking me somewhere in that carriage,
but I was saved by some knights
from Raiga and Edgar's village.
Maybe I hit my head
because I just can't remember anything before then.
To the bestest big sis, Alicia
Happy 10th Birthday!
From
This was all I had.
In the end, we never found my family.
They were probably killed by the goblins.
Eventually, I was given the name Alicia
by the priestess of Edelcia,
and adopted as her own.
And so, here I am today.
Well, anyway!
That's why I'm not sure if I'm really born in August!
Alicia, are memories important to you?
Isn't that obvious?
Since I lost so many memories,
I treasure everything I experience!
I've erased your memories twice.
Are you trying to be funny?
I can use Icuras Cuora, a spell that erases memories.
Erases...
memories...
Why?!
My...
Kuroki.
What memories of mine did you erase?
You'll get a nosebleed, so watch out.
A nosebleed?
The first time was on Mount Dold,
when we defeated the goblin horde together.
The second time was taking a shortcut
to clear the Labyrinth of Darkness.
That means... the goblin quest, becoming a crusader,
and even being ordained as hero?!
It was all you, Kuroki, not me!
I'm nothing special.
But weren't you the one
who quietly repaired the Sealed City's barrier?
That's what the legendary hero would have done!
So you did see that.
You can disclose the truth.
I'll go somewhere far away.
What do you mean?
I don't understand!
I'm also the one who broke the barrier.
Why would you do such a thing?
Well, I wanted to know if I could.
Kuroki.
You're not the kind of guy
to toy with people's lives on a whim, are you?
I came from another world.
Just like Murayama who established
these Purgatory Springs, I'm from Japanbahamal.
Huh? You're from there too?
I'm searching for a way home.
So I figured if the toughest defensive barrier
took on the strongest offensive magic,
perhaps it would trigger a space-time distortion
that I could use to get home.
But it ended up simply destroying the barrier.
That means...
like the hypno beast we fought today,
you want to put a hole through the wall
between this side and that side?
That's the basic idea, yeah.
Are those the only two times you wiped my memories?
Yeah. No more.
Never use that kind of magic ever again!
Not on others or yourself!
I did it to survive.
I'll do it again if necessary.
Kuroki!
I...
don't want to forget you,
and I don't want you to forget me!
I understand.
From now on, I won't use magic to wipe your memory.
That's not enough!
I also won't erase my memories about you.
Are you happy no—?
That's a promise, right?
Right.
Good.
That settles it.
Oh, but...
What is it this time?
Now I understand why you were writing
and mumbling stuff just now.
Again?! What memory had I just erased?
What was it about?
Nothing, just seeing me na—
I'll remember! Please recreate it!
I-It's nothing important. It's okay!
That won't do. We made a promise!
We agreed I wouldn't erase any memory about you!
You only saw a little bit...
A little bit? Of what?
Um... Well...
Can you close your eyes for a bit?
Huh? Okay.
Are you serious?
She shot right through the barrier?
Kuroki?!
He's younger than me, huh?
You get the idea.
Monsters attacked, Alicia got upset,
and Elf started blasting.
It was more like Hell Springs than Purgatory Springs.
What should I call him now?
Young Kuroki?
No, maybe I should just stick to Kuroki?
Could it be that Uncle over-wiped his memories,
and now he's got a couple of screws loose?
U-Uncle, I think you should tone down
the memory erasures a bit.
I agree!
You just erased some unwanted memories
in the bathroom, right?
Huh? No, I didn't.
But... you looked particularly refreshed.
No, no, that wasn't magic.
It was the technique of killing emotions.
Pardon?
Theoretically, no matter how upsetting something is,
if you don't feel it with your heart, you take no damage.
It's simple as that.
You kill your emotions before it takes a toll.
You'll need it much more when you're older.
You two should start practicing it while you're young!
That's a pass. Right, Takafumi?
I see.
If you're dead inside...
There you go.
Great. This is great.
Stop it!
The Heisei Depression.
Nice expression.
The Lost 20 Years.
Keep it up and you can empty your heart even more.
A lot of bad stuff happened.
It works well, Uncle.
Takafumi!
Please! Stop!
No matter what happens from now on,
Good. I feel good.
Hey! Don't do it!
I can overcome it by utilizing this technique.
Come back to us, Takafumi!
Your shadow inevitably lengthens
As I wave you goodbye
Why do you never notice?
I've been looking at you for so long
These emotions I can't express
Are searching for a place to go
A brush of orange in the sky
Gently rises above
A melody rings
As I wish upon a tiny, tiny star
Someday it will shine bright
In that sky that's far away
I wish I could make it clear, I wish you could understand
My love for you is infinite
It twinkles like a star
Shining only for you