I'm   home
Ladies and...
gentlemen!
Eto-musume
Nyaa-tan
Now it's time to report everything that's happened,
and I'm doing it in 30 seconds, meow!
Please keep your ears open,
and listen carefully, meow!
Since the end of the anime,
Takeru went on a school trip,
and we got a new member, Na-tan!
So that's how we're
getting more characters?
We're going off topic.
Then Na-tan said
"Nyaa-tan, I love you."
"I have so much respect for you."
She's such a good girl.
Then when I was about to receive
the power of Sun/Lull,
Chuu appears with a strange thing,
and eliminates some force of evil.
Then Piyo-tan was saying
"This evil is related to Na-tan..."
"because Na-tan and Nyaa..."
Meow!
toki o koe ima ugoki hajimeru
Through time, we start to move
nishi e higashi e to junbi wa mou OK
To the west and to the east, I'm ready OK
kokoro no oku ni nemutteru mono subete
All that sleeps within my heart
hora taitemitara takanaru tamashii
Give it a tap, my soul is screaming
nanika ga hajimaru youna oto
The sound of something beginning
nee issho ni hora kanaeyou yo mirai e to
Hey, let's look to the future together
dokidoki suru ne
I'm so excited
hitotsu futatsu mittsu hyaku nen saki mo
One, two, three, a hundred years from now
wasure wa shinai yo zutto
I will never forget you
nee kimi no tonari ni irukara
Because I'll be right next to you
motto egao mi sasete
Let me see more smiles
tsunaida kizuna o shinjite
Believe in the bond we've formed
hashiride sou Eto-nyan-ran
Let's start running, Eto-nyan-ran
Etotama
Meow-llions of Customers
Thanks for the meal!
Let's eat, meow!
Oh, yes! Eat me!
My, my.
Huh, what's wrong Shaa-tan?
The stock prices have dropped.
Huh?
This is the first time I haven't been
able to predict the trends.
Meow meow?
What's the matter, Uri-tan-san?
This...
Meow...
The sesame oil...
has separated!
Wait, how did that..
It's a super special sesame bottle
that took 6 months to arrive,
and it's gone off in just 3 days,
it's not possible!
Uri-tan-san is really particular
about our condiments, isn't she?
Not quite, meow.
It's just the sesame oil.
Everything's about the sesame oil.
Pah! On to a new topic!
Takeru is nearly back
from his school trip, meow!
I'll be home soon.
I'm looking forward to getting some
more Sol/Lull when he's back, meow.
Right, Na-tan?
Thanks, Nyaa-tan!
I'm looking forward to it too,
I'm so excited!
But... make sure you thank Takeru
for giving you the Sol/Lull.
Of course I know that, meow.
Anway, I've already
prepared a gift, meow.
Ta da! Look at this!
We asked Uma-tan-Sensei for some help.
Nyaa and I are writing an everyday
Take-chan 4-panel manga spin-off!
The first chapter is already on sale
in this month's Takamagahara, meow.
When did you do that?
H... help...
The... pen... is attacking... me...
Don't... let... it... drink... please...
She fell asleep.
What happened?
That's my fault, she was
up all night drawing for me.
All night?
No wonder she fell asleep.
But it's all for Takeru!
We need to do it
for Takeru to drop us Sun/Lull!
I do feel bad for
Uma-tan-sensei though.
But Nyaa-tan, thanks to that decision,
Sensei worked hard, and Take-chan's everyday
spin-off as a salaryman has been completed.
Of course, Nyaa-tan made
such a noble proposition,
that Uma-tan-Sensei wrote
until she ran out of life.
Nyaa-tan, you really are amazing!
Is there anything you can't do?
Its just one thing after another.
I want to be an Eto-musume just
like Nyaa-tan, as soon as possible.
When Takeru comes back,
you can get lots of Sol/Lull,
and become super powerful!
Yay!
I wonder...
What's that!?
Uh... there's a big
hole in the garden...
Did the stupid cat do something again?
What's wrong with her?
Chuu-tan?
It's a sign that something's not right.
Huh?! She's clearly brought
something that's not right!
So you followed me, huh?
That's not good...
Chuu-tan, what's going on?
The seal... is breaking.
The seal?
An evil god, despised
even by other gods...
his seal is about to break.
An evil god?
Could it be... the reason
my shares went down?
This god... is this why my
sesame oil has separated?
Seriously?
If the power
of the evil god is unleashed,
Japan will be destroyed.
As the Zodiac goddesses
who guard Japan,
we must never let this seal be broken!
Chuu-tan.
Where is the seal, meow?
Here.
So close!
I mean if you look at it closely,
it does look like something's sealed in there.
Yep, yep.
Why didn't anyone notice until now?
Seems like Nyaa-tan is
the only one who didn't notice, right?
There was always this weird seal here.
That's right.
You don't remember?
It's true, it really was here.
What's wrong? You look sick.
I... I don't know...
I don't know, but...
I'm scared.
If I do this,
you'll be less scared, right?
Just now...
Oh, no!
Na-tan, don't be so selfish,
you need to share some with me!
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't do such weird things
when we're having a serious moment!
No problem!
Love is invincible!
I'm home.
Mei-tan, you're a bit late.
I'm not going to
forget my Zodiac duties.
I got you a souvenir.
Ah, I'm so happy.
Hey, Chuu-tan,
what you said earlier...
Is it by chance...
It's Susanoo.
Um, Susanoo... as in that Susanoo?
The evil god that can't be stopped?
Um?
Yes.
Aaah, I think it just cracked!
Why are you guys so
scared of Old-man Susanoo?
Old-man?
That's very friendly.
Me and Chuu-tan were
neighbours of Old-man Susanoo.
Right, Chuu-tan?
Don't... you remember?
Remember what?
The one who sealed
the uncontrollable Susanoo.
It was you... Nyaa-tan.
I remember!
I remember it!
The memories just appeared suddenly.
Yep, yep, yep!
It's strange though, the memories
with Old-man Susanoo are so blurry.
Hmmm...
Certainly...
That day...
As usual, Old-man Susanoo would bring me
the souvenirs he got while traveling.
There was a cat that lived there,
and I was playing with it, meow.
What's going on?
Susanoo's seal is breaking!
He suddenly began to rampage, meow.
It wasn't sudden.
Originally, it was enough
to contain Susanoo's evil power,
but the seal was weakened.
Because we hadn't been doing
the maintenance,
the seal had begun to fail.
So that means it's time
to do maintenance on this seal?
That's right, Zodiac Goddesses.
Boss! I mean, God!
He's too bright, my eyes!
God, please tell us
how to seal the door!
I can't see a thing,
what did I do to deserve this!?
Na-tan, it's time to do your duty.
Duty?
What do you mean?
Y-you are the key to sealing Susanoo!
You must awaken and regain
your original power... you know?
Hey, what is this?
What do you mean?
Nyaa-tan!
Oh no, what's happening?
The seal has broken!
I-It's sucking me in.
Na-tan!
Nyaa-tan!
Take this!
Everyone!
Etotama Transformation!
Eto-musume of the cat, Nyaa-tan!
Within the realm of Susanoo,
the power of other gods is suppressed.
I'm counting on you.
Meow, meow!
Oh, sorry Nyaa-tan.
I really, really am sorry!
Get off! And get your boobs off me!
Don't stop!
This is... the sealed world of Susanoo.
Na-tan! Where are you?
So we got invited in, did we?
It feels full of evil.
I'm feeling quite motivated over here.
Mr. Susanoo, where are you?
There's no clues.
God only told us half the story.
I can feel it...
something's here.
Really?
There's nothing—
That looks really strong.
Don't be scared!
For now, we just—
It's so big!
This is... the result
of the mass of evil in Susanoo.
I see it's time to have some fun!
Alright!
One down. We will protect Japan!
First, let's get rid of these guys.
I can help too!
Kii-tan!
Understood, Inu-tan!
Uri-tan... head collision!
The enemies don't stand a chance.
You could have died though.
Oh no!
Hello? How is the project going?
100 million.
Huh? 1 billion over 1,000 years?
It'll be 1,000 years
until they can beat me.
Careful, careful.
Time to get rid
of the viruses, you know?
Moo-tan, clothesline and dropkick!
Your fortune for today...
is bad! Your day will be terrible!
terrible!
...ble!
Moo-tan, special punch!
This is the last one!
That's all of them destroyed.
We need to go rescue Na-tan, meow!
No way...
We worked so hard getting rid of them.
They must be drawing power
from Susanoo's body.
Does that mean these things
will keep resurrecting?
It's like God said, after all.
Nyaa-tan and Na-tan,
have got to seal Susanoo together.
Over there.
I feel the source of the evil.
Okay! So we just need
to get Nyaa-tan over there!
Hurry up, stupid cat!
Um...
Na-tan might be there.
Really, meow?
Alright, meow!
Na-tan? Where are you?
Where are you?
Nyaa-tan.
You're here!
I think I just heard Na-tan's voice.
Are you there?
Na-tan!
I feel like I've seen this before.
Old-man Susanoo!
Listen to the voice of Na-tan!
Where is Na-tan?
Huh, w-wait!
Old-man Susanoo, hey!
Why are you attacking me, meow?
I was just asking where Na-tan is!
I'm angry, meow!
Secret Technique:
Cat Machine Gun!
Cat
Machine
Gun
My attack failed!
Seal.
Of course, the seal!
Wait, Na-tan, where are you?
Anyway, I've got to get the seal, meow!
Um, the seal...
Seal...
Meow!
Seal!
Nothing happened
even though I said "seal"!
I knew it would be useless, meow!
Chuu-tan!
Nyaa-tan.
Na-tan!
Where are we, meow?
I remember I was fighting
with Old-man Susanoo.
I'm sorry I couldn't
hold onto you before.
It must have been scary alone.
Yes, I was scared.
But I know why I was scared.
You know what, Nyaa-tan?
As God said, I am the key to the seal.
I'm not an Eto-musume.
That's true...
Nyaa-tan, do you remember the cat
at Susanoo's house?
Of course! It was
such a cute cat, meow.
That cat was me.
To fulfill my role of the seal,
I took the form of a cat
and stayed at Susanoo's side.
I was always alone.
But Nyaa-tan, you came and visited me.
You played with me,
and stroked my chin.
We purred together.
You gave me so many memories.
I was so happy!
Na-tan.
Even after becoming what I am now,
Nyaa-tan, I've been so happy
to be with you.
That's why...
That's right.
That's what happened.
On that day, when
Old-man Susanoo was sealed,
you left the shape of a cat,
and took the shape of a hammer.
That's how we were able to
seal Old-man Susanoo.
The cat become the hammer.
Na-tan, you're inside
the hammer, right?
Ding ding!
I am!
I'm here with you.
Nyaa-tan!
Chuu-tan!
You can do this, Nyaa-tan!
Leave it to me.
Let's go, Na-tan!
Okay!
Nyaa-tan, keep it up!
Of course!
Just a bit more...
One last hard hit to the center
and the seal is complete!
Right, Na-tan?
Y-Yes.
Are you tired, Na-tan?
N-No, I'm okay.
I can feel it, you're
getting weaker.
I'm okay!
Na-tan, what's wrong?
Something's strange.
What are you doing, Nyaa-tan?
It's the voice of God!
Hurry up and seal Susanoo,
Using Na-tan's Etotama powers.
Wait a minute, God!
What are you saying?
If you use the Etotama...
Na-tan was created to be the seal.
Her purpose is to seal.
I can't.
What did you say?
I can't do that.
I won't, I won't.
I don't want to seal
Old-man Susanoo anymore.
If we don't seal him,
we can just defeat him inste—
Nyaa-tan.
I know you understand.
The only one who can
seal Susanoo is Na-tan.
With that hammer, just like last time.
But...
Only you two can do it.
But, but, but...
Even if I disappear,
the hammer will still be with you.
All the fun we had together,
I'll remember it forever and ever.
So please,
let me fight by your side!
I love you, Nyaa-tan.
You're selfish, Na-tan.
I know.
I love you Na-tan, so please...
Yes?
Don't be scared!
I'm happy!
Flash!
Secret Technique:
Sealing of God!
Secret
Technique
Sealing
of God
Secret
Technique
Sealing
of God
Secret Technique:
Sealing of God!
Secret
Technique
Sealing
of God
It was hard...
But thanks to everyone's efforts,
Susanoo is sealed again.
Good work.
Nyaa-tan.
I'm home!
Welcome back!
What's with the feast?
We're having a party,
to welcome you back from your trip.
It's a treat from Shaa-tan.
Apparently she made a profit
from her stocks.
Oh, great!
It's a thank you for always supporting us.
I bought some special
sesame oil!
No! The smell of sesame oil
is going to be everywhere!
Takeru-san, you should sit down,
I'm sure you're tired.
Sure, thanks.
Hello!
Where's my gift, meow?
I need more than cakes, meow!
Huh? You haven't got it yet?
I haven't got any presents yet!
I sent it in the mail...
I'm sure it'll be here tomorrow.
Ahhhh, I can't wait until tomorrow!
Give me your Sol/Lull in the meantime!
No, what are you doing?
Gimme, gimme!
Well then, see you again
jaane matane to
Wait, don't be too clingy.
Repeating feelings
kurikaesu kanjou
Nyaa-tan, did something happen?
That sunny spot, cozily, stretching out in ones eyes
fuwari hitomi ni hirogaru hidamari
Um...
Nope, nothing, meow!
I'm just feeling super
full of happiness, meow!
The eternity once wished for shakes unsteadily
itsuka negatta eien ga yurete
I turn around alone, not certain why
hitori furimuku nazeka wa wakarazu
Because I met you, hope was born
deaeta kara kibou umareta
I found pleasant days to live
yasashii hibi mitsuke raretanda
In my heart the premonition of a breaking dawn
mune ni yoake mae no yokan
A new blue
atarashii aoiro
Even though it is not right, tears fall
kanashikunai no ni namida ga koboreru
Well then, see you again
jaa ne matane to
And today becomes the past
kyou ga kako ni naru
Turning, my heart and feelings of uncertainty
kururi kokoro to omoi no mayoi go
It seems there is just one thing missing
hitotsu nani ka ga tarinai mitai de
It scares me a little, but I want to change
sukoshi kowai yo demo ne kawaritai
The end
Flash!