Our views have been declining.
Ice Magic vs. Stovetop Flame
Fire
Ice
The latest video, Ice Magic vs. Stovetop Flame,
seems unpopular.
The comments were harsh, like,
"A pointless waste of resources."
We need to tighten up our budget from today.
I'm going to stop bidding on online auctions.
What's that?
I got it at last.
This magazine listed the final
result of Sega Saturn readers' choice.
Unfortunately, I never had
the chance to see the results.
Saturn
Games
are the
World's
Best!
Saturn Magazine Readers' Choice
I couldn't die without knowing it.
Maybe this desire kept me alive
in the harsh other world.
Such a silly thing kept you alive?
Takafumi.
The results are here.
Saturn
Games
are the
World's
Best!
Saturn
Games
are the
World's
Best!
The final page
Saturn
Games
are the
World's
Best!
of Sega Saturn's history is in this magazine!
Saturn
Games
are the
World's
Best!
Stunningly, I don't care.
Right, the last game to come in first place was...
Oh, you're reading it already?
Oh, the winner was a porn game ported
from the PC version.
I guess that's not what you hoped for.
No, I'm not complaining.
I can agree with the ranking as I read the reviews.
But, I feel sad, as if I were watching wild,
macho high-school boys getting tamed by girlfriends.
Really?
Not really.
What?
Number one...
should have been Guardian Heroes!
It adopted the fighting game system
into a side-scroller while maintaining balance.
Its innovation and perfection needs to be recognized!
197th place? What?!
197th place?!
Uncle from Another World
Refrain keshita kioku rewrite
Refrain those erased memories, rewrite​
Uncle from Another World
Monogatari no tsune ga ima miseru kotoba de
With the words that give a glimpse of the story
Don't end this, won't change it​
Dou shitatte kaerarenai
Can't change it, no matter what you do
Mokuteki wo wasurenaideite
Don't forget your goal​
Dare ga kimetan da
Who decides
Sonna ikikata rashikunai yo
the way we should and shouldn't live?
Yaritai koto tsuranuku chikara
The strength to do what you want to do​
Sore koso ga tsuyosa datte
That's what really makes you strong​ ​
UNCLE:
UNCLE: You
UNCLE: You're
UNCLE: You're fi
UNCLE: You're fine
UNCLE: You're fine the
UNCLE: You're fine the way
UNCLE: You're fine the way you
UNCLE: You're fine the way you are
Wakatteiru kara
I know that's the truth
I believe in what I've done​
No reason to go back again​
Ayunde kita hibi wo
The meaning of nostalgia
Natsukashimu imi wo
For those days I walked​
Easy losing memories​
I'm struggling now to overcome​
Akirameru koto wa nai
I will never give up​
Saigo made
Until the end​
Get down, let's get down​
Kokoro no hikari wo oboeteru uchi ni
While I still remember the light in my heart​
GET HOME
Trust yourself
Don't deny
Save yourself
Don't forget
Sold cheaper than a scouring pad
Well, one of the original Saturn RPGs
was placed in second.
Oh, I didn't play RPG at all.
What?
The beginning went okay.
You need salt
to kill slugs !!!
But I couldn't remember what I did the day before...
You need salt
to kill slugs !!!
Why do I need salt...?
But I couldn't remember what I did the day before...
You need salt
to kill slugs !!!
Why do I need salt...?
But I couldn't remember what I did the day before...
You need salt
to kill slugs !!!
Why do I need salt...?
But I couldn't remember what I did the day before...
You need salt
to kill slugs !!!
Why do I need salt...?
But I couldn't remember what I did the day before...
You need salt
to kill slugs !!!
Why do I need salt...?
But I couldn't remember what I did the day before...
You need salt
to kill slugs !!!
Why do I need salt...?
But I couldn't remember what I did the day before...
You need salt
to kill slugs !!!
Why do I need salt...?
But I couldn't remember what I did the day before...
and got lost.
Did you?
Speaking of, I had an encounter like
an RPG game in the other world.
What?
Icuras elran.
You fucking orc. I won't lose to a fugly pig like you.
What is this?
Ah, this was right after I arrived at the village.
Let's fast-forward it.
Uncle, whenever you got to a village,
you found yourself in a battle.
Well, in the flame shrine
at the west end of the village,
the legendary blaze dragon has roused.
The village will be burned down
if we don't do anything.
The only way to slay the blaze dragon
is using the Ice clan's god freezing sword.
However, the descendant of the Ice clan
is a bit of a pain in the neck.
Her name is Mabel.
Unless we melt the ice, trapping her heart,
we can't break the seal of the god freezing sword.
When I was little,
I saw powa-powa blossoms
with my mom at the top of Mount Marchid.
That was beautiful.
I went straight to the shrine of flame
and slew the legendary blaze dragon.
How come?
Seriously, it was hard.
But I killed it after I got
its offensive strategy down.
Not like that!
You should've gone to Mount Marchid
for powa-powa blossoms.
I couldn't remember that.
It's not that complicated.
What? You defeated the legendary blaze dragon?
Thank you very much.
They were so grateful.
Yeah.
I'll get it.
A Sega Saturn and 20 games.
Takafumi, was that a delivery?
Oh, well... this is...
It was a surprise gift for him,
but he just said we've got to start saving.
Here...
What?
Huh?
Is he happy or furious?
It's a bit early, but happy birthday, Uncle.
Oh, by the way...
I found Guardian Heroes.
Wanna play?
I worried in vain.
For my uncle, spending money
on a Sega console can't be a waste.
The town trampled down in
Alien Storm looked like this.
When it's this deserted and chilly,
I can feel the tension in the air.
Yeah.
It's totally different from
New Year's Eve in the other world.
What?
Uncle!
Do you want to know?
Yes.
"If aliens were to invade the earth now,
would you be an ordinary citizen
who runs for your life, or..."
That was the tagline of the game.
Players, as one of the Alien Busters—
Not the game!
Is that a comic?
Yeah.
I haven't spent New Year's Eve
reading a comic in a long time.
Can you follow the story after a 17-year break?
KochiKame would follow the same plot all the time.
KochiKame's serialization is over.
Really?
I never thought it would end.
You won't find it.
I'm more interested in the story
of the other world than the comic.
It's not on the contents page either!
Seriously?
Icuras elran.
It's not a big deal, but it's something like
a New Year's Eve party.
It's a thanksgiving festival
for the gods' protection against winter.
The lord would feed you a splendid dinner.
Cheers!
That's some feast.
The residents of the other world
were pumped up for this festival.
For the festival, I also...
All right everyone, we gonna have a great time!
Yeah!
Well, I wish I could have been like that.
I couldn't be a totally different person
than who I actually was.
I ate alone and went back to my room.
What?
Ah, it was great! The roast chicken—
I'm not talking about the food.
Was that all for the festival?
Yeah.
Where was she? The tsun—
The bad-mouthing girl?
She wasn't there, and nothing happened after that.
D-Do you wanna play on the Saturn?
Sure, let's do that!
Pew pew! Pew pew!
You'll break the buttons.
By the way, Mabel came to my room after the festival.
Ah, the protector of the god freezing sword.
Now, the battle begins!
I want to hear about that!
I-I thought we finally finished talking—
Hurry up!
Well... nothing really happened.
See?
Icuras Elron
Del storba rabelt gal
War-grent seld grakka
Icuras Elron
Del storba rabelt gal
War-grent seld grakka
Icuras Elron
Del storba rabelt gal
War-grent seld grakka
Spirits of memory, investigate now.
I set out on a warm, hospitable journey.
Gale transport blade!
Spirits of memory, investigate now.
I set out on a warm, hospitable journey.
Gale transport blade!
Spirits of memory, investigate now.
I set out on a warm, hospitable journey.
Gale transport blade!
Why are you here?
I wanted you to tell me.
You slew the dragon single-handedly.
I want to be strong like you.
How can I stop being a coward?
"Stop being a coward"?
Who said that you are a coward?
What?
Who said that?
Th-The village mayor.
Live your life the way you want to,
not by trying to meet someone else's expectations.
Sticking to that principle
is strength.
Great.
That's so cool, Uncle.
Mabel being like this!
Like this, Uncle must have gradually
built relationships in the other world.
How have you spent your life until now?
I-I've been a recluse, and closed off my heart.
That's fine.
What? But...
That's completely fine.
No matter what people said,
I never gave up being a Sega player,
and I never will.
Is your role to be an ordinary citizen
who buys a popular console?
Or...
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Incredible!
She chose her life and went back home.
I'm so happy to stay reclusive.
Oh, and she offered me the sword.
Please keep the god freezing sword.
No thanks. It's too cold.
Okay...
But, I declined the offer.
Well, that's about it.
Uncle, do you want a bowl of soba noodles?
Oh, that's a good idea!
Let's boil the water!
What did you do on New Year's Eve
when you were a student? Play games?
Well, I usually watched the
It's Okay to Laugh! holiday special.
It was a special occasion
as students couldn't watch daytime shows.
That show ended too.
Seriously? How is that possible?
Well, it's been 17 years. No wonder.
But it was still on until three years ago.
It lasted that long? That's awesome!
KochiKame ended last year.
What?
What kind of shows do you like, Takafumi?
I don't think you've watched it,
but Not Okay to Laugh.
No way! What happened with Tamori?
Nah, it's not the sequel.
It seems like he watched a lot of TV.
Playing games, chatting, and slurping soba...
that's how the new year rolled in.
January, 2018
The breeze you just made was quite sharp.
Let's keep it that way all day today.
No way, there you go again.
I should avoid this street from now on.
Fujimiya?
Takafumi?
I thought so!
You can't be this tall!
I had a growth spurt in high school.
It's been such a long time!
Yeah.
How are you doing these days?
A lot happened, and I'm working part-time.
I see. I'm going to college.
It's chilly.
Did you wanna stop by my place? It's close by.
Your parents' house?
No.
I'll come by after dropping off the groceries.
Okay, I'll send you the address.
30 minutes later
Takafumi?
Takafumi
I'm grabbing some snacks,
go inside without me.
The door's unlocked
Takafumi
I'm grabbing some snacks,
go inside without me.
The door's unlocked
Takafumi
I'm grabbing some snacks,
go inside without me.
The door's unlocked
Takafumi
I'm grabbing some snacks,
go inside without me.
The door's unlocked
Takafumi
I'm grabbing some snacks,
go inside without me.
The door's unlocked
I'm coming in!
Stonagas resto rarbarum.
Icuras cuora.
Icuras cuora. Icuras cuora!
Wait, gotta use Japanese.
Spirits of memory, deliver unto oblivion—
Uncle!
Takafumi. Enemy. She saw it.
Erase. Erasing her memory faster,
means less impact on her mind.
My friend! She's my friend!
A... friend?
Thank you for being friends with Takafumi.
Well, that was...
I cast in Granbahamal lingo.
Like a dialect?
So, Takafumi is supporting an uncle
who hasn't worked for 17 years.
I'm a YouTuber.
I saw him mumbling to himself out there!
Occasionally, I chat
with spirits to sharpen my magic skills.
He's seriously crazy!
Yes, it's crazy.
Because he returned from another world and does magic.
I practice magic and my YouTube channel showcases it.
Then do the goddamn magic now!
Well I can't do it for free.
I'm a YouTuber with two million views.
Right?
Yeah.
What's with the professional attitude?
Anyway, you shouldn't hinder Takafumi's life anymore.
Oh, I see.
You like Takafumi.
No, no, no, no, no. It's not that.
100% not happening. We're just friends.
That shouldn't be the case. I understand adult romance.
I watched the entire Evangelion series
when I was in junior high.
You watched Eva?
Indeed. Everyone did.
At the time, Sega was one of
the sponsors of Evangelion.
Of course it's because of Sega.
Well, then you know Asuka too?
The girl in the red suit, right?
Oh, shit!
Uncle may catch on to the tsundere concept!
Don't you misunderstand. You're indebted to me now.
T-That's not what I meant.
I didn't mean "together forever" or anything weird!
He may realize what that elfin girl really meant.
Did you know?
Actually, Asuka has a crush on Kaji.
Ah, sorry Takafumi, you may be too inexperienced
to have noticed her crush on Kaji.
What? Yeah.
Such superficial
comprehension...!!
Stop fooling around already.
Don't make assumptions based on
an cartoon's views on love.
You're right.
Let's talk about real love.
Her name was Nanase Kaede.
Her will was destroyed by the enemy,
and she was no longer herself.
In battle, her affection turned into murderous intent.
However, after a long battle,
she felt a positive response.
Joy.
She found herself under the blinding explosions.
"Who did I kill?"
"What did I lose?"
There is no such a thing as "too early"
to express your affection.
Oh, my God.
The difference in his understanding of cartoons and games is scary.
Hey, Fujimiya.
What?
That was just a story from a video game.
A vide—
It's made up?
Huh? Made up?!
I experienced it firsthand.
You, shut your...
Spirits of memory, investigate now.
"Geez, he has a roommate.
I feel stupid for getting psyched and changing my outfit."
What?
True, you got changed.
No, it's the same clothes!
Hmm, you even took a shower.
No, I didn't!
Oh, who's there?
A mind reader, or con man?
What are you?
I'm just an uncle...
back from another world—
Mr. Shibazaki, I got a package for you.
Mr. Shibazaki?
All right, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Cut him off, Takafumi.
Seriously, you need to get out.
If you can't afford the rent,
I'll get a job and help cover it!
Seriously? You want to be my roommate?
What?
I see, that's definitely an option.
Well, I didn't mean that—
But, I've got my uncle with me.
What's in here, it weighs 15 kilograms!
Ah, it's a bag of rice.
Rice?
Can you accept a scribbled signature?
One additional person now knows my uncle in real life.
He looks somewhat more cheerful than his usual self.
Also, I held back on buying rice online for a while.
I could sense a murderous aura.
​​Nagaku nobita kage
​​I saw you off with a "see you"
Jaa ne tte miokutta
And watched as your shadow lengthened
Dou shite kizukanai no
Why don't you notice me?
Konna ni mitsumeteiru no ni
I've been staring at you for so long
Ienai omoi ga
I can't express my emotions
Yukiba sagashite
I'm searching for a place to go​
Nijimu orenji ni
The orange blur
Sotto nobotta
Gently rises in the distance
Kanadeyou
I dance alone
Chiisana chiisana hoshi no inori
And pray to a tiny, tiny star​ ​​
Mada tooi sono sora
The star that's so far away in the sky
Itsuka terashitai
Someday it will shine bright
Todoketai todokanai
I need to make it clear, you need to understand
Itoshisa sono bun dake
My love for you that's so strong
Taema naku matataku yo
The stars shine
Tada hitori no kimi e
Only for you