Year 845:
The Colossal Titan and Armored Titan appear out of thin air,
reducing our ordinary lives, along with the wall, to rubble.
Stop!
Wall Maria was abandoned.
And with a fifth of its population and a third of its land lost,
mankind had its territory reduced to Wall Rose.
However, not all of mankind has given in to the Titans.
The Garrison continues to work on strengthening the walls...
...and young recruits continue to be trained in the art of killing Titans.
It was at this time that...
Year 850
In Trost District,
the Survey Corps' forces were preparing to set foot in the Titans' territory once more.
Thirty seconds until the gate opens!
All troops, prepare to move out!
Oh man, I'm so excited...
Hey, Levi.
Not a chance.
I haven't even said anything yet.
You want me to help you capture a Titan.
That'd be a major pain in the ass for me.
What about you, Miike?
You in?
As always, dull answers from dull men.
We will now begin our 49th expedition outside the walls!
Move out!
Woohoo!
Hange!
Hey, Titans!
I'm coming to meet you!
They're the prey, and we're the hunters.
S
ie sind das Essen und wir sind die Jäger
ie
sind
sind
die
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Ignorant of the
F
umareta hana no
trampled flower's name,
N
amae mo shirazu ni
the bird that fell to the earth
C
hi ni ochita tori wa
waits impatiently for the wind.
K
aze wo machiwabiru
Even if you pray,
I
notta tokoro de
nothing will be changed.
N
animo kawaranai
But that which can alter the present
I
ma wo kaeru no wa
is the resolution to fight.
T
atakau kakugo da
Trampling over corpses,
S
hikabane fumikoete
swine who mock the will to advance.
S
usumu ishi wo warau buta yo
Peace of the cattle,
K
achiku no annei
and the prosperity of deception.
K
yogi no hanei
The freedom of the dead, hungry wolf.
S
hiseru garou no jiyuu wo
Our caged humiliation
T
orawareta kutsujoku wa
signals the start of our retaliation.
H
angeki no koushi da
Beyond the ramparts,
J
ouheki no sono kanata
we're hunters that slaughter our prey.
E
mono wo hofuru Jäger
As these surging urges
H
otobashiru shoudou ni
burn away our bodies,
S
ono mi wo yaki nagara
we ignite the dusk with
T
asogare ni hi wo ugatsu
a crimson bow and arrow.
G
uren no yumiya
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Ilse's Notebook
————— Memoirs of a Survey Corps Member —————
Just wait a minute, Erwin!
I get that building a military logistics base is our top priority this time out,
but uncovering the Titans' true nature is the Survey Corps' primary objective!
You know that as well as I do!
Excuse me, Captain...
I don't think you should be raising your voice at the commander...
Shut it!
To achieve our goals, we absolutely must capture a Titan!
I understand that I'm being unrealistic.
The last time we caught one was over fifteen years ago,
and we lost more than twenty men in the process.
But if the fear of losing men paralyzes us, we'll never obtain any information!
Move more soldiers to the rear.
Yes, sir.
I've already told you...
We don't have the manpower to capture a titan.
We've already lost more than ten men just getting here.
I know that, but—
Hange.
The answer is no.
H-Hey...
Wait, Erwin!
He was never going to agree to it, Hange.
It's already hard enough to kill those monsters.
If we're gonna try capturing one, we'll have to become immortal first.
Hypothetically...
Let's say that, hypothetically, Levi's trying to kill you.
Kill you dead!
What would you do?
Can you fight and beat him?
No way.
That'd be impossible.
Also, I can't breathe.
Let me tell you how to win.
You do the research.
You figure out where he goes, the food he dislikes,
the girls he likes, and how often he goes to the bathroom each day.
You figure out everything about him.
Then, you find something you can exploit.
If you don't fight that way, you'll definitely...
be killed.
Hange!
Captain, you're overdoing it!
Oops, sorry.
But that's what I'm getting at.
Captain!
Shit, I almost died there.
She's one crazy bitch.
Clinically insane.
You realize...
you're a member of the Survey Corps, so at least try to stop talking like a wimp, okay?
What?
Who are you to tell me that?!
Petra, are you done with the resupply?
O-Oh, Eld!
Almost done, sir!
The forest!
They're here!
Stay alert, men!
Captain, it's dangerous to go out alone!
Erwin, I'm going!
Wait, Hange!
Levi!
God, what an idiot.
Found one!
Hey, nice weather today, isn't it?
Good boy.
Hey, want to join me for a stroll inside the walls?
What do you say?
That was close!
Oh dear...
You okay?
Follow me!
All right, good boy.
This way, moron.
H-Hey, don't interfere!
Good boy.
Keep coming this way.
Huh?
What?
Hey!
Hey, wait up!
Where are you going?
What the hell's that dumbass doing?
Going back home?
It's acting strange, even for an Abnormal.
Yeah, its behavior is unlike anything we've seen so far.
No, acting strange is what makes it an Abnormal.
Who cares?
We're killing it.
Hey, wait up!
Does it have a specific destination in mind?
It might be an Abnormal, but is it really possible for a Titan to go to a specific place?
What?
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Is this where...
you wanted to go?
That was close!
What?
What's wrong?
I'm listening.
I've got the shot!
Oluo, wait!
Huh?
Damn.
You alive?
Captain...
I'll serve you for the rest of my life!
It would've been...
such a valuable specimen.
If we could've captured it, mankind might've been able to make some progress.
Shut your stupid mouth, four-eyes!
If you want to be turned into Titan feces, then be my guest.
But leave the rest of our men out of it!
Titans don't have bowel movements...
they don't have a digestive system.
Um...
Captain?
What?
Did the... T-Titan do that?
But there's... no way...
What are you babbling about?
The 34th expedition's emblem.
The body's been in here for a year.
A name's coming to me...
Ilse... Langnar?
Unbelievable.
To think a Titan would do this...
Levi?
What's that?
This is...
Ilse Langnar's legacy.
Currently
Disclosable
Information
The Biology of Titans ①
No historical documents contain any
information regarding the Titans' origin,
making the subject a near-total mystery.
The Biology of Titans ①
No historical documents contain any
information regarding the Titans' origin,
making the subject a near-total mystery.
Currently
Disclosable
Information
The Biology of Titans ②
The Titans are driven by one thing: their desire to eat
humans. However, the data suggests that they don't
eat for sustenance, but simply in order to kill.
The Biology of Titans ②
The Titans are driven by one thing: their desire to eat
humans. However, the data suggests that they don't
eat for sustenance, but simply in order to kill.
My name is Ilse Langnar.
I was involved in the 34th
expedition outside the walls,
as part of the Second Brigade on the leftmost rank of the formation.
We encountered Titans on our return route.
I lost both my horse and my fellow soldiers.
I also discarded my malfunctioning 3D Maneuver Gear.
I'm running north.
I lost my horse in the world outside the walls.
I can't escape from the Titans on foot.
I've lost all of my comrades.
Forget getting home...
even survival seems impossible.
However, I may be able to reach the wall.
I have a plan.
The key is to not give in to fear.
I was prepared for this the moment I volunteered for the Survey Corps.
I bear the wings of freedom, which do not fear death.
I am a Survey Corps soldier.
Even if I'm as good as dead, I'll fight to the bitter end.
I don't have any weapons, but I can fight!
I'll record every moment in this notebook,
and do everything I can.
I will not give up.
I will not...
give up!
I...
I will not...
give up.
I've encountered a Titan.
A 7— No, more like a 6-meter class.
It hasn't eaten me yet.
Is it an Abnormal?
I now stare death in the face.
This is the end for me.
I lived only for myself.
I haven't done anything for my parents yet.
I feel sick.
I'm a goner.
Subject... of... Ymir.
It...
spoke?
The Titan spoke.
Impossible.
Lady Ymir.
It's an honor.
Its words make sense.
"Subject of Ymir."
"Lady Ymir."
"It's an honor."
I'm certain of it.
This Titan's expression has changed.
It's paying its respects to me.
Unbelievable.
Probably for the first time in history,
a human is communicating with a Titan.
Wh-What are you?
I ask for the reason of their existence.
It moans.
No reply.
Where are you from?
I ask about their origin.
No response.
Why do you eat us?
I ask for their objective.
Why do you eat us?!
You don't need to eat to live!
So why?!
You're just a giant useless lump of flesh!
Vanish from this world!
What?
What's...
No!
I'm caught! I'm done. Big mouth. It smells.
Many teeth. Not sharp.
Breath is warm. Waiting alone is—
Dear Erwin Smith,
I am writing this letter to propose we resume the operation to capture Titans.
I hope my reasons become evident when you read the notebook I've attached.
The notebook simply tells us one thing:
we know absolutely nothing about the Titans.
The Titan Ilse Langnar met spoke meaningful words...
and acted respectfully toward her.
Furthermore, it didn't completely devour Ilse,
but instead, stored her corpse in the hollow of a tree.
That appears to be the course of events.
This is the first time in history that mankind has observed this phenomenon.
Ilse used every last ounce of her life to obtain this information,
and we have a responsibility to make something of it.
We must follow her example and never halt our efforts to uncover more about the Titans.
We must carry on her will.
No matter how little information we may obtain,
it will never be for naught.
It will definitely...
help us later down the line in our counterattack.
I believe that wholeheartedly.
Second Squadron Captain, Hange Zoë.
Um...
Hange...
Are you stalking me?
Well, it's good to have a hobby.
About the other day, um...
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't messed up, we could've captured that Titan.
If we'd done that, we would've obtained valuable information.
In the grand scheme of things, my life isn't worth any—
No, I should be the one apologizing.
I almost got you killed.
I'm sorry.
But don't ever say that your life isn't worth anything.
Okay?
Huh?
A-Are you okay?!
Oluo!
Stop fooling around!
Oh, yeah...
Erwin's approved the operation.
He has?
Yahoo!
Twenty days later...
Captain Hange Zoë succeeded in the first capture of a Titan since the fall of Wall Maria,
with the help of Captain Levi's Special Ops Squad.
The operation used a new trapping method proposed by Hange,
and not a single casualty was taken.
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
It's more fragile than a life.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Now, sleep in peace.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
My pulsing urges
myakuutsu shoudou ni
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
trample upon my wishes.
negai wa okasare
As often as I sadly forget,
wasureteshimau hodo
I remember once again.
mata omoidasu yo
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
nani wo mamoru no darou
when a reason ceases to exist.
mou risei nado nai naraba