Once we retake Wall Maria
and defeat all our enemies out there...
Will the lives we had before ever come back?
We'll bring them back.
But some things are gone forever.
We just have to make them pay for that.
What will Eren do after that?
He might leave us behind again
to go somewhere far away.
But
I won't have the power to stop him.
As I was thinking somber thoughts,
a memory suddenly flashed through my mind.
A memory from long ago...
This embroidery pattern has been passed down our family for generations.
If you have children someday, teach it to them.
How do you have children?
Well, you should ask your father.
Hey, Dad.
Uh, well, Dad isn't so sure, either.
Ah right, Dr. Jaeger will be here soon, so why don't we ask him?
Oh, looks like he's here already.
Mikasa, it will be even more beautiful if you add some color to this part.
Dr. Jaeger, we've been wait-
Why, hello there.
I'm sorry, Mikasa.
Eren died in my stead...
I... couldn't do anything...
I'm sorry.
If this reality no longer pleases you,
you have the power to redo everything.
Just choose where you'd like to start.
In your own world, you can shape reality however you please.
However, you still won't be able to stop Eren's death.
Because Eren...
If you have children someday, teach it to them.
Oh, looks like he's here already.
Thanks for coming out here in the rain.
Please, come in.
Doctor!
Hello. Thanks for having me.
And good afternoon to you, Mikasa.
Good afternoon.
Come on in, Eren. Don't be shy.
He-Hello.
Hello.
This is my son, Eren.
He's nine years old, same as you.
He only has one friend back home.
Think you two can get along?
Yes.
They said your mom was going to have a baby.
Yeah. Mom said she can tell it's going to be a boy.
Because it feels completely different from when I was inside her.
Well, if she's right about that,
I hope he makes a good soldier.
A soldier?
Are you going to be a soldier, Eren?
Yeah! I'm going to join the Survey Corps and go see the outside world.
What's the outside world?
The world beyond the walls.
I'll need to go through training to be able to kill the Titans out there.
What about you?
Me?
Your dad is a hunter and your mom grows vegetables.
What are you going to do?
I...
I don't really know.
H-Hey, let's go back, Eren.
My dad tells me not to go too deep into the woods.
Wait!
We went back to the house
and told them about the wild dogs and the three people they'd killed.
I'm going to contact the Military Police.
Thank you.
See you later.
Yeah.
After that, whenever Doctor Jaeger came to visit, Eren was with him.
We didn't go back into the woods.
Sometimes,
Eren would tell me what it was like living in Shiganshina with his friend Armin.
Armin is really smart.
He knows a whole lot of things 'cause he's always reading.
Oh, do you think he knows how to make children?
Huh?
Even I know that.
Really?
A stork carrying a baby comes to the house at night
and puts the baby inside the mother.
How could a stork carry a baby?
The baby rides on its back.
Wouldn't it fall off?
Oh, I guess...
Anyways.
Armin knows a lot of things.
He's the one who told me about the outside world.
And one day, I'm going out there to see it with him.
That's my dream.
What happened to you?
In the outside world, there's a huge lake filled with salty water called the ocean.
You'd think merchants would take all the salt right away, to sell it.
But that's impossible.
The ocean is so big that it can't be depleted.
Probably too big for us to even imagine it.
Fiery water, lands of ice, snowy deserts...
All that and more is waiting outside the walls.
It's many times bigger than anything we've ever known.
But those guys still...
Who?
They're cowards.
They think all that matters is that it's peaceful inside the walls.
So they think it's stupid to go out there where it's dangerous.
Armin told them that one day humanity would have to leave the walls.
And they called him a heretic.
That's the kind of world we live in.
It's full of cowards who will never accept change.
People like them who want us to stay trapped in here forever.
Eren?
I'm going to join the Survey Corps and go to the outside world!
If Eren went home like that,
I knew he might end up in an even worse fight and get hurt even worse.
But
there was nothing I could do to stop him.
That's why
I wanted to at least be there with him.
I need to take this to Dr. Jaeger?
You can come back with him the next time he visits.
Until then, you can have fun playing with Eren.
Eren!
Oh! Hurry, come see this!
The Survey Corps is back!
Damn it, I can't see.
Moses? Moses!
Excuse me, I don't see my son, Moses...
Where can I find him?
It's Moses' mother.
Bring it over.
That's all we were able to recover.
Are you joining the Survey Corps?
Are you really planning to join them?
Yes.
No. I don't want you to!
How many failures is it now?
Those Corpsmen are worthless.
What a real mess.
Tell me about it.
All this shows is that our taxes are being spent fattening them up for nothing.
What's your problem, you damn brat?!
Hey, let me go! Let go!
W-Wait...
Don't insult the Survey Corps!
Whoa there, he's just a kid.
Oh, spare me! I'm doing this brat a favor by teaching him his lesson while he's still young.
How's that?
How long was I out?
It hasn't been long.
Currently Disclosable Information
Ferry Boat
These boats travel between human territories by
moving along steel cables installed above rivers,
using the same compressed air that powers 3D Maneuver
Gear. They frequently transport passengers, cargo,
and military supplies, and have a capacity of 150 tonnes.
Many of the inhabitants of Shiganshina used them to
evacuate to Trost during the attack in 845.
Ferry Boat
These boats travel between human territories by
moving along steel cables installed above rivers,
using the same compressed air that powers 3D Maneuver
Gear. They frequently transport passengers, cargo,
and military supplies, and have a capacity of 150 tonnes.
Many of the inhabitants of Shiganshina used them to
evacuate to Trost during the attack in 845.
Please.
Please let me see Eren.
It appears to be pre-eclampsia.
I'd like you to move closer to where I live for now.
Just as a precaution in case anything more serious develops.
I see.
Hey there!
What's going on?
Mom. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Why did you stop coming to my house?
The Survey Corps is gone.
They had too many missions fail,
so they were disbanded.
They even sealed up the gate.
It's impossible to leave now.
Those cowards are trying to trap us all in here.
Does that mean you'll give up on—
Armin and I are going to leave this place in a hot air balloon.
It's a balloon big enough to lift people into the sky.
And we're building it ourselves.
That's why I haven't been going to your house.
Sorry.
When are you leaving?
In three days.
I want to go too.
What?
Take me with you.
Please.
Take me with you!
Go through the inner gate and walk until you get to a forest.
I'll wait for you there
three days from now, at night.
Give the scarf back then.
Okay.
This has been a long time coming.
You can say that again!
They should have sealed it up sooner, if you ask me.
Don't be late.
We'll leave the third time the bell rings.
Two more!
Attention, ladies and gentlemen!
I, the greatest hypnotist, the extraordinary mirror man,
will now dazzle you with my hypnotic powers!
Feast your eyes as I turn this sweet little girl into a cold-blooded murderer!
Let's begin, young lady.
Have a look at my face.
Um, please let me go.
If I were to release your hand, where would you be off to?
I'm going to meet my friend.
I see.
We should do this quickly, then.
It's best not to keep friends waiting.
Thanks.
But for now, the show must go on.
After all, I promised to make a murderer out of you with my hypnosis.
To that end, I have a proposal for you.
How about you kill me right now?
I could have you kill someone with hypnosis, yes,
but it would take some time.
And you don't have time to spare, do you?
Um, someone, help!
How unfortunate. You can't possibly make it there in time now.
Your friend will leave you behind.
Do you know Eren?
Who are you?
I am nobody,
but I can be anybody.
And I know all there is to know about hypnosis.
You are a lost child.
You became lost in this world of your own volition.
It is a world that exists only because of your inability to accept Eren's death.
However, in this world and any other you might create,
Eren's death is an inevitability you will never escape.
Because Eren is marked by the specter of death.
All of your efforts to protect him
are certain to be in vain.
If you doubt my words, you can confirm the truth with your own eyes.
But only after you kill me.
You have to become stronger and then return to the real world.
Why are you trying to stop me?
All I want is to be with Eren.
That's all I want.
Why?
This is simply the reality of the world and its cruelty.
If that's how the world is, it can...
Well, ladies and gentlemen, did you enjoy the show?
Your very own mirror man has just transformed a sweet young girl into a murderer.
As you can see, this blade is retractable and perfectly harmless.
And the blood spilled from my body is fake as well.
However,
the fact that this girl stabbed me is an unshakable truth that the Titans themselves cannot challenge!
I certainly hope everyone had fun.
This concludes the performance of the extraordinary hypnotist, the mirror man!
Thank you, thank you, everyone!
Are you...
Mikasa?
Um, where is Eren?
I'm sorry, Mikasa.
It's all my fault.
The balloon went out of control right after liftoff.
Then Eren pushed me outside to safety.
But he couldn't get himself out in time,
and the balloon went straight into the wall...
Eren sacrificed himself for me.
I couldn't do anything.
I'm sorry!
My mind was completely empty
except for the feeling that I had just had an exceptionally long dream.
A dream of happiness and sadness.
And when I woke up,
I accepted what had happened to Eren as a solemn fact.
I know Eren will retake Wall Maria,
wipe out every last Titan,
and then get to see the ocean with his own eyes.
But even then,
I don't think it will be possible to stop him from moving forward.
And I won't have...
No,
nobody will have the power to stop him.
But that's okay.
No matter where Eren goes,
I want to be by his side.
That is my one and only wish.
Hey,
Eren.
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
It's more fragile than a life.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Now, sleep in peace.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
My pulsing urges
myakuutsu shoudou ni
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
trample upon my wishes.
negai wa okasare
As often as I sadly forget,
wasureteshimau hodo
I remember once again.
mata omoidasu yo
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
nani wo mamoru no darou
when a reason ceases to exist.
mou risei nado nai naraba