Hey! Hold it right there!
Dammit! It's them again!
Someone get the Military Police!
Yahoo!
Levi! They're here!
Our pursuers!
Hmph! The Military Police, huh?
They never learn!
Bro Levi! Was that a cool line or what?!
Are you dense?
I'm surprised they keep sending their best after us.
The underground merchants must've
crossed their palms with silver.
Probably, considering we helped ourselves to
a generous donation from their vault!
All we did was stop those
fat cats from getting even fatter!
They should be grateful!
Furlan, Isabel.
Let's go!
The underground city...
It lies below the safest region, protected by all three walls, where only the chosen live.
It is the remnants of a failed
underground repopulation plan.
For those who lived in the shadow
of the capital, it was not uncommon
that they would die without ever seeing the light of day.
Wohlan, Freund!
Woh
lan,
Freund!
Well, friend!
lan,
Freund!
Jetzt hier ist ein Sieg.
Jetzt
hier
ist
ein
Sieg.
Victory stands before us.
hier
ist
ein
Sieg.
Dies ist die erste Glorie.
Dies
ist
die
erste
Glo
ri
e.
Our legend begins now.
ist
die
erste
Glo
ri
e.
O, mein Freund!
O,
mein
Freund!
O, my friend!
mein
Freund!
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
Sieg
für
den
näch
sten
Kampf!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
ern
wir
die
sen
Sieg
für
den
näch
sten
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
Kampf!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
battle!
I won't let you say, "My death is meaningless."
Not until but a single arrow remains.
≪一矢≫
The enemy is cruel... But we'll prevail.
Der
Feind
ist
grau
sam...
Wir
brin
gen.
ma
de
Der
Feind
ist
grau
de
sam...
Wir
brin
gen.
The enemy is titanic... So we'll jump.
Der
Feind
ist
rie
sig...
Wir
sprin
gen.
Der
Feind
ist
rie
sig...
Wir
sprin
gen.
Bearing steel blades of glory, we sing an anthem of victory.
Sieg
≪鋼刃≫
Sieg
≪凱歌≫
On our backs are the Wings of Liberty.
Sieg
Frei
heit
≪自由の翼≫
gel
der
Frei
heit
On our chests are our fists, tightly clenched with determination.
The screw of folly rips through.
heit
≪愚行の螺旋≫
gen
der
Tor
heit
Wings of Liberty dance in the blue sky.
sou
kyuu
Frei
heit
sou
kyuu
wo
ma
u
Flü
≪自由の翼≫
gel
der
Frei
heit
A Choice With No Regrets
————— Part 1 —————
Here. Sorry I kept you waiting.
This is for the last job, and the one before.
Here.
Oh, thank—
Now, don't go spending it all at once, you hear?
People will get suspicious.
We know!
Let's go.
Sure.
Work's been a helluva lot easier since we got our hands on this 3D Maneuver Gear.
Now we can pay our guys more.
Seems to me one of them got a little too much.
Got an explanation?
His...
You've probably noticed that
Jan's leg has been getting worse.
Meds are pretty expensive.
They've gone up in price recently too.
Those scumbag shysters...
Did you hear the toll on the stairways went up?
Yeah.
At this rate, bottom-feeders like us will never see daylight.
They've claimed the stairways for themselves, so they set their fees as they see fit.
Even if you pay to get above ground,
it won't mean shit without papers.
You'll just get sent back down.
Apparently, the lack of sunlight is the reason all those guys got messed-up legs.
It's not like you can do anything about it.
Your mother was like that too.
I guess that's why.
Nevertheless, you still gave him too much.
It was his severance pay.
He's done for.
At the very least, he can find himself a good hospital.
Is that so...
How much more would we need...
to live up there?
Ow...
Oh, it's just a kid.
You gave us a real fright.
I'm not a kid!
I'm not...
a kid!
Is that so? So that means I can kick you out and it won't leave a bad taste in my mouth, right?
I'll forgive you for dirtying the floor.
Now piss off.
What's the matter? Can't move?
I can!
Don't underestimate me!
Aren't we the feisty one?
Over here!
Damn. You were being chased, weren't you?
What should we do?
That little brat...
Can't believe she bit me that hard.
Once we catch her, lemme have a little fun with her.
What fun can you have with a brat like that?
Huh?
Hey! A dirty little urchin came this way, right?
They're ten a penny here, pal.
What?!
You shitheads from around here?
Says this guy.
Hey.
Found her.
Thought so. You friends with her?
Nope.
Hand her over, then.
Try protecting her and you're in for a world of hurt.
After all, she tried to go up the 11th Stairway without paying.
You know the one, right?
The 11th is in Government
Minister Lobov's jurisdiction.
We can't let that slide, not even for a kid.
Of course, you two will be charged for harboring her too.
If you understand, then hand her over!
Fine. Move aside!
Don't touch me with your filthy hands.
You'll make my clothes dirty.
Oh my...
You can't just stroll in here.
We take hygiene very seriously here.
Come back after you've washed your hands.
These guys mean business.
Let's get outta here!
Hey, how long are you going to cling on to that for?
It's going to die.
I thought that'd warm it up.
Where'd you get that bird?
It was flying about.
Probably came in via the sewers.
So I thought I'd let it free above ground.
You tried to go up the stairway for that?
This little guy probably prefers soaring the skies instead of wandering the underground city.
That's fine and dandy, but this bird's hurt its wing.
Huh?
For real?
You're something else.
Oh, right.
What's your name? I'm Isabel.
I'm Farlan and that's Levi.
Farlan, and, Bro?
Bro?
Please let me join you!
Huh?
You guys use 3D Maneuver Gear, right?
I've seen you in action.
Seeing you guys fly free like birds made me jealous.
I want to try it too!
What should we do?
Hey!
If you're going to stay here, learn how to clean before learning to use the 3D Maneuver Gear.
Thank you, Bro!
Die Stühle liegen sehr eng
Our chairs sit so close to each other,
Wir reden die ganze Nacht lang
and we talk all night long.
Dieser niedrige Raum ist nicht schlecht
This humble room isn't so bad...
Wir können uns gut verstehen
as we get along well together.
So ist es immer, unser Licht ist nur das
That has always been the only light for us.
Trinken und singen wir, begrüßen morgen
Singing and drinking, we greet the sunrise.
So ist es immer, unterm riesigen Himmel
That's how it's always been under the vastness of the sky.
Leben wir zusammen, die Nacht ist lang
Let's live here together. The night is long.
Currently Disclosable Information
The Underground City
Built as part of an underground colony to avoid Titans.
However, it turned into a slum for criminals and the
destitute after the project was scrapped.
Since its residents rarely get sunlight, many of them
develop crippling leg conditions as a consequence.
The Underground City
Built as part of an underground colony to avoid Titans.
However, it turned into a slum for criminals and the
destitute after the project was scrapped.
Since its residents rarely get sunlight, many of them
develop crippling leg conditions as a consequence.
What is it, old geezer?
You want something from us?
I need a job done.
You sure you didn't get the wrong address? We aren't handymen.
I assure you, the pay will be good.
Piss off.
I believe I have already put down a deposit for your services
You're kidding, right? This is the first time we've met.
That is true.
But I'm sure you will recognize the gentleman over there.
Jan!
His leg is severely impaired.
He must have it operated on in a hospital above ground.
I am correct, am I not, Levi?
What are you getting at?
I'll repeat myself.
That  is our deposit. Now will you hear me out?
Very well.
Are these the ones?
Yes. I've heard great things about them.
Who the hell are you?
I understand your wariness.
But you'll learn to trust me in time.
How so?
The fact that I've contacted you personally proves it.
I am risking quite a lot by being here.
Have you received my deposit?
I don't know what you call it above ground,
but it's called "taking a hostage" where we're from.
It's proof that your reward will be ample.
Do you understand?
Once you complete this job, not only will you be generously compensated for your work,
but you will also earn the right to live above ground.
Levi, we're ready to roll.
I've verified Jan's status. He's definitely been admitted to a top class hospital.
The man in the carriage's identity is legit, too.
This job is the real deal.
We're doing this, aren't we, Levi?
Let me say one thing...
Whether you accept this job or not,
the target will come into contact with you.
In other words, there's no getting around it.
Bro.
Just act natural. It's only when we come face-to-face with them like that bald geezer said,
that our job begins.
Hey, hey.
Hey there, boy.
Huh?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Hey! Hold it right there!
Those thieves are back! They've hit us again!
Somebody, call the Military Police!
Yahoo!
Levi! They're here!
Our pursuers!
Military Police, huh? When will they learn?
Yo, Bro! Was that line sweet or what?
Are you dense?
Those movements, they're not the Military Police!
Yeah, there's no mistaking it...
It's them.
Those Wings of Freedom crests...
The Survey Corps.
These soldiers must have experience fighting titans - they really are a cut above the rest.
You two! You know what to do.
Of course.
It's showtime, right?
Now then, let's see how good the Survey Corps are!
Don't even think about it. Look around you.
Let me go, asshole!
Goddammit!
Levi!
You're quick on your feet.
I will ask you a few questions.
Where did you obtain these?
You're all very skilled with three-dimensional maneuvers.
Who taught you how to use it?
I'm guessing you're their leader.
Have you undertaken squad training before?
Asshole!
I'll ask once more.
Where did you learn how to use 3D Maneuver Gear?
No one taught us! We taught ourselves!
You taught yourselves? That's hard to believe.
We did so to escape from this hellhole.
It's something that someone like you who's
basked in the sunlight would never understand.
Either way, take your filthy hands off my Bro!
Stop acting stuck up just because you're soldiers!
My name is Erwin Smith.
What is your name?
Levi.
Levi, I would like to make you a deal.
A deal?
We'll let you off the hook so long as you lend us your strength.
Join the Survey Corps.
And if I refuse?
You'll be handed over to the Military Police.
Considering the length of your rap sheet,
the Military Police will make your lives a living hell.
Make your decision.
Very well.
I'll join the Survey Corps.
If we were to assume that I'm not me,
tatoeba ore ga ore janai toshite
then could you be sure that you are you?
omae wa omae da to iikireru no ka
I shattered a vessel of sand, spilling its contents.
suna no utsuwa wo kowashite koboreta
Could you retrieve your heart and gather it all?
kokoro wo hirotte atsumerareru ka
The sound of others calling my name
dareka no yobu koe ga
is now all but noise to me.
miminari ni kawatta
It's as if time is standing still.
toki ga tomatta mitai da
Now, open your eyes.
saa me wo samase
I slipped out of the vast darkness,
fukai yami wo ore wa nukedashita
and fled from it as swiftly as a gale.
hayate mitai ni nigedashita
It's as if I was a living corpse.
ikita shikabane mitai datta
We now head beyond the walls.
oretachi wa kabe no soto e
Let us meet again in those uncharted lands.
mata aouze chizu ni nai basho de
No one could have forseen this outcome.
Together with Farlan and Isabel,
Levi joins the Survey Corps.
In order to accomplish a specific objective,
he readies himself for the 23rd reconnaissance mission.
A Choice With No Regrets
————— Part 2 —————