They're the prey, and we're the hunters.
S
ie sind das Essen und wir sind die Jäger
ie
sind
sind
die
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Ignorant of the
F
umareta hana no
trampled flower's name,
N
amae mo shirazu ni
the bird that fell to the earth
C
hi ni ochita tori wa
waits impatiently for the wind.
K
aze wo machiwabiru
Even if you pray,
I
notta tokoro de
nothing will be changed.
N
animo kawaranai
But that which can alter the present
I
ma wo kaeru no wa
is the resolution to fight.
T
atakau kakugo da
Trampling over corpses,
S
hikabane fumikoete
swine who mock the will to advance.
S
usumu ishi wo warau buta yo
Peace of the cattle,
K
achiku no annei
and the prosperity of deception.
K
yogi no hanei
The freedom of the dead, hungry wolf.
S
hiseru garou no jiyuu wo
Our caged humiliation
T
orawareta kutsujoku wa
signals the start of our retaliation.
H
angeki no koushi da
Beyond the ramparts,
J
ouheki no sono kanata
we're hunters that slaughter our prey.
E
mono wo hofuru Jäger
As these surging urges
H
otobashiru shoudou ni
burn away our bodies,
S
ono mi wo yaki nagara
we ignite the dusk with
T
asogare ni hi wo ugatsu
a crimson bow and arrow.
G
uren no yumiya
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
...and we're the hunters.
U
nd wir sind Jäger
nd
wir
sind
Jä
ger
Distress
In theory, our assignment was relatively straightforward.
Make it through the forest and get everyone home safe.
At least that was how...
it was meant to play out.
In this exercise,
the mission handed down to us, the 104th Training Corps,
was to split each squad into two groups,
retrieve an object that had been planted in a
specified location, and return to base with it.
A simple task covering a distance
of roughly 80 km in total.
Marco took the helm for our group.
I was made the scribe, tasked with recording every event.
The second group was led by
Thomas, with Mikasa as their scribe.
Both groups left the training camp at the same time and took separate paths encircling a large forest.
After exchanging information at our destination,
we were to return to the training
camp via the other group's route.
The point of the exercise was...
to see how alert we could stay in a non-threatening situation.
This exercise is a simple one!
You may think this will be a walk in the park, even for maggots like you.
Well, you're wrong!
Whether in battle or in peacetime,
a soldier is always a soldier!
Always retain your readiness
to fight, whatever the situation!
Do not surrender to boredom!
Do not let tranquility distract you!
This exercise is a battle in itself!
Do not forget that!
Sir!
Well...
it's better not to gallop all the way, right?
Uh, I guess...
You'll look a real idiot if you rush
on ahead and your horse gives out.
Let's just take it nice and slow.
Well, I'm not going to hold back.
Jean, if you're going to ride at
a snail's pace, I'm going on ahead.
Hey, Eren, wait up!
But we need to do this as a group...
What should we do, Jean?
Like I care.
It's not like taking this seriously
will get me into the Military Police.
You don't know that...
Anyway, for now, let's just focus on the exercise.
Not gonna happen.
Hey, it's too soon to give up.
Stop being such a baby.
So we're not even allowed to moan now?
It'd be fine if moaning made time go faster.
You said it...
The road ahead is a long one.
What a pain in the ass.
But if we go that way, we might
not make it there before sundown.
Well, how about taking a more easterly route?
Problem is, that route leaves us out roasting in the sun.
What's wrong, Mikasa?
Nothing...
I'm just being paranoid.
Tch, we've even got a lizard as a running buddy...
You don't see lizards too often.
They're really tasty.
Huh?
They are!
We used to eat them all the time back home.
They kinda taste like chicken.
You know how to cook them?
Of course!
It's easy.
All right then!
H-Hey!
They sent us on a glorified scavenger hunt, but I'd rather go lizard hunting any day!
Hey, stop!
I'll go after him.
Gotcha!
What are you doing?!
This isn't a game!
An exercise without an instructor isn't going to score us any brownie points!
Stop this!
Stop acting like children.
You're one to talk!
Jean! Just grin and bear it.
Why should I?
If we show up late, we'll end up having to report all of this.
Armin, please don't record any of this just yet.
S-Sure thing.
Just put down that Jean Kirstein was obstructed by Eren Jaeger while he was hunting for food.
What did you say?!
They're very tasty!
Huh?
Let's go.
Okay.
We could've fed the whole group with a lizard that size...
Are you sure?
There's no mistaking it.
I put them down here. When I came
to get them, they were all gone.
Our 3D Maneuver Gear...
Hey...
Whoever was here has been gone for a while.
I saw another one over there.
That tells us their numbers.
Also...
Look over here.
Wagon tracks...
And more than one set.
We weren't given any information
about anyone living out here.
Must be bandits.
Huh?
I've heard stories of gangs stealing military equipment,
then selling their haul on the black market.
3D Maneuver Gear fetches a high price.
Are you saying we were targeted?
If they'd seen us, they might've attacked.
We should consider ourselves lucky to be alive.
Do you think we'd better call off the
exercise and report back to base?
No, we're close to our objective.
We should hurry there and fill Marco's group in before we head back.
These rations are so bland.
We should've just caught that lizard.
Forget about that now. Lizards are dumb.
You're the one who went off chasing it.
It's more sensible than chasing Titans.
And what's that supposed to mean?
Why did you join the Training Corps?!
I'll tell you this much: I didn't sign up to throw my life away.
What did you just say?!
There are some topics that are off-limits!
Um...
J-Just leave it, Armin.
It's only light dinner conversation.
Heh.
Did seeing the Titans in person turn you into
a try-hard for these stupid training exercises?
Congratu—
Shut the fuck up!
Stop it!
Let's go catch a lizard, you guys!
You shut the fuck up!
That'll definitely sort everything out.
I never liked you from the start!
That's my line!
No, it's mine!
You're all talk!
Let go!
Not like you can do anything, anyway!
Hey, guys!
Well, what can you do, huh?!
More than you ever could!
Shut up.
You'll rip it, you jackass.
Hey, guys!
Just knock it off, you two!
Let go!
I think we should really go hunt some lizards!
No, you let go!
Don't move.
Gather up all the 3D Maneuver Gear.
And make it snappy.
What are you going to do with them?
Gonna sell 'em to our contacts.
It's not as if you're gonna rid the world of Titans.
So what's wrong with putting
useless equipment to better use?
Huh?
Now, guys, now!
Eren!
Don't even bother working out your next move. Just give in and shut up.
Currently
Disclosable
Information
The Wasteland Navigation Exercise
A field exercise in which two groups of cadets traverse
a wasteland. Both groups depart at the same time and
travel along two different routes, retrieve a planted
object, then return to base. The target of this exercise
is to find out how alert the cadets can stay in a
non-critical situation.
The Wasteland Navigation Exercise
A field exercise in which two groups of cadets traverse
a wasteland. Both groups depart at the same time and
travel along two different routes, retrieve a planted
object, then return to base. The target of this exercise
is to find out how alert the cadets can stay in a
non-critical situation.
We don't plan on ending her life. We'll release her en route.
But if you come after us, we won't hesitate to kill her.
You got that?
If you'd...
If you'd all acted when I said,
we could've done something!
That's just your opinion.
I don't agree.
In fact, your rash actions put everyone in danger.
We'll call off the exercise.
It's for the best.
Are we just going to abandon Krista?
That's not it at all.
We can't do anything by ourselves.
We have to wait for the instructor's orders.
And if it's too late by then?
I'm not letting this go!
I'm going to save her!
I'll go alone if I have to!
Eren...
She said she gave all her love to me.
Eren!
Stop!
We dreamed a new life, someplace to be at peace.
We don't even have our horses anymore. How are you going to track them?
That doesn't matter!
Of course it matters! I'm going with you!
But things changed, suddenly.
I need my share of payback too.
I lost my dreams in this disaster.
I'm crying,
You guys...
missing my lover.
I don't have the power
on my side forever.
Oh, where is my lover?
But he's right...
And I've got no power.
How are we going to track them?
We could split up, but there's a limit
to how much ground we can cover.
I'm standing alone, no way,
At times like these,
we should get a higher vantage point!
"If you get lost on a mountain, climb it."
calling out your name.
"If you get lost in a forest, climb a tall tree."
Those are sayings my father taught me.
Look!
Once we're done packing, we move out!
Get on with it!
What shall we do?
We could just rush them.
They've got guns.
They'll blow us away.
I have a plan.
They need to sell their stolen wares.
And the only place around here
they can do that is the town of Odel.
We should make a beeline for it and ambush them there.
We're going to beat them there without horses?
Odel? Shouldn't be a problem.
We can cut straight through the forest.
Yahoo!
On the other side of the forest, the road splits in two.
One road leads straight to Odel, so if they take that route, we have no chance.
So...
They're here.
Okay!
Assuming that all goes according to plan,
we still need to know which wagon
Krista and the 3D Maneuver Gear is in.
How do we find that out?
When we hear the sound of the wagons, we'll know.
If our gear is in the front wagon, one ring.
In the rear wagon, two rings.
If it's in both, I'll ring it three times.
And then, we'll...
attack!
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
What's happening?
You runt!
What are you doing?!
What you bastards do all the time!
I'll get those fuckers.
H-Hey!
Dammit...
I won't miss this time!
Don't!
Krista!
You bitch.
You all right?
Yeah.
Somehow.
Jean!
Eren!
We're fine.
Our 3D Maneuver Gear is too.
But Krista's still...
We're going after them!
Sasha, have you got a flare?
Y-Yes, I do, but...
Can I please use it?
This stupid kid...
I told you to get off me!
Don't kill her! She's going to make us some money!
That's how it is, huh?
Thanks to your little friends, this whole
thing's been a complete bust.
You're going to take personal responsibility for that.
Goddammit!
Stay back! Drop your weapons!
Hand over your gear without another word!
Do it now!
Shit. This ain't funny.
I can't believe I'm doing this.
I survived the Titan invasion,
but I can't grow shit in this wasteland.
And to think, I always told my daughter not to be a burden to others...
Get on with it!
What?
Mikasa!
Don't kill him!
Okay.
You guys all right?
The bandits were arrested by the Military Police,
and the incident came to a close without a single casualty.
The exercise was called off, but a record of events had to be handed in.
The report contained the truth, the
whole truth, and nothing but the truth.
May I ask... a question?
What is it?
Should we have turned back the moment our 3D Maneuver Gear was taken from us?
Or...
were our actions of chasing down the bandits correct?
I see no reason to answer that.
However...
As a soldier and as a human being,
I would take the more difficult choice.
To return to base or to chase after the bandits...
Which choice do you think is more difficult, Arlert?
W-Well...
I couldn't answer him.
Perhaps everything that happened in the forest...
was all part of the exercise, after all.
I should never have taken the helm.
Really?
I thought you were a good leader.
Nah, I'm no good at leading.
Jean's more suited to that sort of thing.
Jean?!
I'd rather not put up with that.
You'll see it one day.
I'm not so sure I will.
I wonder what kind of soldiers we're all going to become.
That was the year 848.
Two years before our first deployment.
Your dream is where my heart belongs.
sono yume wa kokoro no ibasho
It's more fragile than a life.
inochi yori kowareyasuki mono
Constantly abandoned, and constantly found.
nandodemo sutete wa mitsuke
Now, sleep in peace.
yasuraka ni saa nemure
My pulsing urges
myakuutsu shoudou ni
mya
kuu
tsu
shou
dou
ni
trample upon my wishes.
negai wa okasare
As often as I sadly forget,
wasureteshimau hodo
I remember once again.
mata omoidasu yo
In this cruel yet beautiful world,
kono utsukushiki zankoku na sekai de wa
I endlessly question the reason for my survival.
mada ikiteiru koto naze to tou bakari de
Oh, with this strength and weakness,
aa bokutachi wa kono tsuyosa yowasa de
I wonder what it is we'll protect,
nani wo mamoru no darou
when a reason ceases to exist.
mou risei nado nai naraba