Wohlan, Freund!
Woh
lan,
Freund!
Well, friend!
lan,
Freund!
Jetzt hier ist ein Sieg.
Jetzt
hier
ist
ein
Sieg.
Victory stands before us.
hier
ist
ein
Sieg.
Dies ist die erste Glorie.
Dies
ist
die
erste
Glo
ri
e.
Our legend begins now.
ist
die
erste
Glo
ri
e.
O, mein Freund!
O,
mein
Freund!
O, my friend!
mein
Freund!
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
Sieg
für
den
näch
sten
Kampf!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
ern
wir
die
sen
Sieg
für
den
näch
sten
Feiern wir diesen Sieg für den nächsten Kampf!
Kampf!
This victory shall guide us to our next battle!
battle!
I won't let you say, "My death is meaningless."
Not until but a single arrow remains.
≪一矢≫
The enemy is cruel... But we'll prevail.
Der
Feind
ist
grau
sam...
Wir
brin
gen.
ma
de
Der
Feind
ist
grau
de
sam...
Wir
brin
gen.
The enemy is titanic... So we'll jump.
Der
Feind
ist
rie
sig...
Wir
sprin
gen.
Der
Feind
ist
rie
sig...
Wir
sprin
gen.
Bearing steel blades of glory, we sing an anthem of victory.
Sieg
≪鋼刃≫
Sieg
≪凱歌≫
On our backs are the Wings of Liberty.
Sieg
Frei
heit
≪自由の翼≫
gel
der
Frei
heit
On our chests are our fists, tightly clenched with determination.
The screw of folly rips through.
heit
≪愚行の螺旋≫
gen
der
Tor
heit
Wings of Liberty dance in the blue sky.
sou
kyuu
Frei
heit
sou
kyuu
wo
ma
u
Flü
≪自由の翼≫
gel
der
Frei
heit
A Choice With No Regrets
————— Part 2 —————
This is humiliating, plain and simple!
Are you honestly telling us to accept criminals in our ranks when we've always held discipline in the highest regard?!
The morale of our men will plummet if we allow those bottom feeders to join the ranks!
I agree with Flagon.
And to suggest we take these criminals with us on the next expedition?!
I understand your concerns.
But I can personally vouch for their 3D Maneuver Gear skills.
The new formation that Erwin has been working on is ground-breaking.
It takes the emphasis away from how best to kill Titans,
and places it firmly on how best to avoid them.
I believe it'll greatly reduce the number of casualties we sustain.
This formation is likely to become accepted as the norm for our forces.
What those cretins lack are discipline and manners.
It shouldn't take too long to drill it into their skulls.
They seem to have brains in their heads. Right, Erwin?
Correct.
Meeting adjourned.
Attention!
Starting today, these three will be fighting alongside you!
Introduce yourselves!
The name's Levi.
Levi, the first thing you need to learn is some goddamn discipline.
Next!
I'm Isabel Magnolia! Nice to meet ya!
My name is... Farlan Church.
Flagon, these three will be assigned to your squad.
Look after them.
M-My squad, sir?
Any objections?
N-No...
But shouldn't Erwin...
Erwin is tasked with overseeing all the soldiers.
The new recruits will be your responsibility.
Is that understood?
Yes, sir!
Understood!
This is the barracks.
There are quite a few bunks in here.
Yay!
We're all in the same room!
Women have a separate dorm.
What?!
But I wanna stay in here!
You two men will sleep over here.
So I know you guys were living in the underground city's slums,
but do try to keep this place clean.
Huh?
Wh-What's with that look?
How dare you approach your superior with that attitude—
Sorry!
We understand. We'll try to keep the place clean.
You'll begin training first thing tomorrow, got it?
Your hand's upside-down!
Don't disobey your superiors, Levi.
We're drawing enough attention as it is.
Didn't you hear what that prick was spouting out of his big mouth?
We weren't just caught by accident, you know.
I hope you haven't forgotten why we're here, Levi.
Yeah, I know.
The Survey Corps will likely come after you.
Be sure to put up little resistance.
There are two things I'll have you do for me...
The budget for our next expedition has finally been approved after getting past all the red tape.
I see.
You're not surprised?
I'm just relieved.
I had already begun my preparations, after all.
It appears that the leader of the
anti-Survey Corps faction had a change of heart.
Nicholas Lobov, I take it?
So you know about him...
A while ago, you told me that you were certain the expeditions would be approved,
which is why you already began preparing...
Erwin, could it be that you coerced Lobov through illicit means?
There are two things I'll have you do for me.
First, you'll obtain a certain document,
which is in the possession of an Erwin Smith.
Lobov appears to have ties to the Lang Company, which provides goods for the Military Police.
It seems he was planning to redirect the Corps' funds to them.
The intel is reliable. I've already obtained evidence of this fact.
And once you've retrieved the document, kill their leader, the same Erwin Smith.
Those are the tasks you must complete.
We've arrived, sirs!
Please.
So...
What do you plan to do, Erwin?
Please don't ask me for any more details.
I'm acting on this independently.
Go down a dangerous path
and you may never make it back.
Commander.
It was only after joining the Survey Corps and coming face-to-face with a Titan
that I came to understand the futility of mankind.
Wealth and power...
Noble ideals...
All of those would disappear in an instant if the Titans were to breach these walls.
Which is why...
I will use any means necessary
to ensure that the expeditions
and our efforts to take back this world
from the Titans are not abandoned.
For the future of humanity.
The future of humanity, huh?
He will meet his end... by my hand.
I'm surprised.
Did someone teach you how to ride a horse?
Nah.
But I've always been fond of animals.
This guy says he likes me too.
No way!
I'm serious!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Those blades weren't designed to be held like that.
Do you want to die the moment you step outside those walls?
You should ask yourself the same question.
What was that?!
All I have to do is slice the nape of a Titan's neck, right?
I'll do it my way.
Was he given formal training?
No, I don't believe so.
Good. Very good!
Everything, from how we search for Titans to how we defeat them, is dependent upon individual methods!
This is getting fun!
Do you really think...
that you can take down a Titan without any training?
What?!
What's with that incredible speed?
So, is this what Erwin meant by "reform"?
So that's how we'll relay the direction to head in, correct?
That's right.
How will we communicate the level of danger?
The color of the flare will distinguish that.
Dammit. Where is it?
I thought this would be easy,
considering how little there is here.
We won't find it, no matter how many times we turn his office over.
It's probably best to assume it isn't in his room.
Then where could it be?
What do you do with something you really want to keep safe?
I'd just stick it in my waistband, of course.
I don't know if Erwin wears a waistband or not, but it's likely that he's carrying it on him.
And so I was thinking...
We could use this expedition to our advantage.
Outside the walls, Erwin and the others will have their hands full with Titans.
We just have to wait for an opportunity.
I see. Great idea!
You okay with that, Levi?
Sure.
But I'll be going alone.
What?
You two come up with any excuse to stay behind.
Bro...
Why?!
We haven't even seen a real Titan yet, and it'll be our first time outside the walls.
It may take all we've got just to make it back alive.
But if I'm by myself, I'll manage somehow.
But that's...
So what you're saying is that we can't handle it, right?
That's right. At least, that's how I feel.
How can you say that? You won't know until we've at least tried!
What's wrong? It's not like you to lose your nerve like this.
If you won't stay behind, then we're done talking!
We'll wait for another opportunity.
Levi!
Wait, Bro!
Bro.
Levi.
Let's talk about this.
No matter how I look at it, you going alone is a bad idea.
It's a fool's errand!
You said that, when we first step outside the walls,
it'll be all three of us together, right?
Have you forgotten?
It's the same.
Without the moon and the stars, the night is just as dark above ground as below it.
The color of the sky, sure.
But...
But it's different.
We know that there's no ceiling!
It's completely different!
That's right. The sky is endless.
It may be the same darkness,
but it's different from underground.
Look!
The moon is so bright!
Right?
It feels different, doesn't it?
Of course.
We're not underground.
Die Stühle liegen sehr eng
Our chairs sit so close to each other,
Wir reden die ganze Nacht lang
and we talk all night long.
We'll never go back down there.
He's right, Bro. The three of us always pulled through, right?
Dieser niedrige Raum ist nicht schlecht
This humble room isn't so bad...
It'll be the same with the Titans.
Let's do this together.
Levi, believe in us.
Wir können uns gut verstehen
as we get along well together.
So ist es immer, unser Licht ist nur das
That has always been the only light for us.
Trinken und singen wir, begrüßen morgen
Singing and drinking, we greet the sunrise.
So ist es immer, unterm riesigen Himmel
That's how it's always been under the vastness of the sky.
All right.
I'll believe in you.
Yay!
Leben wir zusammen, die Nacht ist lang
Let's live here together. The night is long.
Bro sure is a stubborn one, ain't he?
Currently Disclosable Information
Survey Corps Expeditions
The purpose of the expeditions is to map out the outside
world and to attempt to uncover the true nature of the
Titans.
However, each of these expeditions comes at a price
to the Survey Corps' numbers, and as many as
30% of new recruits will die on their first time outside.
Survey Corps Expeditions
The purpose of the expeditions is to map out the outside
world and to attempt to uncover the true nature of the
Titans.
However, each of these expeditions comes at a price
to the Survey Corps' numbers, and as many as
30% of new recruits will die on their first time outside.
Open the gate!
Today, we take another step forward!
Show me the fruits of your training!
Show them the strength of humanity!
We will now begin the 23rd expedition outside the walls!
Onward!
Incredible!
Yeah.
Not bad.
What are you doing?
Stay focused.
We're not out here to sightsee.
There's no telling when we could run into a Titan.
If we do see one, we'll clean it right up for you!
Idiot!
You wanna be the first to die?
What's your problem?
You're only able to talk like that
because you've never seen a Titan before.
You have no idea just how many
good soldiers have been eaten...
Titan spotted!
Up ahead, on the right!
One 15-meter class!
That's... a Titan?
Two 10-meter class Titans are approaching from the rear!
They're too close for us to slip away.
Prepare for combat!
Ready your 3D Maneuver Gear!
Flagon, shoot your flare!
I know!
Commander, let's tighten our formation.
It looks like it's going to rain.
Dammit!
Incredible!
They move way faster than the MPs!
They're here!
Two of them!
You two, stay right where you are!
Levi!
Let's go, Isabel!
Right!
Do they want to die?!
All of the Titans have been eliminated!
Hurry back into formation!
How was that, Levi?
We took down a Titan all by ourselves!
We did it, Bro!
We did it!
Yeah... You guys did well.
Squad Leader, those three...
Yeah.
I'm beginning to understand why Erwin
was so insistent on having them join.
I agree.
Considering it was your first time,
that was pretty impressive.
But you used too much gas.
You need to be especially conservative out here.
You're telling me to take priority of
my equipment over the lives of my comrades?
I'm saying you're making a lot of unnecessary movements.
Are you having doubts?
If you are, that'll be the death of you very soon.
Damn him! He'd better watch his back when he's alone!
He'll hear you.
Visibility's decreasing...
If the storm gets any worse, the flares won't be of much use.
Erwin, should we reduce our speed?
Yes, though I'd like to get away from
this open area as soon as possible.
I didn't know it could rain this hard.
We won't be able to make out any
rampaging Titans in these conditions.
This is our chance.
We'll use this rain as cover to get in close on Erwin.
Levi!
Are we gonna go for it, Bro?
Yeah.
But it'd be suspicious if all three of us broke away.
I'll go alone.
True, it's probably best not to carelessly move around.
We've got no choice. We're counting on you, Bro!
Go and secure our surface citizenship!
If anyone asks, tell them I went on ahead to survey the terrain.
Got it!
Are you having doubts?
Make your decision.
Just you wait, Erwin Smith.
You will die by my hand.
What the hell... happened here?
The Titan...
No way...
Did we pass each other?
So you're the sole survivor?
How pathetic.
I'll kill you!
That's why I'm here!
These documents revealing Lobov's crimes...
are a fake.
The real ones have likely reached Darius Zackly by now.
Lobov is finished.
You knew everything right from the start!
You knew we were after you, and yet you—
Believe in us.
We're counting on you, Bro!
Stop. Don't regret it.
Memories of regret will only dull your future decisions.
And then you'll begin to let
others make your choices for you.
All that's left for you then is to die.
Nobody can foretell the outcome of their choices.
Each decision you make only leads to another decision.
The expeditions will continue.
I expect you to come with me, Levi.
I don't understand.
I've never understood.
Die Stühle liegen sehr eng
Our chairs sit so close to each other,
Even if I believe in my own strength...
Even if I believe in the decisions of my trusted comrades...
Wir reden die ganze Nacht lang
and we talk all night long.
In the end...
Dieser niedrige Raum ist nicht schlecht
This humble room isn't so bad...
Nobody...
Wir können uns gut verstehen
as we get along well together.
except...
this guy sees something that I can't.
So ist es immer, unser Licht ist nur das
That has always been the only light for us.
Fine.
I'll follow you, Erwin Smith.
Forward!
Trinken und singen wir, begrüßen morgen
Singing and drinking, we greet the sunrise.
So ist es immer, unterm riesigen Himmel
That's how it's always been under the vastness of the sky.
Leben wir zusammen, die Nacht ist lang
Let's live here together. The night is long.
I will never regret this decision for as long...
If we were to assume that I'm not me,
tatoeba ore ga ore janai toshite
then could you be sure that you are you?
omae wa omae da to iikireru no ka
I shattered a vessel of sand, spilling its contents.
suna no utsuwa wo kowashite koboreta
Could you retrieve your heart and gather it all?
kokoro wo hirotte atsumerareru ka
The sound of others calling my name
dareka no yobu koe ga
is now all but noise to me.
miminari ni kawatta
It's as if time is standing still.
toki ga tomatta mitai da
Now, open your eyes.
saa me wo samase
I slipped out of the vast darkness,
fukai yami wo ore wa nukedashita
and fled from it as swiftly as a gale.
hayate mitai ni nigedashita
It's as if I was a living corpse.
ikita shikabane mitai datta
We now head beyond the walls.
oretachi wa kabe no soto e
Let us meet again in those uncharted lands.
mata aouze chizu ni nai basho de