The cherry blossoms flutter in April.
Hiyori!
Morning!
We're high schoolers now, huh?
Good morning, Yama-chan, Umi-chan.
We get to be together again.
Yeah, since our middle and high schools are affiliated.
Nothing is going to change, though.
There you go again.
Yama, you hiked up your skirt a bit, didn't you?
You noticed?
What do you mean, "you noticed"?
You aren't exactly hiding it.
Whoa! Hiyori, you did too?!
Just a little bit.
Actually, I did too.
Seriously?
Somehow, it seems like I'll meet a new me.
I'm feeling pretty optimistic about that.
NORAGAMI
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
The clock is ticking
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
Let's meet again tonight
Which club should I join?
Maybe the cooking club.
If I did that, I could make food
for Yato and Yukine-kun.
Hiyori. Hiyori!
Know what this is?
It's called divine possession.
All right, this one is a touch difficult.
Does anyone know the solution?
b
Divine Possession,
Curse of a God
This is child's play.
Pardon me?
How many years do you think I've been a god?
A god?
And thus, my fellow freshman,
I, Iki Hiyori,
will be making my high school debut today.
Nice to meet'cha!
Hey! Your legs!
Tee-hee.
Don't just go "tee-hee"!
Hiyori.
To make her high school debut
when all these people already know her...
She's pretty good!
What happened to Iki?
Does she want to change her image?
I liked her better before.
They're looking, and they're looking at me!
I can't get enough of this pleasure!
No! This person is an impostor using my face!
Everyone, listen to me!
It's pointless.
They don't even know you're there.
Yato, what the hell are you doing?!
Glad you asked!
The body of a human like you,
who hangs around a god 24/7,
is something that is as easy as pie to take over.
That's divine possession!
Though, this is the first time I've tried it.
I shouldn't have hiked up my skirt!
Give me my body back!
Is this your first time, Hiyori?
What?
You're my first too!
Hurry up and give it back!
What's mine is mine.
And what's yours is mine too.
Don't worry, Hiyori. I'll be with him.
Kofuku-san too?!
That's right, Hiyori.
I won't do anything bad.
I have a bad feeling about this!
A'ight, let's go get ourselves some new followers!
Who is that girl?
Suddenly announcing herself
atop the teacher's desk is a bit far for a debut.
Hey! Come back!
My bad.
That hurt.
I twisted my ankle.
Could you please take me to the infirmary?
What are they doing?
I-Iki-san.
What happened to you?
Nothing happened.
It's just, I've become more honest with my
feel-ings.
School Infirmary
Thank you!
Here. Feel free to contact me anytime.
Huh? What is this?
Later!
H-Hey!
Your ankle?
Each time is a mere five yen.
I provide services for 5 yen
24h Delivery
Delivery
Yato
Delivery, you say? What are you delivering?!
Could it be that?! It must be that!
No! My optimism about
my high school life is disappearing!
All right!
And just like that, I'm going to
start pulling in lots of business!
I'll do art!
Hey! We're a bunch of reckless, dreaming girls!
I sing love rituals. Every day is a great day!
I'll do music too!
I'm Hiyorin! Nice to meet you.
I'm looking forward to an invitation
to accompany you!
Oh, but if it's after dark, I ab-so-lute-ly must refuse.
What kind of drink should I make for you?
W-Water.
Okay, your order of water is in!
Here you go.
Hiyori!
Y-You haven't worked at a cabaret club, have you?
As a hostess, a few times.
You've been a hostess?!
Even though I look like this,
I'm great at stealing the hearts of first timers.
But I guess I leave a weak impression.
I've really been through a lot.
This girl is really weaving a tale.
Even though I'm such an able guy.
Really, I wanted to be born a human.
And now she's made it worse
with 8th-grade syndrome.
But I've decided to live with just one tracksuit.
Yato!
I... I will not falter anymore!
Stop that already!
Yato!
Come back here!
That guy...
He just does whatever he wants.
What's wrong?
It's ridiculous—
M-Mayu-san?!
What, were you peeping?
Not really...
As usual, he's just doing whatever he feels like doing.
That unemployed, tracksuit-wearing bum
that calls himself a god.
That tracksuit-wearing bum and Kofuku-san
snuck out by themselves,
so I came to see what they were doing.
Diakoku-san asked me to keep an eye on them.
And it's panning out just how I thought it would.
What should I do?
Come with me!
Hm?
This is not a situation Regalia can handle.
This is an alarming
and serious problem.
Sensei.
I really don't get this part.
Y-You there. That's not our school's uniform.
Teach me. Teach me.
I-I don't have much of a choice. Let's study it together.
Okay.
Oh, Hiyori! Look, look!
Tomoko, I'm begging you,
break up with me, no questions asked!
Is this Nikori Loans?
I would like to borrow 500,000 yen.
Money Collection
I'll use this to fund for my date with Kofuku-chan.
What ever shall I do?
I exchanged numbers with so many teachers.
This isn't good.
At this rate, the faculty will go broke.
I think changing schools would make me happier.
No, I can't be timid!
If it were Tomo-sama,
he would definitely be getting back up by now!
And then...
Yato, prepare yourself!
What? Yato has performed a divine possession?
Yes.
Oh dear.
And here I was just trying to admire
the falling cherry blossoms.
You have it hard, too.
Sorry about that idiot's mischief.
But is this divine possession thing really so serious?
Of course it's serious.
It is of grave import.
You see, a divine possession is an action
only allowed when there is a specific aim.
For instance, when you want to give
a special revelation at the shrine,
or wish to chastise someone.
But doing that without any aim,
much less for fun, is absolutely outrageous!
If Takamagahara found out,
it would lead to a council of the gods.
A council of the gods?
To put it simply, the gods
will severely reprimand Yato-kun.
I think I'd actually prefer that.
I'll guess I'll have to help you out.
God
Stray
NORAGAMI
Senpai!
Huh?
Good luck with today's match.
We're rooting for you.
U-Um...
If you win, I...
I...
think I could work up the courage
to confess to you guys.
All of us?
Yes! I'm so embarrassed.
Okay, let's kick some ass!
Yeah!
Now I've had Iki help me gain more followers again.
Yato-chan, you're such a bad boy.
I won't let you do that!
Tomo-sama, lend me your strength.
Oh?
Now, now. Leave this to me.
Tenjin-sama? Why are you here?
Under normal circumstances,
gods don't meddle in human affairs.
But Yato-kun's being too naughty.
Th-That being said,
you also seem quite naughty.
When meddling with humans, you need to come armed.
It suits you.
Mayu, you're also pretty playful.
Now then, let's quickly put up barriers,
then encircle and capture Yato-kun.
Please do.
Whoa, that old man is pretty dashing!
I wonder if he's a new teacher.
He could be someone's father.
Why hello there, young ladies. How do you do?
Oh my! Deep within those beautiful eyes...
Is it just my imagination,
or are you are hiding sadness within them?
Huh? How did you know that?
Actually, she had an unrequited love
that transferred to a school far away this spring.
Parting with the one you love. I understand that.
I also have experiences with that.
But it's fine.
O cherry blossoms, never forget your master.
O
cherry
blossoms,
never
forget
your
master
Lend fragrance to the wind,
that it may bring me tidings of you.
Lend
fragrance
to the
wind
that it
may bring
me tidings
of you.
The spring winds will surely
deliver your feelings to him.
That's the elderly's wisdom for you!
A woman becomes more beautiful with each worry.
Shed many a tear,
and allow your flower to bloom  .
Onee-sama, you're pretty lovely too.
Please listen to my love troubles too!
Me too!
Me too! Me too!
These adults are good for nothing.
They scored another goal.
Our team is completely useless.
They're so bad.
And even though I went
to the trouble of cheering for them.
For starters...
A bamboo shoot sprouted from the ground!
Help me!
I-It's a condor!
Is this Hell?!
Why is it only our team suffering
from this series of unfortunate events?
You're right, it is.
But why?
It's definitely your fault.
Jeez, what do I keep telling you?
Hey! Run faster! Get a move on!
Come on! What are you doing?
Just let me do a little more!
No dice. We're going back right away.
Damn it, the way they're playing,
this is gonna be a crushing defeat.
My hand has been forced.
Hey! Hey! Hurry up and pass me the ball!
Huh? Iki?
I got it.
Awesome!
Second Half
Piece of cake.
Iki! You're amazing!
That was godly!
Talk about getting carried away.
Hiyori, now's our chance to capture him.
T-That was incredible!
What?
Hurrah!
Are you okay with this?
I think I'll go freshen up and wash away this sweat!
Hurr—
By wash away sweat, he can't mean...
I need to hurry up and hit the showers!
Wait right there!
Goodness, what are you doing?
This is your body, so isn't that dangerous?
Playtime is over.
Since it's come to this, I'll take my body back by force!
Zusshino Kick!
An opening!
How naïve, Hiyori.
After being possessed,
taking your body back from me is impossible.
Ah, I really worked up a sweat.
Hey, pull yourself together, Hiyori.
That's...
No wait.
If I go any further, she really will kill me.
But, since I took over her body
this is a wall I must overcome!
However,
I must overcome my destiny.
I'm going to overcome it.
No, but Hiyori... but... however!
Hell yeah! Someone came in!
Th-This is so exciting.
To think it would go this well on my first try…
This was definitely worth trying. I'm lucky she's cute.
I wonder if this girl is a freshman.
Isn't that you, Hiyori-chan?
Oh? So her name is Hiyori-chan?
Why am I on your screen?
Wh-Who are you?!
This guy can see us?!
Huh?
Wh-What does this mean?
This should be in real time, but...
Wait, that's a hidden camera, isn't it?!
Don't accuse me of things like that.
You've got nothing on me.
You just destroyed the evidence!
Wait, Hiyori.
He's got a gloomy aura.
That's it!
He's been touched, and that's why he can see us!
His eyes look dangerous.
Don't interact with him! Let's go!
But—
Wait!
You're going to spread rumors, aren't you?!
I don't want that!
Stop it!
I was just trying to have fun!
Calm down.
If you spread rumors about this, it's all over.
If that's how it is, then...
I'll end it now!
Who knows?
This is also...
Hiyori-san.
This is bad.
Y-Yeah.
It's no good! You can't do it, Hiyori!
But!
Calm down.
Your hand!
Look out!
Kofuku!
Y-You okay?
That's our Yato-chan.
What did you come back here for?
Hey, you and your damn bowl cut!
Don't try to bite the dust in front of me!
I really hate guys like you!
But...
What a gloomy school.
S-So cool.
My shoulder... got dislocated.
All right, the game's over.
Stop it!
Please stop!
Shut your mouth!
Jeez, just think about
how much trouble you've made for Hiyori.
What would you have done
if you had permanently injured her?!
This is why you don't mature, you airhead!
But... But I was so lonely!
And Hiyori won't spend time with me.
I just wanted to live the good high school life
by taking classes with Hiyori!
Good grief, that's a kid's excuse.
Jeez. I guess I forgive you.
Hiyori.
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
My word, Hiyori-san, you're soft on him.
That's great, isn't it, Yato-chan?
You need to reflect on your actions, too.
Like this...
The cherry blossoms flutter in April.
What you did yesterday was amazing!
Your signature phrase sent chills down my spine.
So lovely.
You were really cool.
I-Iki-senpai!
Let's sweat it out again sometime.
I'll follow you for the rest of my life!
I want to be carried like that too!
I'll ask you to deliver something soon!
I have safely made my high school debut.
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
Your heart is all jagged
So you hurt anything you touch
Those eyes that frown at everything
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
Someone was laughing at you
So you put that barrier around you
But I'll reach in there with my hand
And bring you out
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
And don't let go
I want you to know that you
Are not alone any more