How dare you
insult
their memory!
That was way too easy.
I think I get it now.
I see why the Master ordered me
to dispose of you along with the Hashira.
I totally understand now!
Your very existence is just...
It just grates on my nerves, you know!
He's still alive?
You're wondering why I'm not dead
even after you decapitated me, aren't you?
It's because that thing
over there was not my main body.
While you were snoozing away,
I fused my being with this entire train!
Every inch of it has become my blood, flesh, and bone!
Do you think you can protect them by yourself?
All these humans squirming the train from stem to stern,
can you alone keep me from devouring them?
What should I do? What can I do?
I can protect only two cars at most!
Any more is just too much for me to handle!
Rengoku! Zenitsu! Inosuke!
This is no time to be sleeping!
Wake up already, will you? Please!
Nezuko!
Protect the passengers who are asleep!
Follow me, damn minions!
All right!
Explosive Awakening!
Clear the way!
Lord Inosuke is comin' through!
Demon Slayer
Infinity Train
taiyou wo akaku tojikomete
With the red sun trapped inside,
kuruma wa doko e susumu
where is the train heading?
konton no fukiareru yoru ni
In the chaotic night
bokura no koe ga hibiita
our voices resonate.
negai no akari wo tomoshite
With the light of hope
kokoro wa yume wo nugisutete
our hearts shed our dreams
shiroi michi wo yuku
and go onward down the path
kurai sora ni wa akeboshi ga mirai wo
In the dark sky, the morning star
shines down on the future,
dou shitemo sashite ugokanai kara
unmoving no matter how much we point,
yasashiku sasou kinou ni te wo futte
so we waved farewell as yesterday gently beckoned.
bokura wa naita
We cried so that
mata hashiridasu tame
we could start running again.
mayottemo nageittemo inochi wa
Even if we get lost or cry
akarui hou e te wo nobasu kara
life reaches out to where the light shines.
hikari wo inori sora takaku utagoe
Let us pray for the light, the singing voice up in the sky,
semete kimi ni todoku you ni
and let our song at least reach you.
Episode_5
Forward
Inosuke!
No corner of this train is safe anymore!
We have to protect everyone who's asleep!
The whole train has been taken over by a demon!
I repeat!
This whole train is a demon!
I knew it!
I was right on the money!
That means I was a total stud as the boss!
Beast Breathing!
Fifth Fang!
Rip and Shred!
I'll save every last one of y'all!
Then I'll have you fall to your knees!
And worship me!
As your savior!
Lord Hashibira Inosuke is comin' through!
I have to save the others!
If Inosuke can hold down the fort here,
I should go on ahead!
The situation is this bad already?
Water Breathing.
First Form.
Water Surface Slash!
Not enough.
There's no end to this!
How am I supposed to fend it off?
I can feel them scurrying around inside me.
Thrash around all you want,
but I'll just keep regenerating.
And then, after all your strength is depleted
I'll take my oh-so-sweet time
feasting on those two hundred passengers.
Thunder Breathing.
First Form.
Thunderclap and Flash!
Sixfold.
I'll protect you, Nezuko!
Protecc...
That sounded like thunder.
From one of the cars in the back?
What's going on?
Is Zenitsu awake?
What about Rengoku?
And Nezuko?
It's all I can do to protect the ones here!
This is bad! What should I do?
We can't fight in coordination!
Are the passengers in the back all right?
Damn it!
It's too cramped!
I can't swing my sword!
To think all this happened while I was napping.
How preposterous!
Some Hashira I am!
If only I could
crawl under a rock!
What the—
What was that?
A demon attack?
Young Kamado!
Rengoku!
I was quite thorough with
my bladework on my way here,
so it should take the demon a while to regenerate.
But there's no time to lose! I'll keep it short!
Right!
This train has eight cars in all.
I'll protect the five in the rear.
The Boy of Yellow and the Kamado Sister
will defend the remaining three.
During all of this,
you and the Boar Head Boy
will search for the demon's head.
Head?
But this demon is—
No matter what form it assumes,
so long as it's a demon, it's got a head!
I'll search for it while fighting, as well!
Show me how fired up you are!
Amazing! It's like he just disappeared!
Did the train shake earlier because he was on the move?
His tactical mind is just as quick, too!
Five cars, all by himself?
This is no time to be dazzled, you idiot!
Do what you have to do!
The demon's scent is getting stronger by the second!
I have to hurry!
Inosuke! Where are you, Inosuke?
Shut up or I'll end ya!
Up there, huh?
How dare that Goggle-eyes order me around!
But he was kinda...
Sorta...
He was pretty fuckin' cool!
And it pisses me off!
Inosuke! Keep an eye on the first three cars!
You ain't gotta tell me that!
And by the way, I've found it!
Already!
Thanks to my all-out Seventh Form,
I found the master's weak spot!
You did?
So, it is up front!
That's right, straight ahead!
And that front part is a heck of a lot creepier!
I can't pick up the scent because of the wind,
but if Inosuke says so, there's no doubt about it!
Is it around where the coal's loaded?
Exactly!
Got it!
All right, let's go!
Forward!
Demon Slayer
Infinity Train
Rengoku is protecting five cars for us!
Inosuke's found the enemy's weak spot!
Zenitsu and Nezuko are fighting, too!
I have to be useful, as well!
I have to protect everyone!
This is it, huh?
Hell yeah!
Inosuke!
Something's fishy, very fishy!
Especially around here!
Who the hell are you?
G-Get outta here!
It's here, the demon's head.
The demon's
weakness!
Gross!
Get away from me!
Just how many hands—
Shit!
Water Breathing.
Sixth Form.
Maelström!
Are you all right, Inosuke?
Don't act like you came to rescue me, okay?
Yeah, I know!
It's here.
Right under us!
The demon's scent is strongest directly below this place.
Inosuke! The demon's head is under here!
Don't order me around! I'm the boss!
Fine!
Just watch.
Beast Breathing.
Second Fang.
Hack and Slash!
This is...
It's his neck bone!
Water Breathing.
Eighth Form.
Waterfall Basin!
It blocked!
The gash is closing up!
It's regenerating so fast!
Not to mention, it took everything I had just to expose the bone!
I have to sever it!
Inosuke! Let's synchronize our breathing and attack together!
One of us will slash the flesh while the other jumps in to sever the bone!
Y'know what?
That's a great idea!
Good thinkin'!
Thanks!
Let's do this!
Eyes of Forced Unconscious: Sleep.
Dream
A Blood Art!
He got me! I'm falling asleep!
Inosuke!
Slash your own neck inside your dream!
It'll wake you up!
It's all right!
I can still break the spell!
Keep your eyes closed, idiot!
You'll just fall asleep again otherwise!
All right, I'm awake!
The moment I wake up, I can't help but look directly into one of those demon eyes!
I've gotta keep them closed when I wake up!
I have to keep my eyes shut!
Again!
Wake up!
You have to wake up!
Hurry!
Sever the neck!
Cut it!
Slash it!
It's just a dream!
There's no time left!
I have to wake up!
This isn't a dream, dumbass!
Don't fall for the trap!
Don't die such pathetic deaths!
I'm wearing the hide of the mountain god on my head.
I bet he's too scared to look me in the eye!
You loser eyeballs!
I see.
He's having a hard time
telling which way Inosuke is looking!
All right!
Now we just gotta rip this thing to shreds!
Inosuke!
Don't you dare get in the way of my dream!
Did he just stab you?
I'm okay.
Just forget about that bastard!
I can't do that! I won't let him die!
If we don't chop this thing's head off soon,
none of us will make it!
I hear you! Let's get moving!
Inosuke!
Let's synchronize our breathing!
We'll attack together and chop off the demon's head!
Not good!
If I fall asleep now...
I got ya!
C'mon! Follow my lead!
Beast Breathing.
Fourth Fang.
Slice and Dice!
Father, please guide my blade!
I'm going to sever that bone
with this strike!
Dance of the Fire God!
Azure Heaven!
zankokuna unmei ga
Cruel fate
kiba o mukidashite
has bared its fangs
bokura o machikamaeteite mo
and is waiting for us,
kono michi wa yuzurenaiyo
but we're not giving up this path.
mada tarinai konna mon janai
It's not enough, not like this,
todokanai nowa iyada
I don't want to miss it.
mukimi ni nare
Get up from nothing,
kizuna hitotsu ni senaka o azuke
we are one for all.
utsukushii sekai wo
I want to preserve
kimi no namida wo
the beautiful world
mamoritai
and your tears.
raimei ga toki o tsugeru
The thunderclap gives the signal,
bokura wa sora ni hanatarete
we are released into the sky,
wazawai ni furisosogu
turning into a platinum blade,
shirogane no yaiba ni kawaru
that rains down disaster.
oitekita monogatari to
There are stories we've left behind,
mou naku senai mono ga aru
and stories we can't lose anymore.
kurayami o nuritsubuse
Go straight to the edge of hellfire,
gouka no fuchi e massugu ni
and fill the darkness.
What am I doing here?
I still haven't woken up from that dream?
Huh?
Big Brother...
I will protect you!
Ne...
Nezuko!
It was a dream?
Thank goodness!
Your sweet little chin looked like a butt!
I almost forgot the preview!
Next, Episode 6, "Akaza"!
TO BE CONTINUED