What better way to die than to die while dreaming!
Your strength as a demon hunter is of no relevance.
A human's driving force
comes from the heart—the spirit!
All you have to do is destroy their spiritual core
and they'll die, just like that!
All human hearts are the same.
Weak and fragile, like glasswork.
Fall deeper.
And deeper still...
into your dream.
It'll be a deep slumber.
And then,
Waning
One
you shall never wake up again.
Waning
One
Demon Slayer
Infinity Train
taiyou wo akaku tojikomete
With the red sun trapped inside,
kuruma wa doko e susumu
where is the train heading?
konton no fukiareru yoru ni
In the chaotic night
bokura no koe ga hibiita
our voices resonate.
negai no akari wo tomoshite
With the light of hope
kokoro wa yume wo nugisutete
our hearts shed our dreams
shiroi michi wo yuku
and go onward down the path
kurai sora ni wa akeboshi ga mirai wo
In the dark sky, the morning star
shines down on the future,
dou shitemo sashite ugokanai kara
unmoving no matter how much we point,
yasashiku sasou kinou ni te wo futte
so we waved farewell as yesterday gently beckoned.
bokura wa naita
We cried so that
mata hashiridasu tame
we could start running again.
mayottemo nageittemo inochi wa
Even if we get lost or cry
akarui hou e te wo nobasu kara
life reaches out to where the light shines.
hikari wo inori sora takaku utagoe
Let us pray for the light, the singing voice up in the sky,
semete kimi ni todoku you ni
and let our song at least reach you.
Episode_3
Should_Have_Been
C'mon! This way!
The peaches over here are delicious!
And with the white clovers in full bloom,
I can make you a ring of flowers!
I'll make some really great-looking ones
for you, Nezuko!
Sure! Make lots of them!
All right, Zenitsu?
There's a river along the way,
but don't worry, it's not too deep.
Really?
Oh dear, Zenitsu!
What should I do? I can't swim!
I-I'll carry you on my back and jump right across!
I won't even let your toes get wet!
Just leave it to me!
Let's go!
Expedition Team! Expedition Team!
We are the Cave Expedition Team!
Boss!
What's up, Underling 1 and Underling 2?
Ponjiro
I can smell the master of this cave over there, pompoko!
Chunitsu
And I can hear it breathing as it sleeps, squeak!
There he is!
All right, let's go!
It's on!
Roger that, Boss!
Hey, you!
Come along, Underling 3!
Over here!
Look, I'll give you these sparkly acorns! C'mon!
Bring it on!
What did I come here for?
Oh, right.
To report to my father.
To tell him that I've become a Hashira.
So what if you're a Hashira now?
It's a worthless title.
It means nothing.
You will never amount to anything.
Neither you
nor I.
Brother!
Was father pleased to hear the news?
Do you think he will acknowledge me
if I became a Hashira as well?
He wasn't always like that.
In fact, he was once a Hashira himself.
He was a passionate man.
And yet, one day, out of the blue,
he quit being a swordsman.
Just like that.
The man who had raised us both with such enthusiasm...
Why?
There's no point in dwelling on this now.
Senjuro has been through even worse.
He barely has any memories of our mother
who died of illness when he was young,
and just look at the state father is in.
I'm going to be honest.
Father wasn't happy to hear it.
He told me that it meant nothing.
But that's not enough to extinguish my passion!
The flame inside my heart will never go out!
I will never give in!
Listen closely, Senjuro.
You and I are different.
You have a big brother.
A brother who believes in you!
Whatever path you take,
you're going to become a fine man!
Just keep that burning passion inside your heart and give it your all!
Let us both keep doing our best!
No matter how lonely it gets.
Looking good.
The ropes I created allow one to invade the dreams of whoever they're tethered to.
Dream
I always exercise the utmost caution with my plans.
Once you're asleep, Hashira or not, you're no different than a baby.
I'm so going to enjoy the feast
after I've disposed of the demon hunters.
No need to tense up so much.
Relax your shoulders.
Like this?
That's right.
That was close. He's right around the corner.
I have to make sure he doesn't see me!
I need to get to the edge of the dream!
Quickly!
The world of dreams I show them isn't infinite.
It's circular, with the dreamer at its center.
Outside the dream is the realm of the subconscious,
where you'll find the spiritual core.
That is what you must destroy.
Dream
Do that, and the dreamer
will be reduced to a hollow shell.
There it is!
I can see further but I can't move beyond this point.
I'll destroy his spiritual core right away!
And then, I'll get to experience a happy dream myself!
What an odd subconscious realm.
All this fire, it's so hot.
I must hurry.
Found it!
The spiritual core!
I've never seen a red one before.
All I have to do is destroy this...
And then it'll be my turn...
I thought humans couldn't move while they were under the spell.
Such a strong survival instinct!
I'm going to make your favorite rice crackers today, Tanjiro.
I'll start breaking old rice cakes first.
It's our lucky day, Rokuta!
We're getting rice crackers!
No fair!
Tanjiro is not the only one who likes rice crackers!
I like them, too!
Me, too!
Then, let's have them together, okay?
Can you get the grill ready for me?
All right!
I'll crush them up in the grinding bowl!
Okay, I'll be in charge of flipping them over!
I'll help, too!
Well then, I'll be in charge of eating them!
No fair!
Demon Slayer
Infinity Train
Let's go, Nezuko.
Why did I just say that?
I'm back!
Welcome home, Tanjiro.
Yeah, good to be home!
Welcome home, Tanjiro!
Welcome home!
Welcome back!
Wait, where's Nezuko?
Sis went up the mountain to pick vegetables.
In broad daylight?
She's not supposed to?
Well...
Um...
Tanjiro,
could you get the bath ready?
I'll have my hands full with this for a while.
I keep saying all these strange things.
Maybe I'm just tired.
Huh? It's gone.
I wonder what that was just now.
A toolbox, perhaps?
I guess my eyes are playing tricks on me.
Wake up!
You have to wake up!
You're in danger!
It's a dream!
It's all just a dream!
Wake up, now!
I see.
Right now...
I'm on board the train!
Wake up and fight!
Fight!
Hey, Tanjiro, gimme your pickled radishes!
No, you don't! Stop it right now!
Why are you always taking food away from him?
What's your problem?
You just had seconds!
No good! I'm not awake yet!
I'm still inside the dream!
How do I get out?
Even knowing that it's a dream...
What am I supposed to do?
I have to wake up...
Big Bro!
What should we do? The fire is—
Tanjiro!
That's Nezuko's scent!
It's her blood!
Nezuko...
Nezuko!
My uniform and Sun Blade are back.
I'm waking up!
Little by little! I can feel it!
Tanjiro?
Are you okay, Big Bro?
Brother?
Sorry.
I have to go.
I have to hurry back!
I'm sorry.
Tanjiro!
Big Bro!
Brother!
If the demon who's showing me this dream is nearby...
I have to find and defeat him quickly!
Where is he?
I have to...
Where are you going, Tanjiro?
I picked lots of veggies today!
Mom! He went this way!
He just burst into flames all of a sudden!
Mom?
Are you all right, Tanjiro?
Big Bro...
What's the matter, dear?
Why are you dressed like that?
I wish I could stay here...
forever.
I wish I could just turn around and go back.
Just like how it should've been from the start.
Right here.
If things had been as they should've...
you would all be alive and well.
And Nezuko would be able to go
out in the sunlight, under the blue sky.
If it was as it should've been...
If none of that ever happened...
I'd be making charcoal here every day.
I never would've even touched a sword!
If only this wasn't a dream...
If only this was real...
But it's too late now.
I can never go back!
Big Bro!
Don't leave us behind!
Sorry!
I'm sorry, Rokuta!
We can't be together anymore.
But you'll forever be in my heart.
All of you will always be in my heart!
There are too many things I need to thank you for.
Too many things I need to apologize for!
I can't possibly forget you!
My heart will always be with you, no matter what!
So, please...
please forgive me!
I must hurry and destroy his spiritual core.
So, this is what's inside of his soul?
How can it be so beautiful?
It stretches out to the horizon...
and...
it's so warm.
Things aren't going well, are they?
I wonder why.
They haven't destroyed any of the spiritual cores yet.
Oh well...
I guess it doesn't matter,
as long as they're buying me some time.
Not here.
But I can smell him, just barely.
Something's off, though.
It's like there's a film over everything!
The faint demonic scent is all over the place!
I can't tell the exact location!
I've gotta hurry!
I can tell that Nezuko is hurt!
If everyone else is out as well, we're in big trouble!
What should I do?
Can't I use Total Concentration Breathing?
Am I just asleep right now?
Tanjiro.
Take up your sword.
There's something you must cut down.
There's something...
I must cut down.
There's something I must cut down
in order to wake up.
I think I know what it is.
But what if I'm wrong?
If what happens in here has an effect out there,
it'll all be over!
Don't hesitate! Do it!
You have to!
My death in this dream will lead me to reality!
In other words,
what I have to cut down
is my own neck!
zankokuna unmei ga
Cruel fate
kiba o mukidashite
has bared its fangs
bokura o machikamaeteite mo
and is waiting for us,
kono michi wa yuzurenaiyo
but we're not giving up this path.
mada tarinai konna mon janai
It's not enough, not like this,
todokanai nowa iyada
I don't want to miss it.
mukimi ni nare
Get up from nothing,
kizuna hitotsu ni senaka o azuke
we are one for all.
utsukushii sekai wo
I want to preserve
kimi no namida wo
the beautiful world
mamoritai
and your tears.
raimei ga toki o tsugeru
The thunderclap gives the signal,
bokura wa sora ni hanatarete
we are released into the sky,
wazawai ni furisosogu
turning into a platinum blade,
shirogane no yaiba ni kawaru
that rains down disaster.
oitekita monogatari to
There are stories we've left behind,
mou naku senai mono ga aru
and stories we can't lose anymore.
kurayami o nuritsubuse
Go straight to the edge of hellfire,
gouka no fuchi e massugu ni
and fill the darkness.
Good job preparing yourself for all this.
It's because of what you always told me.
Even if you're in anguish,
try to be a graceful and strong person
who can feel love for other humans.
All those people suffering at the hands
of the demons... Nezuko... Take care of them...
Tanjiro.
I'm going to give it my all, Father!
Next, Episode 4, "Insult."
TO BE CONTINUED