Third Form.
Inferno Vault!
Fourth Form.
Fire Whirl!
Destructive Death.
Fifth Form.
Blazing Tiger!
Disorder!
Kyojuro!
Did he do it? Did he win?
Demon Slayer
Infinity Train
Episode_7
Set_Your
Heart_Ablaze
Episode_7
Set_Your
Heart_Ablaze
Episode_7
Set_Your
Heart_Ablaze
Don't die on me, Kyojuro.
Rengoku...
Rengoku!
You put your life on the line,
and yet it was all for nothing, Kyojuro.
Those impressive slashes you inflicted upon me have healed already.
But what about you?
A smashed left eye, shattered ribs, and damaged internal organs.
All irreparable.
If you were a demon you'd heal in a blink of an eye.
And those would be but mere scratches.
You can struggle all you want,
but a human can never surpass a demon.
I have to go help him!
But I don't have the strength to move.
All because of this injury,
and the backlash from
using the Dance of the Fire God!
Why, Kyojuro?
Because...
I will see my duty fulfilled!
No one shall die here!
Not on my watch!
I'll inflict as much damage as quickly as possible!
Flame Breathing.
Esoteric Art!
Such tremendous fighting spirit!
Despite all those injuries,
you're full of spirit and determination!
And that ironclad stance!
You have to become a demon, Kyojuro!
Let's fight each other for all eternity!
Set your heart ablaze.
Go beyond your limits!
I am the Flame Hashira,
Rengoku Kyojuro!
Ninth Form.
rengoku
Hell Fire!
Destructive Death.
Annihilation Type!
Rengoku!
I can see—
Ren...
goku...
You'll die!
You know this wound will kill you!
Become a demon!
Say that you'll become a demon!
You're strong.
You're one of the chosen few!
Kyojuro.
Yes, Mother?
I want you to think well
about what I'm going to ask you.
Do you know why you were
born stronger than so many others?
I don't know!
It is so you can protect the weak.
Those blessed with more natural talent than others
must use their strength
for the good of the world—for the people.
It's unforgivable to use strength granted by
the heavens to hurt others or empower yourself.
Helping the weak is the duty of those born strong.
You must take this responsibility seriously and fulfill your duty.
Make sure you never forget that.
I won't!
I don't have much time left.
Having a child as strong and gentle as you was truly a blessing.
I'm counting on you.
Mother,
the honor is mine to have been born to you!
He stopped it?!
His strength is unbelievable!
Even after I've skewered his guts with my arm!
Damn it!
It's almost dawn!
I have to kill him and get out of here!
I can't pull my arm out!
I won't let you escape!
No matter what Rengoku says,
I have to do this! Right now!
I have to slice off the demon's head!
Quickly!
The sun is rising!
Its light will fall here!
I have to get away!
I've got to get away!
No way I'm ever letting go!
Not until I slice your head off!
Out of my way!
Move, Inosuke!
We have to fight! For Rengoku!
Beast Breathing.
First Fang!
Pierce and Bore!
I've got to get away from the sunlight!
That took way too long!
I need to get far away from the sun!
Don't run away!
Come back here, coward!
Turn and face me!
What the hell is that brat on about?
Does he not have a brain in his head?
I'm not running away from you guys!
I'm running away from the sun!
Besides, the battle's already been decided!
He'll run out of strength and die before long!
The Demon Slayers are always fighting you demons in the dead of the night!
Where you have the advantage!
Us humans, made of flesh and blood!
We don't regenerate as fast!
And if we lose a limb, it's gone forever!
Don't you dare run away, you bastard!
You're a coward!
You hear me, dumbass!
Rengoku is stronger than you'll ever hope to be!
He's amazing!
Rengoku didn't lose!
He didn't let anyone die!
He protected everyone!
He saw the fight through to the end!
You're the one who lost!
And victory
belongs to Rengoku!
Stop yelling already.
You'll reopen that wound.
You're badly injured, remember?
If you die, Young Kamado,
I won't have my victory anymore.
Rengoku...
Come here, lad.
Let us speak one last time.
Demon Slayer
Infinity Train
There's something I recalled...
while I was dreaming of the past.
The Rengoku residence,
you should pay it a visit.
There are notes left by the previous Flame Hashira.
My father used to read them often,
but since I never did,
I don't know what's in them.
Within those notes,
you might find something...
about that dance you mentioned.
R-Rengoku, please don't talk any more.
Just stop the bleeding
with a breathing technique!
Isn't there a way to close up your wounds?
None.
I'll be dead soon.
I need you to hear me out while I can still talk.
Tell my little brother Senjuro
to always follow his heart,
and walk down the path he feels is right.
Tell my father
that I want him to take care of himself better.
One last thing.
Young Kamado,
I believe in your sister.
I accept her as part of our ranks.
Your sister shed blood to protect the people inside that train.
Anyone who risks their lives fighting demons to protect humans
is a rightful member of the Slayers, no matter what anyone says.
Stand tall and be proud!
If you ever feel disheartened
that you're somehow not enough,
set your heart ablaze!
Grit your teeth and look straight ahead.
If you curl up and hide, time will pass you by.
It won't comfort you or wait for you to grieve.
Don't feel bad that I'm going to die here.
As a Hashira, it's my duty to protect my juniors.
Any Hashira would've done the same.
The young buds must be allowed to bloom.
Young Kamado.
Boar Head Boy.
Boy of Yellow.
Keep learning and keep growing.
And someday,
become the next Hashira
supporting the Demon Slayers.
I believe in you.
I believe in all of you.
Mother.
Did I do well?
Did I use my blessings wisely?
Was I able to carry out my duties,
and fulfill my responsibilities?
You did perfectly fine.
When the train went off the rails,
Rengoku had unleashed all these techniques.
That must be why we managed to
avoid suffering any casualties.
It must be.
I can't believe he's gone.
Was it really a Waxing Moon?
Yeah.
Why would it come here?
Something that strong? I mean...
Yeah...
This is all so frustrating!
Just when I managed to break through one wall,
I find another, taller one, right in front of me.
All these amazing people are fighting with such skill and power just beyond it.
And I can't make it over to join them!
If I'm still stumbling around in a place like this...
How can I ever...
Can I ever become anything like Rengoku?
Quit whining already!
There's no point in sitting around, wondering about maybes!
He already said he believed in us,
so don't worry about anything other than living up to that!
All living things go back to the earth when they die!
Sobbing or sniveling won't bring them back!
Don't cry even if you're down!
No matter how pathetic or humiliated you feel,
you have to keep moving forward!
But you're crying, too.
I can see the tears flooding out from that headpiece.
I'm not crying!
Get over here! We're gonna train!
Is that so...
Rengoku has...
So, even Rengoku couldn't beat a Waxing Moon?
I don't believe it.
Praise to Amida Buddha.
Those repulsive demons,
I'll exterminate them all!
I see.
Not one of the two hundred passengers lost their lives?
Kyojuro did a splendid job, indeed.
What an incredible young man.
I'm not forlorn.
My life will soon reach its end, as well.
Soon, I'll be joining Kyojuro and the others
in the land of the dead.
Rengoku...
Rengoku.
Rengoku!
Screaming "Goodbye" and "Thank you" till my voice breaks
sayonara arigatou koe no kagiri
is far more important than giving in to sorrow
kanashimi yori motto daiji na koto
As I watch you go away, I want to let you know
sariyuku senaka ni tsutaetakute
I'll be ready to face anything, come rain or shine
nukumori to itami ni maniau you ni
I always thought what we had would last forever
kono mama tsuzuku to omotteita
Within my mind, I painted our days together
bokura no ashita wo egaiteita
Now I'm calling out to you
yobiatteita
to show you the embers
hikari ga mada
that still burn bright in my heart
mune no oku ni atsui no ni
We met amidst a blazing journey
bokutachi wa moesakaru tabi no tochuu de deai
We came together; we let go—for the sake of the future
te wo tori soshite hanashita mirai no tame ni
If any of my dreams were to come true
yume ga hitotsu kanau tabi
I'll have you to thank for it
boku wa kimi wo omou darou
Vowing to get stronger, I let my tears flow
tsuyoku naritai to negai naita
As we part ways, with this resolve inside me
ketsui wo hanamuke ni
Held captive by my memories and nostalgia
natsukashii omoi ni torawaretai
Wailing at the cruelty of this world
zankoku na sekai ni nakisakende
It will only get worse as time goes on
otona ni naru hodo fuete yuku
I don't want to lose anything—never again
mou nani hitotsu datte ushinaitakunai
If I stop trying and give in to sadness
kanashimi ni nomare ochite shimaeba
I might be able to escape this pain
itami wo kanjinaku naru keredo
But your words echoing
kimi no kotoba
all your wishes and dreams
kimi no negai
kimi no koe
I swore to protect them till the end
boku wa mamorinuku to chikattan da
With a roar, it's crumbling—crashing around me
oto wo tatete kuzure ochite yuku
Our one and only, irreplaceable world
hitotsu dake no
kakegae no nai sekai
The spark I reached my hand out to protect
te wo nobashi dakitometa hageshii hikari no taba
It burst into flames; it went out—for the sake of the future
kagayaite kietetta mirai no tame ni
Holding on to the hopes and dreams I've been entrusted with
takusareta shiawase to yakusoku wo koete yuku
I will keep pushing on without ever looking back
furikaerazu ni susumu kara
I will look straight ahead, no matter if I cry
mae dake muite sakebu kara
Setting my heart ablaze, I'll keep moving ahead
kokoro ni homura wo tomoshite
Until I reach that distant future
tooi mirai made