Inosuke!
Don't you dare get in the way of my dream!
Did he just stab you?
I'm okay.
Just forget about that bastard!
I can't do that! I won't let him die!
If we don't chop this thing's head off soon,
none of us will make it!
I hear you! Let's get moving!
Not good!
If I fall asleep now...
I got ya!
C'mon! Follow my lead!
Beast Breathing.
Fourth Fang.
Slice and Dice!
Father, please guide my blade!
I'm going to sever that bone
with this strike!
Dance of the Fire God!
Azure Heaven!
Demon Slayer
Infinity Train
taiyou wo akaku tojikomete
With the red sun trapped inside,
kuruma wa doko e susumu
where is the train heading?
konton no fukiareru yoru ni
In the chaotic night
bokura no koe ga hibiita
our voices resonate.
negai no akari wo tomoshite
With the light of hope
kokoro wa yume wo nugisutete
our hearts shed our dreams
shiroi michi wo yuku
and go onward down the path
kurai sora ni wa akeboshi ga mirai wo
In the dark sky, the morning star
shines down on the future,
dou shitemo sashite ugokanai kara
unmoving no matter how much we point,
yasashiku sasou kinou ni te wo futte
so we waved farewell as yesterday gently beckoned.
bokura wa naita
We cried so that
mata hashiridasu tame
we could start running again.
mayottemo nageittemo inochi wa
Even if we get lost or cry
akarui hou e te wo nobasu kara
life reaches out to where the light shines.
hikari wo inori sora takaku utagoe
Let us pray for the light, the singing voice up in the sky,
semete kimi ni todoku you ni
and let our song at least reach you.
Episode_6
Akaza
Dance of the Fire God!
Azure Heaven!
Those are some death throes!
The train's turning over!
Inosuke—
Hey! Is your gut all right?!
Y-Yeah!
Inosuke, protect the passen—
I can't die.
If I die, that'll make him a murderer!
I have to survive!
I won't let anyone die!
Are you okay, Santaro?
Pull yourself together!
I was lucky I could jump off the demon's flesh!
Shoulda seen me bounce!
Your gut feeling any better?
You got stabbed, dammit!
I'm all right.
What about you?
Never been better!
Not a scratch on me!
I won't be able to move for a while.
Can you go help the others?
Was anyone injured?
What about the engineer up front?
Let the bastard die for all I care!
We can't...
He's the one who stabbed you, remember?
His leg got crushed.
He can't even move anymore!
There's no way he can walk like that!
Just let him rot!
Then he's suffered enough already.
Help him out, will you?
Please.
I'll do it for you, then!
Because I'm a good boss!
Only because my minion asked me to!
But after I'm done rescuing, I'll rip all his hair out!
Please don't.
It's almost dawn.
Get your breathing under control.
We have to...
save the injured...
before it's too late.
Nezuko.
Zenitsu.
Rengoku.
I'm sure they're all safe!
You have to believe in them!
My body is disintegrating. I can't regenerate.
Did I lose? Am I going to die?
Me?
Ridiculous.
Waning
One
Absurd!
Waning
One
There was so much more to do!
Waning
One
I couldn't devour a single human!
My plan to fuse with the train
and eat everyone just went up in smoke!
And look what I've been reduced to!
After all the time and effort I put in!
Waning
One
All because of him!
Waning
One
It's all his fault!
I had taken hundreds of hostages,
but he still cornered me and pinned me down!
Is this the power of a Hashira?
And that brat...
He was so fast.
He never even broke out of my spell!
Not to mention, that girl!
She's a demon!
What's up with that?
A demon joining forces with demon hunters?
Why hasn't Master Muzan executed this traitor?
Damn it!
Damn it all!
It all started going to hell when he broke out of my spell!
He's to blame for this!
If nothing else, I want to kill that bastard!
No matter what!
And that boar head, as well!
I could've killed this bastard if it wasn't for him!
That boar thwarted me.
His intuition was extraordinary!
He could sense my gaze!
Have I truly lost?
Is this the end?
Oh, what a despicable nightmare this is!
What an awful, horrible nightmare!
It's always us Waning Moons
who get killed by the demon hunters.
The members of the Waxing Six have remained unchanged for over a century.
They're strong enough to defeat Hashira
who have killed an untold number of demons.
Do they have otherworldly powers?
Even after receiving so much of his blood,
I couldn't compete with them!
I want to do it over!
I want one more chance!
What a terrible, wretched nightmare this is!
I see you've mastered
Perpetual Concentration Breathing.
Very impressive!
Rengoku...
It is the first step toward becoming a Hashira, after all.
But that's just the first of the thousands yet to come!
I'll do my best.
You're bleeding from the gut.
Concentrate harder and take control of your breathing.
Picture your nerves reaching every part of your body.
Can you see the blood vessels?
The one which is torn.
Concentrate harder!
That's it.
Stanch it.
Stop the bleeding.
Focus!
Great! Looks like you succeeded.
There are lots of things you can do if you master breathing.
Not that you'll be able to do everything,
but you'll be much stronger than you were the day before.
Right.
Everyone else is safe!
Lots of injuries, but no one's life is in danger.
So don't strain yourself.
Take it easy and rest up.
Thank you.
Demon Slayer
Infinity Train
Waxing
Three
Those eyes! He's the Waxing Three!
Why has he come here?
Waxing
Three
Flame Breathing.
Second Form.
Rising Scorching Sun!
That's a fine blade.
His speed of regeneration,
and this heavy, overwhelming aura...
So, this is a Waxing Moon.
Now why would someone
as powerful as you attack the wounded?
I thought he might interrupt the
little chit-chat that we're about to have.
What exactly are we going to talk about?
This might be our first meeting, but I already hate you.
Is that right?
Well, I loathe weak humans too.
The mere sight of them makes my skin crawl.
Then it seems the two of us will never see eye to eye.
Hear me out, I have a brilliant proposal for you.
Why don't you become a demon as well?
No, thanks.
Waxing
Three
Just from a glance, I can tell you're strong.
Waxing
Three
You're a Hashira, aren't you?
Waxing
Three
Your fighting spirit has been honed to the hilt.
It's close to the edge of perfection.
I'm the Flame Hashira, Rengoku Kyojuro.
I'm Akaza.
Kyojuro,
let me tell you why you'll never truly reach perfection.
It's because you're just a human.
Destined to grow old and eventually die.
Become a demon, Kyojuro.
Waxing
Three
If you do, you can go on training for hundreds of years and keep getting stronger.
Of all the demons I've come across, this one smells the most like Kibutsuji!
I have to help fight him!
Both growing old and passing away
are things that make being human beautiful.
It's precisely because of those that our lives
are all the more precious and honorable.
Strength isn't a word that
means much in regards to the flesh.
This boy is not weak!
Don't insult him.
I'll repeat it as many times as it takes.
The two of us will never see eye to eye.
No matter what the reason,
I will not become a demon!
I see.
Technique Development.
Destructive Death! Compass Needle!
Waxing
Three
I guess I'll just have to kill you then.
Waxing
Three
I can't even follow their movements!
There were never any Flames
among all the Hashira I've killed so far.
None of them ever took me up on my offer, either.
I wonder why!
As a fellow warrior,
I just can't wrap my head around it.
Not when only the chosen few get the chance!
Watching the hideous decline of
someone blessed with extraordinary powers...
It pains me! I can't bear it!
Die for me, Kyojuro.
Die while you're young and strong.
Destructive Death.
Air Type!
I see.
Flame Breathing.
Fourth Form.
Fire Whirl!
He strikes the empty air,
but the impact comes directly at me!
The strikes travel instantly.
If I keep fighting from a distance,
it'll be tough to slice his head off.
In that case,
I'll just have to get up close!
These extraordinary reflexes
and these breathtaking sword skills, as well.
Time will steal it all, Kyojuro!
Infuriating, isn't it?!
That's just how it goes!
That's what it means to be human!
Don't move!
If that wound reopens, it'll be fatal!
Stand back! That's an order!
Don't bother with those weaklings, Kyojuro!
Give me your best shot!
Eyes on me.
Waxing
Three
Nice moves!
Waxing
Three
Rengoku!
Ol' Goggle-eyes!
Just turn into a demon, Kyojuro.
Then, we can fight endlessly and get stronger together!
You've got what it takes!
Never!
Let me make this clear.
I do not like you!
I will not become a demon!
Flame Breathing.
Waxing
Three
Third Form.
Inferno Vault!
What a magnificent attack!
Destructive Death.
Air Type!
I want to join the fight, but there's no opening.
I just can't keep up with their speed!
Those two are on a whole other level!
Getting between them would only mean death! I can feel it in my bones!
Even if I did find an opening, I'd only be in the way!
Rengoku...
You still don't get it?!
You're only hastening your death with these attacks!
Kyojuro!
Flame Breathing, First Form.
Oblivious Fire!
It's such a shame I have to kill you now!
You haven't reached your peak yet!
Second Form.
Rising Scorching Sun!
In a few short years, your abilities
will be sharpened to an even finer point!
Third Form.
Inferno Vault!
Fourth Form.
Fire Whirl!
Destructive Death.
Fifth Form.
Blazing Tiger!
Disorder!
Kyojuro!
Did he do it? Did he win?
Don't tell me...
No way!
Let's fight some more.
Don't die on me, Kyojuro.
zankokuna unmei ga
Cruel fate
kiba o mukidashite
has bared its fangs
bokura o machikamaeteite mo
and is waiting for us,
kono michi wa yuzurenaiyo
but we're not giving up this path.
mada tarinai konna mon janai
It's not enough, not like this,
todokanai nowa iyada
I don't want to miss it.
mukimi ni nare
Get up from nothing,
kizuna hitotsu ni senaka o azuke
we are one for all.
utsukushii sekai wo
I want to preserve
kimi no namida wo
the beautiful world
mamoritai
and your tears.
raimei ga toki o tsugeru
The thunderclap gives the signal,
bokura wa sora ni hanatarete
we are released into the sky,
wazawai ni furisosogu
turning into a platinum blade,
shirogane no yaiba ni kawaru
that rains down disaster.
oitekita monogatari to
There are stories we've left behind,
mou naku senai mono ga aru
and stories we can't lose anymore.
kurayami o nuritsubuse
Go straight to the edge of hellfire,
gouka no fuchi e massugu ni
and fill the darkness.
Rengoku!
Ol' Goggle-eyes!
Rengoku...
Rengoku!
NEXT
FINAL EPISODE
"SET YOUR HEART ABLAZE"
I...
I will fulfill my duty!
"SET YOUR HEART ABLAZE"