Tanjiro.
Take up your sword.
There's something you must cut down.
There's something...
I must cut down.
There's something I must cut down
in order to wake up.
I think I know what it is.
Don't hesitate! Do it!
You have to!
My death in this dream will lead me to reality!
In other words,
what I have to cut down
is my own neck!
You must be the incarnations of this boy's soul.
The sky is so clear and relaxing.
Is that his spiritual core?
Why bring me here?
Because I was searching for it?
That's why?
Even when...
I was trying to destroy it?
Why would you...
Demon Slayer
Infinity Train
taiyou wo akaku tojikomete
With the red sun trapped inside,
kuruma wa doko e susumu
where is the train heading?
konton no fukiareru yoru ni
In the chaotic night
bokura no koe ga hibiita
our voices resonate.
negai no akari wo tomoshite
With the light of hope
kokoro wa yume wo nugisutete
our hearts shed our dreams
shiroi michi wo yuku
and go onward down the path
kurai sora ni wa akeboshi ga mirai wo
In the dark sky, the morning star
shines down on the future,
dou shitemo sashite ugokanai kara
unmoving no matter how much we point,
yasashiku sasou kinou ni te wo futte
so we waved farewell as yesterday gently beckoned.
bokura wa naita
We cried so that
mata hashiridasu tame
we could start running again.
mayottemo nageittemo inochi wa
Even if we get lost or cry
akarui hou e te wo nobasu kara
life reaches out to where the light shines.
hikari wo inori sora takaku utagoe
Let us pray for the light, the singing voice up in the sky,
semete kimi ni todoku you ni
and let our song at least reach you.
Episode_4
Insult
Where the heck is this spiritual core thing, anyway?
And what's with this subconscious realm?
That naked boar-man was so creepy.
This is driving me insane!
What are you even doing in here?
You gross naked boar-headed freak!
It's pitch-dark.
I can't see a damn thing in here.
This sucks.
What is wrong with this
blond brat's subconscious realm?
Do I have to fumble around to find his spiritual core?
You gotta be kidding me.
What was that?
What the hell's a dude doing in here?
Damn you, parasite!
The only person allowed in here is Nezuko!
I'm so gonna kill you.
Where's Nezuko?
Wh-Who the heck knows?
All right, then...
Die!
No!
Wake up...
I have to wake up...
Hurry!
Nezuko!
It's okay. I'm alive.
Nezuko! Are you okay?
I'm so glad, Nezuko.
Zenitsu.
Inosuke.
Rengoku.
Who are these people?
They're all tied to the others with ropes.
Ropes?
What is this?
It's burned off.
Nezuko's burning blood did it?
It's faint, but I'm picking up a demon's scent, too!
This smell...
It's the ticket!
I knew it. It's giving off the same scent.
Infinity Train: Tokyo
.'.'.;'.      -',-.,
We were put to sleep when our tickets were punched.
A demon must be behind this!
Did he unleash such a strong
Blood Art with just this faint scent?
I don't know why, but...
I have a feeling that I shouldn't sever this rope with my Sun Blade.
Nezuko! Do me a favor!
I want you to burn off everyone's ropes!
Zenitsu! Wake up!
Get up, Zenitsu!
You've gotta wake up!
Wake up, Inosuke! Please!
Inosuke...
Attagirl.
I'm sorry, okay?
Thanks. You did a great job, Nezuko.
It didn't work.
They're still asleep.
What should I do?
Rengoku—
What are you doing?
Is a demon controlling her?
Get out of our way!
We won't get to have our dreams
just because of you guys!
Is she acting on her own?
This guy, too?
What do you think you're doing?
If you're awake, you'd better help us out!
You may have Tuberculosis or whatever,
but if you don't help out,
I'll go tell him and he won't
show you any dreams, y'hear me?
Is he the one who was connected to me?
She said he has Tuberculosis.
How awful.
It's unforgivable,
taking advantage of their weakness!
I'm sorry.
I have no choice but to fight back.
You want to stay inside a happy dream, don't you?
I get it.
I wanted to stay inside mine, too.
If only this was the dream...
Until I touched his heart...
I was willing to hurt others...
if it meant I could escape
from the pain of my illness.
But now...
Are you all right?
Thank you.
Be careful.
Right!
Nezuko!
The scent is too strong!
It's the demon!
His scent overpowering even in this strong wind!
How did I manage to sleep through it?
Even if each car was closed off and airtight,
it's unbelievable!
I was totally useless!
The demon is upwind.
Is he in the first car?
It's dangerous, Nezuko!
Stay there and wait for me!
Go wake everyone up!
What's this? Awake already?
Morning!
You could've stayed in a bit longer!
It was him!
Demon Slayer
Infinity Train
Why are you awake, anyway?
Did I not show you the sweetest dream?
I could've shown you a dream
where your family was being slaughtered.
Would you have liked that one better?
No, of course not.
Much too distressing, right?
All right, how about this?
Why don't I show you a dream
where your father comes back to life?
What I really love...
is showing people happy little dreams,
right before submerging
them into their worst nightmare.
I just adore the sight of a distorted human face.
Waning
One
I get such a kick out of it!
Waning
One
How enthralling is it to gaze at someone shattered by misfortune, squirming in agony!
I can't get enough of it!
However, I never let my guard down.
My methods might be roundabout, but I will kill the demon hunters for certain.
Infinity Train: Tokyo
.'.'.;'.-',-.,
I just had to mix my blood with the ink on the tickets.
And once the conductor punched a hole in them,
creating clamp marks,
the spell was activated.
This is a remote art.
It took more effort, but this was
the best way to avoid being detected.
Not being detected is important.
It is reality for them
until they realize it's a dream.
And yet...
how did this one manage to wake up?
And he figured it out in such a short time.
How could this be when the human desire
for a cheerful world of their own imagination
is of such great magnitude!
Intruding on one's soul is something I won't allow!
I won't ever let you get away with this!
What's this?
Those earrings he's wearing...
How lucky is that?
He came straight to me!
Could this be a dream?
Now I can receive an even
greater share of Master Muzan's blood!
And once I become more powerful,
I can even challenge a Waxing Six and usurp their place!
Water Breathing.
Tenth Form.
The Wheel of Life!
Blood Arts.
Whispers of Forced Unconscious: Hypnosis.
Go to sleep!
It didn't work?
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep!
It's not working, but why?
Waning
One
No, it's impossible!
Waning
One
He's falling under the spell over and over.
But he becomes aware of it right away,
and takes his own life in order to reawaken!
Waning
One
To commit suicide like that even if it's in a dream...
Waning
One
To take his own life with his own hands,
that takes incredible willpower!
This little bastard...
He's out of his mind!
Why didn't you save us?
Where the hell were you
when we were being murdered?
Why were you the only one to survive?
What do you think you were here for?
You're so useless!
You're the one who should've died.
How dare you go on living without a care.
There's no way they'd ever say that!
Not ever! Not my family!
How dare you
insult
their memory!
That was way too easy.
Is it possible that this is a dream?
Waning
Five
Or was this demon just weaker than him?
Waning
Five
I think I get it now.
I see why the Master ordered me
to dispose of you along with the Hashira.
I totally understand now!
Your very existence is just...
It just grates on my nerves, you know!
He's still alive?
Oh, that look on your face is so delightful!
That's the look I've been longing to see!
You're wondering why I'm not dead
even after you decapitated me, aren't you?
Fine, I'll tell you since I'm feeling so ecstatic.
It's so simple even an infant would understand.
It's because that thing
over there was not my main body.
Same rings true for what's talking to you right now.
It might look like my head but that is not the case.
While you were snoozing away,
I fused my being with this entire train!
Every inch of it has become my blood, flesh, and bone!
Look at your face.
Do you understand the implications now?
Over two hundred passengers on this train are food that will strengthen my body,
as well as my hostages!
Do you think you can protect them by yourself?
All these humans squirming the train from stem to stern,
can you alone keep me from devouring them?
What should I do? What can I do?
I can protect only two cars at most!
Any more is just too much for me to handle!
Rengoku! Zenitsu! Inosuke!
This is no time to be sleeping!
Wake up already, will you? Please!
Nezuko!
Protect the passengers who are asleep!
Follow me, damn minions!
All right!
Explosive Awakening!
Clear the way!
Lord Inosuke is comin' through!
Beast Breathing!
Fifth Fang!
Rip and Shred!
Lord Hashibira Inosuke is comin' through!
zankokuna unmei ga
Cruel fate
kiba o mukidashite
has bared its fangs
bokura o machikamaeteite mo
and is waiting for us,
kono michi wa yuzurenaiyo
but we're not giving up this path.
mada tarinai konna mon janai
It's not enough, not like this,
todokanai nowa iyada
I don't want to miss it.
mukimi ni nare
Get up from nothing,
kizuna hitotsu ni senaka o azuke
we are one for all.
utsukushii sekai wo
I want to preserve
kimi no namida wo
the beautiful world
mamoritai
and your tears.
raimei ga toki o tsugeru
The thunderclap gives the signal,
bokura wa sora ni hanatarete
we are released into the sky,
wazawai ni furisosogu
turning into a platinum blade,
shirogane no yaiba ni kawaru
that rains down disaster.
oitekita monogatari to
There are stories we've left behind,
mou naku senai mono ga aru
and stories we can't lose anymore.
kurayami o nuritsubuse
Go straight to the edge of hellfire,
gouka no fuchi e massugu ni
and fill the darkness.
Inosuke, I'm so glad you're here!
Of course I came!
I'm the boss, you know!
Now, it's time for a Taisho-era secret!
Inosuke's Kasugai Crow
is named Dongurimaru.
He's always by Inosuke's side,
but he nearly got eaten by him,
so now I hear that he's staying invisible!
Inosuke, I'm really counting on you!
Don't be so bossy!
You're just an underling!
You make me feel so secure
when you're around, Inosuke!
Don't make me feel so warm and fuzzy!
Let's go, Monjiro!
Right!
Next, Episode 5, "Forward!"
TO BE CONTINUED