What's up, you creepy nerd?
Despite almost being late, you're already sleeping?
You think you're some hotshot, huh?
No, I didn't mean to.
I bet you were playing erotic games all night.
You're disgusting!
Good morning, Nagumo!
Sh-Shirasaki...
G-Good morning, Shirasaki.
You were almost late again today.
You should try to come a bit earlier.
R-Right!
This guy is Hiyama Daisuke.
Hiyama
Daisuke
He always picks on me.
It's probably because I'm a nerd, right?
Although, she's also one of the reasons.
Shirasaki Kaori.
Shirasaki
Kaori
One of the two immensely popular goddesses in the school.
For some reason, she seems to care about me.
Since she has those childhood friends of hers,
I don't get any weird delusions about myself,
but it really puzzles me.
Good morning. You've got it tough every day, huh?
Good morning, Yaegashi.
Well, as they say, you reap what you sow.
Why don't you try to fix your behaviour then?
Don't, Kouki.
It's useless, nothing will get through to him.
I think it's wrong to take advantage
of Kaori's kindness like that.
Kaori can't take care of you forev—
Kouki.
I'm talking to Nagumo because I want to.
Kaori is truly kind!
And this is my daily life.
Maybe it would be a bit better if I stopped being a nerd.
Like that'd happen.
I'm gonna live minimally,
while dedicating life to my hobbies.
If the cost is my school life, then so be it.
Students, the bell has already rung!
Get into your seats, please.
Amanogawa!
Wh-What is—
E-Everyone, out of the classroom!
The god of this world, Ehit, summoned us here
from our higher ranked world, Earth.
We were summoned to overthrow the demons,
and save humanity from extinction.
It seems that we have powers that are many times
more powerful than the humans of this world.
But, to master that power,
we must train ourselves.
These are called Status Plates.
As the name implies,
it displays your status in numerical form.
Training everyday will naturally increase your stats.
However, your class does not change.
To put it simply, that class is your talent.
The are two class categories, combat and non-combat.
Combat classes are granted to somewhere between one-in-one-thousand to one-in-ten-thousand people .
Elemental Affinity, Elemental Resistance, Physical Resistance,
Composite Magic, Swordsmanship, Herculean Strength, Quick Step, Foresight, Increased Mana Recovery Speed, Presence Perception,
Magic Perception, Limit Break, Language Comprehension
Elemental Affinity, Elemental Resistance, Physical Resistance,
Composite Magic, Swordsmanship, Herculean Strength, Quick Step, Foresight, Increased Mana Recovery Speed, Presence Perception,
Magic Perception, Limit Break, Language Comprehension
Class  ·  Monk
As expected of a Hero class!
The values are off the charts for level one.
I anticipate great things.
Oh, you're a Priest, huh?
Class  ·  Swordsmaster
Class  ·  Priest
It suits you, doesn't it?
One-in-one-hundred people have non-combat classes.
Out of those, one-in-ten people have unusual abilities.
The most common classes are those
for crafting, such as a Blacksmith.
My classmates all have those one-in-one-thousand,
to one-in-ten-thousand classes.
I should have a great class too.
Language Comprehension
Synergist! The very definition of a blacksmith!
Your status values also suck!
You're so incompetent!
You're gonna die quickly for sure.
Hey!
I will not allow my students to ridicule others.
I'm a non-combat type too!
You have nothing to worry about.
Soil Management, Soil Restoration, Soil Cultivation, Enhanced Fertilization, Selective Breeding,
Plant Appraisal, Fertilizer Production, Mixed Breeding, Automatic Harvesting, Fermentation Proficiency,
Ranged Temperature Control, Farm Barrier, Fertile Rain, Language Comprehension
Soil Management, Soil Restoration, Soil Cultivation, Enhanced Fertilization, Selective Breeding,
Plant Appraisal, Fertilizer Production, Mixed Breeding, Automatic Harvesting, Fermentation Proficiency,
Ranged Temperature Control, Farm Barrier, Fertile Rain, Language Comprehension
Wha— Farmer is a super rare class!
Your magic power rivals that of the Hero!
Magnificent!
It seems I...
Trespassing prohibited
have the most commonplace abilities ever.