How about earning money as a pro baseball player?
If you use magic to pitch at 1,000 km/h,
you could win a huge contract!
Millions guaranteed!
When I was in high school,
I hated the guys on the baseball team.
They acted like they owned the classroom.
That's—
But, I knew that they practiced hard,
sweating under the brutal sun.
I don't want to trample on their
efforts by cheating with magic.
Uncle.
For about six years, from sixth to eleventh grade,
I dedicated my life to Alien Soldier.
I know how they must've felt,
as I sweated like they did.
No, you don't. Apologize
to all baseball players right now.
He seriously believes what he's saying.
Uncle from Another World
Refrain keshita kioku rewrite
Refrain those erased memories, rewrite​
Uncle from Another World
Monogatari no tsune ga ima miseru kotoba de
With the words that give a glimpse of the story
Don't end this, won't change it​
Dou shitatte kaerarenai
Can't change it, no matter what you do
Mokuteki wo wasurenaideite
Don't forget your goal​
Dare ga kimetan da
Who decides
Sonna ikikata rashikunai yo
the way we should and shouldn't live?
Yaritai koto tsuranuku chikara
The strength to do what you want to do​
Sore koso ga tsuyosa datte
That's what really makes you strong​ ​
UNCLE:
UNCLE: You
UNCLE: You're
UNCLE: You're fi
UNCLE: You're fine
UNCLE: You're fine the
UNCLE: You're fine the way
UNCLE: You're fine the way you
UNCLE: You're fine the way you are
Wakatteiru kara
I know that's the truth
I believe in what I've done​
No reason to go back again​
Ayunde kita hibi wo
The meaning of nostalgia
Natsukashimu imi wo
For those days I walked​
Easy losing memories​
I'm struggling now to overcome​
Akirameru koto wa nai
I will never give up​
Saigo made
Until the end​
Get down, let's get down​
Kokoro no hikari wo oboeteru uchi ni
While I still remember the light in my heart​
GET HOME
Trust yourself
Don't deny
Save yourself
Don't forget
Sold cheaper than a scouring pad
June, 2018
Compared to other sports,
baseball terminology sounds really dangerous.
Ah, like dead balls and stolen bases?
And sacrifice flies and twin killing.
Exactly.
That reminds me, I almost got assassinated once.
Huh?
You just dropped a massive bomb!
Icuras elran.
In this incident, I was totally exhausted
after exploring a dungeon.
Hold on, this person...
They were there when you broke
the barrier of Luvaldram.
They were also there when he was with Elf.
True, they were!
Were they just waiting for the right moment?
Seriously?
Found you.
Mabel.
What's up?
Because you slew the Legendary Blaze Dragon
without sealing it with the god-freezing sword,
you released me from my meaningless duty
to hand the sword down to an heir!
Hooray!
Oh, good for you! I'm glad that my efforts paid off!
Yes, yes!
He didn't get the sarcasm at all!
It's Uncle's fault that Mabel's
life went down the drain!
Why... why didn't you draw your sword?
I've been attacked many times by those with intent to kill,
as if they're playing a Psikyo shoot 'em up.
So I can tell, you have no murderous intent at all.
Actually, your complexion's looking a bit off.
Are you eating well?
I know... that you... saved the village.
So that's the time Mabel tried to kill me,
but for the time being, I took her to an inn.
You dragged her!
Where am I?
An inn.
Here.
So? What happened? I thought you
wanted to be a hermit back at home.
When I returned, my house
was being cut down for firewood.
The mayor said I needed to work
and earn my worth properly.
Mabel
Manu
If I didn't agree to that,
the village would breed me like a pet.
This world is so messed up.
That's the villagers' long-held
grudges against the Ice clan!
So, which one did you choose?
I froze the villagers' feet with the god-freezing sword,
dripped cold water on their necks, and ran away.
Eh, all the villagers?
All one hundred and eight.
Damn, how tenacious are you?!
Now I can't go back!
Is working really that bad for you?
Well...
Surrounded by flowers in a flower shop,
tasting samples at a bakery,
cuddling fluffy stuffed animals in a toy store...
I don't have the willpower to endure such harsh labor.
Which part of these jobs was harsh?
Her standards are ridiculous!
I understand.
Working your life away
on the daily grind in an office,
going drinking with coworkers after five o'clock,
I couldn't handle that either.
What? Uncle was planning on getting
a typical white-collar job?
Working in Japan was so easy eighteen years ago!
※Life was rough back then too
But I'm supporting myself as an adventurer now.
It's the best job for finding a way back to my world.
That's amazing.
I wish I could have something like that.
What? "Amazing"?
Well, in my own world, I did beat Alien Soldier
on super hard in under thirty minutes.
Huh? Is that good?
Yeah, and I'm using those skills I learned
from video games to become a better adventurer!
Your world?
Mabel, you were a guardian all your life.
Can't you make a living using the god-freezing sword?
The freezing magic you used earlier was impressive.
I-I, the guardian, should use the god-freezing sword?
But, my clan kept it for four hundred years—
Like I told you before,
no matter what anyone says, this is your life, Mabel.
You choose what you want to do.
The power to carry through is strength.
You remember it.
For now, maybe I should find a way
to break the seal of ice completely.
Oh, I went to Mount Marchid
to pick powa-powa blossoms after that,
but nothing happened.
Really?
The seal of ice is linked to my heart.
So if I become an adventurer,
and fix my gloomy personality,
then maybe the ice seal...
Gloomy?
I think being an introvert is perfectly fine!
I-It's not fine.
The villagers said they get
depressed just being around me.
My eyes are always puffy too.
I disagree!
It's fun talking with you,
and your eyes are charming like
Heather from Dynamite Headdy!
No, wait, you're making me blush!
Oh, that's right. That thing on your left hand.
What?
It's worth enough to get by for the rest of your life.
It's my responsibility,
as the one who took away your duty.
Please accept it.
N-No worries for the rest of my life?
What's this geezer doing?!
That's twice now.
I put it on while you were sleeping.
Um, I, but...
I'm sorry.
I respect you, but I don't think of you in that way.
I can't accept this.
It's melting, it's melting!
Her icy heart, gone in a second!
Come on, it's okay!
N-No, it's n-not good.
W-Why? I-I rejected him, r-right? I-I did.
Huh? I-I said no, r-right?
I found it while exploring today.
Maybe this was meant to be.
There are only seven cosmite rings in the world,
and this is one of them.
This is my token of apology.
I-I can't accept such a precious ring.
Well, it's late now. Stay here for tonight.
It's a small bed, so there's not much room for two.
As Elf is staying here too,
she may let you stay in her room.
E-Excuse me.
What?
Do you have any money I can borrow
for the public bath?
I haven't bathed in a while.
Do you think you smell?
You smell a little earthy, but it's not a bad smell.
D-Don't smell me!
Well, if you sell the ring,
you can afford the bathing fee.
Huh?
Sell the ring?
Yes.
As I said, sell the ring and never worry
about money for the rest of your life.
Hey, orc face! It's late!
Have you awakened to some sort of orc instinct?
T-Then, I'll stay with you until you feel bett—
He turned me down.
Hey, you! Lend me a hand! She's out of control!
I see.
Huh? Wai—Stop!
My defense is low because I spent my spirits
in the dungeon earlier today!
And that's how I was almost assassinated
and sealed with ice until the next morning.
Isn't that horrible?
Yeah.
Yes.
You were horrible.
Still, you're amazing!
You said you beat Alien Soldier in thirty minutes?
To be precise, it was twenty nine minutes
and twenty nine seconds!
It was so intense.
Really?
The key was that I saved up Homing Force instead of using it freely.
Just run through with Ranger Force for easy battles...
Ah, someone beat it in twelve minutes in this video!
How dare you, Internet?
It's not the Internet's fault, Uncle.
Oh, speaking of the Internet,
what does it mean
by the North American version of the game?
Oh, you mean the region-code.
The same game can be in different
languages by the sales regions.
If it's in English, I'd be in trouble.
But I kind of understand what's said
at the beginning of Altered Beast.
Like, "Go, hero, defeat the evil!," or something like that.
Wait, let me use a translation app.
Rise from your grave.
Grave?!
The main character was dead?!
You were totally off.
Why's that?
Maybe the blood of Another World.
Wait, they're still talking.
Perhaps he's the same
as the ancestors of the Ice clan.
A traveler transported here
from Japanbahamal in Irellars.
Wait, she just said...
Granbahamal raybelio
Mildo shaine zad
All creation, summon
an ice storm in this residence!
I am human, not orc
All creation, summon
an ice storm in this residence!
I am human, not orc
All creation, summon
an ice storm in this residence!
I am human, not orc
Hey, she just said "Japanbahamal."
What?
How do they know about Japan?
Let's take a look.
What a disaster that he put the ring on you
while you were sleeping.
Marriage while sleeping, rather,
a forced marriage by an orc while sleeping,
is a lifelong trauma.
No one would marry you after you married a filthy orc.
Don't despair.
A-Actually, you don't seem to mind it.
Why's that?
Maybe the blood of Another World.
Perhaps he's the same
as the ancestors of the Ice clan.
A traveler transported here
from Japanbahamal in Irellars.
I see. They were talking while I was sealed in ice.
They were talking about Japan, right?
Raybelio yuul elran.
The founder of the Ice clan
was a warrior from Japanbahamal,
four hundred years ago.
He lost his life in a war in Japanbahamal,
and was given a new body and life in Granbahamal.
Then, he received a message from God.
"Hear me, traveler.
I shall grant you one power
to survive this harsh world."
The knight responded with his wish.
"Give me a sword that can slay you."
Divine bonus, a classic pattern of the Another World reincarnation fantasy!
The warrior's reply was so cool!
What happened next?!
The god responded,
"You wish to have the power to slay God.
"Ha ha ha, how interesting."  Howev—
Anyway, does that ugly orc
face look like a human to you?
"Ha ha ha, how interesting."
Because you share blood?
"Interesting."
Seriously?
"Intere—"
You can't mean that.
I-It's just getting interesting.
C-Could you be a little more patient?
I read all this in a book in my village.
Shoo, shoo.
The knight acquired the god-freezing sword
and studied at the Shrine of Wisdom,
fell in love with a shrine maiden,
broke the seal of the sword,
and slew the Legendary Blaze Dragon.
The sword's been kept in the clan for generations.
She spoiled it just when it was getting interesting!
B-Back to my point, do you see the orc face as...
T-Telling this story is the only thing I'm confident at.
I've been practicing so hard...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, don't cry.
T-There, there.
I didn't get that.
Huh?
What?
I didn't get anything cool like
the god-freezing sword!
You must have received
magic power as the divine bonus.
I didn't get any bonus! I even didn't talk with a god!
Then, let's look at the moment you
were transported eighteen years ago!
You're right.
Eighteen years?
Can you rewind that far?
It's a long time ago,
so it may take a while to search.
Well...
Mob lynches, execution, execution...
He's mumbling some disturbing things!
He was constantly hunted
because they thought he was an orc variant.
Seriously?
Found it!
You shitty orc! Are you trying to eat my cow?
No, Uncle, this isn't the right one!
Then how about this one?
Burn this pagan evil orc!
That's the time you made the magical vase!
So, this one?
Nope!
This one?
No!
This?
You've been hunted too many times!
I'm a real heavy sleeper.
If I was attacked while asleep, I couldn't avoid it.
How did you even manage to survive this long...
Hm, is this it?
What's going on?
It's similar to the resurrection
spell of divine magic.
I first witnessed this magic much later on.
Why's it in such an old memory?
Wait. Isn't that you when you were seventeen,
right when you arrived in that world?
I see.
This was how my body was formed in Granbahamal.
Did a god create your body?
Seems like it.
This is where I was mistaken
for an orc variant and got beat up.
I didn't know their language,
but I offered them my money.
They mistook the cash for spell cards
and beat me even more.
January, 2000. I was off to buy new video games
with my holiday money.
I was so happy, but got in an accident on the way,
and the rest is history.
What was I going to buy?
What a heavy story.
W-Wait. I hear something.
Huh? Is this the god's voice?
Wait, let me turn up the volume.
Wǒ shì yì shìjiè zhī shén
nǐ shì zhuǎnyí zhì rén.
Zài zhège kēkè de shìjiè lǐ wǒ huì
gěi nǐ yīzhǒng shēngcún de lìliàng.
I don't understand!
Did the god mix up the region code or something?
What could they be mumbling
while I was getting clobbered senseless?
Uncle, I'll translate it! Please rewind thirty seconds!
Okay.
Qīn'ài de gùkè péngyǒu nǐmen hǎo.
Hello, dear customers
and friends.
We sincerely welcome
you to Granbahamal.
Hello, dear customers
and friends.
We sincerely welcome
you to Granbahamal.
Zhōngxīn huānyíng nín guānglín gé rán bāhāmǎěr.
In-store announcement?
Totally prerecorded.
She's saying, "I will give you power,"
just like Mabel said.
Wǒ shì yīgè bùtóng shìjiè de
shàngdì nǐ shì zhuǎnyí de rén.
I see. What I wished at that moment became my ability.
Zài zhège kēkè de shìjiè lǐ...
So your powers must have awakened then!
This is when you gained unrivaled magic power!
Your wish was "I want the power
to exterminate these shitheads."
Or "Make them miserable
and make them regret ever being born," right?
T-Takafumi, did something happen to you
while you were in high school?
※His parents divorced
No, what I was thinking was...
If only...
If only I could speak their language, we could understand each other!
Oh, this one.
Shēngcún tōngguò wǒ shíxiànle nǐ de yuànwàng.
Well...
Rúguǒ nǐ qù duō ěr duō shāndǐng bù nín kěyǐ
zài zhīshì shèngdì huòdé zuìdī xiàndù de zhīshì.
"Approved. Your wish has been granted.
You will be able to acquire the minimum amount
of knowledge if you summit Mount Dordo," it says.
So, then, Uncle's magic power was...
translation?
Ahh.
So lame.
Suddenly, I understood their language,
so I guess that was my bonus.
So you could have just learned the language
at Mount Dordo instead?
...am not
I am not an orc!
Oh, I see.
This is how you spoke to each other!
Well, this is quite expected of Uncle, in a way.
No.
I was sold to a freak show
as a rare orc who knew the human language.
I was worth three copper coins.
And then—
Wait, Uncle!
I need some coffee.
Me too!
Oh, good idea! Let's have a coffee break!
The god seemed to have lost their passion for work.
The residents of Another World
were as shitty as always.
The horrible story seemed to have no end,
so we decided to have a coffee break.
Delish.
Good beans.
What a profoundly deep flavor.
​​Nagaku nobita kage
​​I saw you off with a "see you"
Jaa ne tte miokutta
And watched as your shadow lengthened
Dou shite kizukanai no
Why don't you notice me?
Konna ni mitsumeteiru no ni
I've been staring at you for so long
Ienai omoi ga
I can't express my emotions
Yukiba sagashite
I'm searching for a place to go​
Nijimu orenji ni
The orange blur
Sotto nobotta
Gently rises in the distance
Kanadeyou
I dance alone
Chiisana chiisana hoshi no inori
And pray to a tiny, tiny star​ ​​
Mada tooi sono sora
The star that's so far away in the sky
Itsuka terashitai
Someday it will shine bright
Todoketai todokanai
I need to make it clear, you need to understand
Itoshisa sono bun dake
My love for you that's so strong
Taema naku matataku yo
The stars shine
Tada hitori no kimi e
Only for you